{"question": "In which movie you can see Jon Stewart?", "answers": ["Khiladiyon Ka Khiladi", "Zapruder film", "Jism 2", "Doogal"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jon Stewart?", "answers": ["Con Air", "Jay and Silent Bob Strike Back", "Yes Man", "The Manchurian Candidate"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jon Stewart?", "answers": ["Aarzoo", "American Hustle", "Suspect Zero", "Wishful Thinking"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jon Stewart?", "answers": ["Playing by Heart", "Rat Race", "Ocean's Twelve", "Once Upon a Time Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jon Stewart?", "answers": ["Porco Rosso: The Last Sortie", "The Great Buck Howard", "Big", "Attila"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jon Stewart?", "answers": ["Big Daddy", "Attila", "Death Race 2000", "Kadhalukku Mariyadhai"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jon Stewart?", "answers": ["Zandalee", "Quicksilver Highway", "Diljale", "Mixed Nuts"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jon Stewart?", "answers": ["The Rundown", "Malcolm X", "The Faculty", "The Man Who Shot Liberty Valance"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jon Stewart?", "answers": ["Mei and the Kittenbus", "Be Cool", "This Is the End", "The Adventures of Tom Thumb and Thumbelina"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jon Stewart?", "answers": ["Don't Drink the Water", "Veyyil", "Flatliners", "Half Baked"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jon Stewart?", "answers": ["Just for Laughs: Stand-Up: Vol. 3: Launching Pad", "Ainthu Ainthu Ainthu", "Found a Groom", "Sabrina"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jon Stewart?", "answers": ["Mrs. Soffel", "Much Ado About Nothing", "Death to Smoochy", "Eat Pray Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jon Stewart?", "answers": ["Rosewater", "Deadfall", "Pitch Black", "Tears of the Sun"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jon Stewart?", "answers": ["The Secret Policeman's Other Ball", "On Your Mark", "The Office Party", "Pilot Season"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jon Stewart?", "answers": ["Do the Right Thing", "Since You've Been Gone", "Shadows and Fog", "Blood Alley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Family Bond", "Seven", "Blade Runner", "Love Actually"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["The Bowling Ball", "Birdy", "London 2012 Olympic Opening Ceremony: Isles of Wonder", "The Weather Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["XXX: State of the Union", "Shakti: The Power", "The Lion King", "Vincent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Hot Shots! Part Deux", "Fast Times at Ridgemont High", "Tai Chi Master", "I Heart Huckabees"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Revolution", "Spike & Mike's Classic Festival of Animation", "City of Ember", "The Appointments of Dennis Jennings"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Blackadder: Back & Forth", "Khatta Meetha", "The Terminator", "Devdas"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Maybe Baby", "Gran Torino", "The Whole Nine Yards", "Romance & Cigarettes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Keeping Mum", "The Medallion", "Who Do I Gotta Kill?", "Marigold"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["The Jubilee Girl", "Madea's Big Happy Family", "Love and Death", "Fathers' Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Comic Relief 2007", "ATL", "Seeking a Friend for the End of the World", "Once Upon a Time Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["The Wrong Man", "Johnny English Reborn", "Courage Under Fire", "Mr. & Mrs. Smith"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Aravaan", "Rajavin Parvaiyile", "Deewana", "Four Weddings and a Funeral"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Salem's Lot", "Riding the Bullet", "Rich and Strange", "Bean"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["9", "The Terminator", "The Tommyknockers", "Dead on Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["The Nightmare Before Christmas", "Blackadder's Christmas Carol", "How to Train Your Dragon", "LOL: Laughing Out Loud"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["The Siege", "Doctor Who and the Curse of Fatal Death", "Ghosts of Mars", "The Local Stigmatic"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["The Other Guys", "Captive", "As Long as I Live", "Mr. Bean's Holiday"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["The Lone Ranger", "Just for Laughs: Stand-Up: Vol. 3: Launching Pad", "Night at the Museum: Battle of the Smithsonian", "Another Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Princess Mononoke", "The Dark Knight", "Logan's Run", "Never Say Never Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Island in the Sky", "Rasigan", "The Tall Guy", "Too Young the Hero"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Rat Race", "Cujo", "Whatever Works", "The Imaginarium of Dr. Parnassus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Shutter Island", "Unknown Soldier", "Spider-Plant Man", "Risky Business"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["K\u016bs\u014d no Sora Tobu Kikaitachi", "The Secret Policeman's Other Ball", "300", "Sendhoorapandi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Machete", "Bernard and the Genie", "Pr\u00eat-\u00e0-Porter", "Kelly's Heroes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Bringing Out the Dead", "The Witches", "Duplicity", "Closer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Found a Groom", "Rowan Atkinson Live!", "Hanover Street", "The Bourne Identity"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Scooby-Doo", "Winter Passing", "The Negotiator", "16 Blocks"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rowan Atkinson?", "answers": ["Johnny English", "Rob-B-Hood", "Rumble in the Bronx", "Fist of Legend"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Manhattan Murder Mystery", "Special 26", "The Devil's Own", "This Means War"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Pom Poko", "Annie", "2 Guns", "Who Am I?"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Old Dogs", "After Earth", "Platoon", "Ender's Game"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Limitless", "Hondo", "Wild Wild West", "Red River"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Black Mask", "She's the Man", "The Pursuit of Happyness", "Flesh and Blood"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Arizona Dream", "Time Share", "Raising Arizona", "Transporter 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Without Limits", "Body of Lies", "Winter's Tale", "Old Dogs"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Suhaag", "Made in America", "Manglehorn", "Tim Janis: Beautiful America"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Ali", "All About Steve", "The Country Bears", "Kiss of the Dragon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Love Today", "Six Degrees of Separation", "Priya: The Charming Girl of India", "Shadowmancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Grown Ups 2", "Enemy of the State", "Dickie Roberts: Former Child Star", "Full Frontal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Where the Day Takes You", "Dostana", "Billu Barber", "Always"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Misery", "Paradise Alley", "The Legend of Cain", "Kadhalukku Mariyadhai"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Laffapalooza! #1", "Sin City: A Dame to Kill For", "Hard Rain", "Grindhouse"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Independence Day", "Cocaine Cowboys", "The World According to Garp", "Dance Me to the End of Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Hitch", "Hatya: The Murder", "Titan A.E.", "The 39 Steps"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["The Rookie", "The Lords of Flatbush", "Seven Pounds", "Bananas"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["The Manxman", "Men in Black", "300", "The Conqueror"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["You Don't Know Jack", "True Crime", "Son of Sardaar", "Hancock"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Stuff", "Grand Champion", "Good Will Hunting", "Men in Black II"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Little Big Soldier", "Coimbatore Mappillai", "Bucky Larson: Born to Be a Star", "La escribana de uraba"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Best of Raw: Vol. 1", "Awakenings", "The American Can", "Tropic Thunder"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Humko Deewana Kar Gaye", "The Legend of Bagger Vance", "Billy Madison", "Runaway Bride"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Big Fish", "The Jayne Mansfield Story", "Sleepwalkers", "Bad Boys"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["The Romantics", "16 Blocks", "I Am Legend", "Kung Fu Panda 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Rounders", "The Will Smith Music Video Collection", "The Truman Show", "The Jacket"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["The Secret Life of Bees", "Now You See Me", "The Bucket List", "Lagaan: Once Upon a Time in India"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Shark Tale", "4 the People", "The Thin Pink Line", "The Wicker Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Evolution", "Pardes", "Where the Wild Things Are", "Men in Black: Alien Attack"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Turbo", "The Tourist", "Hancock 2", "Boys"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Koyla", "Jaanwar", "Magic Mike", "Lakeview Terrace"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Reach Me", "The Sugarland Express", "Gangster Squad", "The Karate Kid 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Joe Kidd", "Skyscraper", "Saving Face", "Dick Tracy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Men in Black 3", "Try Seventeen", "Strays", "Salt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["21 Jump Street", "Bad Boys II", "Mississippi Masala", "Frenzy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Mumbai Diaries", "The Karate Kid", "Strangers on a Train", "Thuppakki"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Showtime", "The Libertine", "Menace II Society", "Der Fuehrer's Face"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Smith?", "answers": ["Wake of the Red Witch", "Spider-Plant Man", "Lethal Weapon 2", "ATL"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Patriot Games", "Alice & Viril", "Coimbatore Mappillai", "Shakti: The Power"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Saturday Night Fever", "Sachein", "Qayamat Se Qayamat Tak", "Something Like a Business"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Gangs of New York", "Red Lights", "Criminal", "Villu"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Annie", "Udhaya", "The Bone Collector", "Red Sonja"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Manglehorn", "1911", "She's the Man", "Kuruvi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Shanghai Knights", "Minority Report: Bonus Material", "Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man's Chest", "Priyamaanavale"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Nanban", "Pyaar Kiya To Darna Kya", "8", "Exit Strategy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Elephant White", "Ali", "Ninaithen Vandhai", "Kicking & Screaming"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Shark", "Apt Pupil", "Hum Hain Rahi Pyar Ke", "Punchline"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Kick-Ass 2", "The Nightmare Before Christmas", "Thamizhan", "Tyler Perry's Laugh to Keep from Crying"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Pushing Tin", "The Astronaut's Wife", "Azhagiya Tamil Magan", "Arrietty"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["The Curse of the Jade Scorpion", "Yohan: Adhyayam Ondru", "Get Shorty", "Awakenings"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Get the Gringo", "My Least Favorite Career", "Deewane", "Khushi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Pokiri", "Leaving Las Vegas", "The Waterboy", "Tomorrow Never Dies"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Tequila Sunrise", "Valet Guys", "Velayudham", "Dan in Real Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Half Baked", "The Preacher's Wife", "Rowdy Rathore", "Mad City"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Blackadder's Christmas Carol", "Yuvan Yuvathi", "Menace II Society", "Rasigan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["The Hudsucker Proxy", "Romeo + Juliet", "The Adventures of Tintin: The Secret of the Unicorn", "Sendhoorapandi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["The Brazilian Job", "Sky", "Nenjinile", "Orphan's Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Intolerable Cruelty", "The I Love Lucy 50th Anniversary Special", "Kannukkul Nilavu", "The Corruptor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Laffapalooza! #1", "Minsara Kanna", "The Forbidden Kingdom", "Beavis and Butt-head Do America"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Aladin", "Looking for Richard", "Cyborg 2", "Love Today"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Number Seventeen", "Nerrukku Ner", "WWE: WrestleMania 27: Vol. 2", "Much Ado About Nothing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Thuppakki", "Sea of Love", "The Avengers: Age of Ultron", "Cool World"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Baazi", "Elephant White", "Bagavathi", "Saudagar"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["The Truman Show", "For Colored Girls", "Madhurey", "Hey Ram"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["The Fighter", "Gridiron Gang", "Magnolia", "The Bodyguard"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["The Thin Pink Line", "Cocaine Cowboys", "Priyamudan", "Joker"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["The Singing Detective", "The Quick and the Dead", "Naalaiya Theerpu", "Salt"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Pudhiya Geethai", "Captain America: The First Avenger", "Looking for Richard", "Northern Lights"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Grand Champion", "Gods of Egypt", "Youth", "Cinema16: American Short Films"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["1408", "Vishnu", "O.S.O.", "Suhaag"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Naajayaz", "Shahjahan", "American Breakdown", "The Good Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Silsila", "Parker", "Poove Unakkaga", "Sinbad: Legend of the Seven Seas"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["K\u016bs\u014d no Sora Tobu Kikaitachi", "Ek Tha Tiger", "Once More", "Murder!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Gerry", "Khiladi 786", "RED", "Nilaave Vaa"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["The Cold Light of Day", "Endrendrum Kadhal", "The Conqueror", "Say Anything..."], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Confessions of a Dangerous Mind", "Risky Business", "Being Flynn", "Aadhi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Snake in the Eagle's Shadow", "Maniac", "Vettaikkaaran", "Riding the Bullet"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["To the Limit", "The 39 Steps", "Friends", "Island in the Sky"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["License to Wed", "Paint Your Wagon", "Ghilli", "The Wedding Singer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Rajavin Parvaiyile", "The Nightmare Before Christmas", "Looper", "Dosti: Friends Forever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Deva", "Playing for Keeps", "Raakh", "Magic Mike 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Hairspray", "Kadhalukku Mariyadhai", "Foxfire", "One More Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Saroja", "Coach Carter", "The Family That Preys", "Bad Boys"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Tashan", "Celebrity News Reels: Hollywood's Most Infamous Couples and Ugliest Breakups", "Vaseegara", "A.I. Artificial Intelligence"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["The Young Master", "City of Ember", "Thirumalai", "The Brothers Grimm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Fire with Fire", "Sivakasi", "Found a Groom", "Thick as Thieves"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Badri", "Grudge Match", "Abbot Hai Teng of Shaolin", "Heartbreak Ridge"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Star Wars Episode III: Revenge of the Sith", "Paranoia", "Thulladha Manamum Thullum", "Jewel of the Sahara"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vijay?", "answers": ["Frost on Satire", "Tooth Fairy", "Brannigan", "Thirupaachi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Under the Sea 3D", "The Haunted Mansion", "Poltergeist", "The Great Gatsby"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Amblin", "Transcendence", "After Earth", "Sixteen Candles"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Lincoln", "Fifty Shades of Blue", "Inside Job", "Baaghi: A Rebel for Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Evolution", "Original Sin", "Seven", "The Three Caballeros"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Taking Chance", "Dazed and Confused", "Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade", "Mighty Aphrodite"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Reservoir Dogs", "Memoirs of a Geisha", "I Am Legend", "D-Tox"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["The Great Gatsby", "The Curious Case of Benjamin Button", "Night Skies", "Our Father"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["The Alamo", "The Lost World: Jurassic Park", "The Pacifier", "Antz"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Dick Tracy", "Hook", "Cast Away", "Dog Day Afternoon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["War of the Worlds", "Next", "Trucks", "The Astronaut's Wife"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Shout", "Hamlet", "Celebrating AFI", "The Color Purple"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["The Mosquito Coast", "Dreamcatcher", "The Sugarland Express", "Grand Champion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Shade", "JFK", "Casper", "The Game of Their Lives"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Love Part 2", "Lara Croft: Tomb Raider", "Catch Me If You Can", "Volunteers"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Stalk of the Celery Monster", "The Adventures of Tintin: The Secret of the Unicorn", "Plane Crazy", "Under Suspicion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Money for Nothing", "Tooth Fairy", "Indiana Jones and the Raiders of the Lost Ark", "Black"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Wild at Heart", "A Home of a Million Gold", "Welcome", "Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Reservoir Dogs", "Captain America: The Winter Soldier", "Band of Brothers", "Despicable Me 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Cabin Boy", "Joe Versus the Volcano", "Shahjahan", "Bewafaa"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Coriolanus", "War Horse", "Trespass", "Meeting Evil"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Tears of the Sun", "Twister", "World's Greatest Dad", "Rudderless"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Close Encounters of the Third Kind", "Crash", "The I Love Lucy 50th Anniversary Special", "Three Kings"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Regarding Henry", "Innerspace", "After Earth", "Dolores Claiborne"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Last Action Hero", "A.I. Artificial Intelligence", "Boobie", "Twin Dragons"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Schindler's List", "Ultimate Fights", "Courage Under Fire", "Miracles"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["The Last Stand", "Letters from Iwo Jima", "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham", "The Journey of Natty Gann"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["True Romance", "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial", "Collateral", "Thick as Thieves"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Deuce Bigalow: European Gigolo", "The Last Witch Hunter", "Flags of Our Fathers", "...And Justice for All"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["The Last Witch Hunter", "The Normal Heart", "The Good Life", "Three O'Clock High"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Runaway Bride", "Super 8", "The Men Who Stare at Goats", "The Descendants"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Minority Report", "The Bounty Hunter", "Sin City: A Dame to Kill For", "Poor Things"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["The Medallion", "The Marriage Counselor", "Vampire's Kiss", "Amistad"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Ghilli", "Jaws", "Sabotage", "Forces of Nature"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Step Up", "Summer City", "Big Daddy", "We're Back! A Dinosaur's Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Mad Max: Fury Road", "Something Evil", "That Thing You Do!", "Sleeper"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["The Devil's Rain", "The Marriage Counselor", "Love Today", "Always"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Tomorrow Never Dies", "The Terminal", "Fading Gigolo", "Qayamat: City Under Threat"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["An American Tail: Fievel Goes West", "The Sex and Violence Family Hour", "Cry Freedom", "Johnny English Reborn"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["This Is the End", "Love", "Jurassic Park", "Veer-Zaara"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["...And Justice for All", "Don: The Chase Begins Again", "Christine", "Twilight Zone: The Movie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Spike & Mike's Classic Festival of Animation", "Paul", "Judwaa", "Speed 2: Cruise Control"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Saving Private Ryan", "Kaal", "Fast Times at Ridgemont High", "Frenzy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["The Devil's Rain", "Duel", "Thunder Run", "Blood Work"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom", "Much Ado About Nothing", "The Good Girl", "Back to the Future Part II"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["American Sniper", "The Nightmare Before Christmas", "Red Surf", "Kevin Hart: Laugh at My Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Revolver", "Star Wars Episode II: Attack of the Clones", "Tai Chi Master", "Munich"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Used Cars", "Homefront", "The Grifters", "Mallrats"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["The Goonies", "Four Weddings and a Funeral", "Love Today", "Knight and Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["1941", "High School Musical 2", "Child in the Night", "Bhoothnath"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Snake in the Eagle's Shadow", "Firelight", "My Name is Khan", "The Other Guys"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steven Spielberg?", "answers": ["Toy Story", "Scenes from Django Unchained - UK Winner", "Peter Pan", "Empire of the Sun"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Assassins", "The Firm", "The Big Boss", "Two of a Kind"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Love Part 2", "Seeking Justice", "Rio Lobo", "Naalaiya Theerpu"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Doing Time on Maple Drive", "The Game of Death", "The Appointments of Dennis Jennings", "Thank You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Lincoln's Gettysburg Address", "Way of the Dragon", "Junior", "Pudhiya Geethai"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Who Am I?", "The Boy in the Plastic Bubble", "Spirited Away", "An Orphan's Tragedy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Hollywood Homicide", "Pocahontas", "Clerks II", "The Orphan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Pretty Woman", "Thirupaachi", "A Mother's Tears", "The Pursuit of Happyness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Sweet Time Together", "Heart Stopper", "Mrs. Doubtfire", "Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Infancy", "Beretta's Island", "Alexander", "The Pacifier"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Grease", "Pirates of the Caribbean 5", "The Hardy Men", "A Home of a Million Gold"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["We Owe It to Our Children", "Crimes and Misdemeanors", "Much Ado About Nothing", "Curly Sue"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["In the Land of Blood and Honey", "Unbroken", "Mr. Nice Guy", "Meng li xi shi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Four Rooms", "9", "License to Kill", "Bruce Lee: A Warrior's Journey"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Marlowe", "Coolie", "Casino", "Nothing in Common"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["The Big Hit", "The Object of My Affection", "WWE Tagged Classics 2003: No Way Out", "The Thunderstorm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Big Jake", "Golmaal Returns", "Fu gui fu yun", "Don't Drink the Water"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Bruce Lee in G.O.D.: Shib\u00f4teki y\u00fbgi", "The Mist", "Chennai Kadhal", "Losin' It"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Blossoms & Blood", "The Kid", "Marley & Me", "The Vanishing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Hang 'Em High", "Curdled", "Fist of Fury", "Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["The Guiding Light", "The Wendell Baker Story", "Paranoia", "Think Like A Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Enter the Dragon", "Broadway Danny Rose", "2 Guns", "Anchorman 2: The Legend Continues"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["The Waterboy", "Manhattan", "Orphan's Song", "Kambakth Ishq"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["It's Father's Fault", "RED 2", "The Running Man", "Pulp Fiction"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["A Madea Christmas", "Critters 3", "What Lies Beneath", "In the Face of Demolition"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Crank", "Stand by Me", "Circle of Iron", "First Blood"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["In Love and War", "Love", "Rob-B-Hood", "Rambo III"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["The Bodyguard", "Ponyo", "Walking Tall", "Too Late for Divorce"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["Behind the Candelabra", "The Fan", "Black", "Madea's Big Happy Family: The Play"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["A Nightmare on Elm Street", "Taking Chance", "Jhoom Barabar Jhoom", "Good Deeds"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["Temptation: Confessions of a Marriage Counselor", "She's So Lovely", "Wanderlust", "Taking Chance"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["We the Peeples", "Kannukkul Nilavu", "Daddy and Them", "Apocalypto"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["The Wise Little Hen", "The Terminator", "The Tourist", "Why Did I Get Married"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["Why Did I Get Married Too?", "Irokoishi", "Blended", "Assassins"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["The Goonies", "Longshot", "Batman Begins", "Madea's Big Happy Family"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["I Can Do Bad All by Myself", "Hum Aapke Hain Kaun...!", "The Tree of Life", "Sweet Time Together"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["Mumbai Diaries", "Cocaine Cowboys", "Tyler Perry's Madea's Family Reunion", "Pudhiya Geethai"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["Saugandh", "The Wise Little Hen", "The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers", "A Madea Christmas"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["Old School", "Independence Day", "Azhagai Irukkirai Bayamai Irukkirathu", "Tyler Perry's Laugh to Keep from Crying"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["Kuch Kuch Hota Hai", "Shadowmancer", "Sivakasi", "Madea's Class Reunion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["For Colored Girls", "Planet 51", "Donald in Mathmagic Land", "The Man with One Red Shoe"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["Mission: Impossible \u2013 Ghost Protocol", "Dumb and Dumber To", "Star Trek", "Kiss the Girls"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["Christmas in Connecticut", "Meet the Browns", "We Bought a Zoo", "Valley Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["The Family That Preys", "The Big Brawl", "Days of Thunder", "The Shining"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["The Legend of Conan", "Madea Goes to Jail", "The Toxic Boy", "Logan's Run"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["Wishful Thinking", "The Marriage Counselor", "Life Is Beautiful", "Something to Talk About"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["August Rush", "Alex Cross", "Blade Runner", "Paycheck"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["Death Race", "Aarakshan", "Single Moms Club", "Amistad"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["Kill Bill Volume 2", "Celebration of Gospel: Taking You Higher", "Live by Night", "Rose Red"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["Echelon", "The Sword in the Stone", "Moonrise Kingdom", "Diary of a Mad Black Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["Dilwale", "Cahill U.S. Marshal", "A Bronx Tale", "Daddy's Little Girls"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["My Dog Skip", "What's Done in the Dark", "Celeste and Jesse Forever", "Inception"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tyler Perry?", "answers": ["The Machine", "It", "Juvies", "Madea's Witness Protection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["The Mangler", "The Experts", "Flying Swords of Dragon Gate", "Righteous Kill"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Mujhse Shaadi Karogi", "Ghost Rider: Spirit of Vengeance", "Duplicity", "Romeo Must Die"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Mission: Impossible II", "WWE: King of the Ring 2002", "The Book of Eli", "Unleashed"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Alexander", "Mo' Better Blues", "The One", "Jaws"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Manglehorn", "Black Mask", "The Shining", "Finding Forrester"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Mary Reilly", "The Legend 2", "The Dilemma", "Thuppakki"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["The Ugly Truth", "Casa de Mi Padre", "American Sniper", "The Expendables 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["The Mummy - Tomb of the Dragon Emperor", "Dirty Harry", "1911", "Hannah Montana: The Movie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Linda Lovelace for President", "Gangster Squad", "Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade", "High Risk"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["The Sorcerer and the White Snake", "Rowan Atkinson Live!", "Mrs. Soffel", "The Lake House"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["The Other Guys", "Simon Birch", "Star Wars Episode VI: Return of the Jedi", "\"Dr. Wai in \"\"The Scripture with No Words\"\"\""], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Spy Kids 3-D: Game Over", "Donnie Brasco", "That Thing You Do!", "The Master"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Once Bitten", "Fist of Legend", "The Croods", "Mission: Impossible 5"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Everyone Says I Love You", "The Lost Symbol", "Once Upon a Time in China III", "Thick as Thieves"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Poove Unakkaga", "Swordsman II", "This Is the End", "Husbands and Wives"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Redemption", "My Least Favorite Career", "The Expendables", "The Last Boy Scout"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Rich and Strange", "Hero", "Patriot Games", "The Eagle"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Tai Chi Master", "Good Deeds", "Mohabbatein", "The Conversation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Seeking a Friend for the End of the World", "A Soldier's Story", "The Iceman Tapes: Conversations with a Killer", "Ocean Heaven"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Garv", "The Third Wheel", "Hitman", "Rambo: First Blood Part II"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Don Juan DeMarco", "Abbot Hai Teng of Shaolin", "The Experts", "The Whole Nine Yards"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Bobby Deerfield", "Stalk of the Celery Monster", "Kung Fu Cult Master", "Nanban"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Hoshi o Katta Hi", "The Running Man", "The Last Samurai", "Dragon Fight"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Fist of Fury", "War", "The Imaginarium of Dr. Parnassus", "Laughing Out Loud: America's Funniest Comedians"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["It's Father's Fault", "Spy Hunter", "Hatya: The Murder", "The Expendables 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Zila Ghaziabad", "Captain America: The Winter Soldier", "My Father is a Hero", "Cujo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["The Defender", "Coriolanus", "Scooby-Doo", "Deep Blue Sea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Club Paradise", "Little Big Soldier", "True Romance", "Cradle 2 the Grave"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Meet Joe Black", "Miss You Already", "Born to Defence", "Hercules: The Thracian Wars"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Happy Birthday", "Cobra", "The Sixth Sense", "Once Upon a Time in China II"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Strays", "Naye Nagme: Vol. 2", "The New Legend Of Shaolin", "Satyagraha"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["The Adventures of Tom Thumb and Thumbelina", "Baghban", "Shaolin Temple", "Thulladha Manamum Thullum"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["The Legend", "Force 10 from Navarone", "Singh Is Kinng", "Gia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["The Mission", "Scary Movie", "Wheels on Meals", "Kiss of the Dragon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["JFK", "The Forbidden Kingdom", "Jack & Jill", "Raja Hindustani"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["How the Grinch Stole Christmas!", "Everyone Says I Love You", "Serpico", "Once Upon a Time in China"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Dil To Pagal Hai", "The Proposal", "Planet of the Apes", "Badges of Fury"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Terminator 5", "The Trap", "Lethal Weapon 4", "Pale Rider"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Shaolin Temple 3: Martial Arts of Shaolin", "Antz", "The Number 23", "Step Up 2: The Streets"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Baazigar", "The Lone Ranger", "Once Upon a Time in China and America", "The Truman Show"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Ransom", "The Warlords", "Singh Is Kinng", "Starter for 10"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Fearless", "Riddick: Blindsided", "Seven", "Deconstructing Harry"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Return of the Killer Tomatoes", "Badlanders", "Last Hero in China", "The Incredible Burt Wonderstone"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Enemy of the State", "The Kid & I", "As Long as I Live", "The Founding of a Republic"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jet Li?", "answers": ["Carlito's Way", "Kids From Shaolin", "The Ladykillers", "Way of the Dragon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["We're the Millers", "Safe House", "Bachelor Party", "Don 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["The Green Mile", "Downhill", "The Manchurian Candidate", "Brannigan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Chal Mere Bhai", "Superstar", "The Preacher's Wife", "Jakob the Liar"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Lucky Numbers", "Blackmail", "We Are One: The Obama Inaugural Celebration at the Lincoln Memorial", "Sands of Iwo Jima"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Man on Fire", "Return to Horror High", "The Marriage Counselor", "You Don't Know Jack"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Fashionista's Fantasy", "Tightrope", "The Siege", "Fresh"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["The Company Men", "Michael", "Elizabethtown", "He Got Game"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["True Women", "Mo' Better Blues", "Apollo 13", "The Green Mile"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Little Miss Sunshine", "Kung Fu Panda: Secrets of the Masters", "Pirates of the Caribbean: At World's End", "The Mighty Quinn"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Before Night Falls", "Khiladiyon Ka Khiladi", "The Great Debaters", "Rounders"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["The Master", "Carbon Copy", "Wizards of Waverly Place: The Movie", "Anna Nicole Smith: Exposed"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Apollo at 70: A Hot Night in Harlem", "Happy Feet Two", "Speed 2: Cruise Control", "Shakti: The Power"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull", "Howl", "D\u00e9j\u00e0 Vu", "Bouncers"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Inside Man", "My Father is a Hero", "Empire State", "The Notebook"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Date Night", "Stalk of the Celery Monster", "Cobra", "The Taking of Pelham 123"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Flight", "Van Helsing", "The Legend of Drunken Master", "Two of a Kind"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Capone", "Soul Men", "Hollywood on Fire", "Mr. Dough and the Egg Princess"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["For Queen and Country", "Namak Halaal", "Good Will Hunting", "The Sex and Violence Family Hour"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["John Q", "Hum Aapke Hain Kaun...!", "Sleeping Beauty", "Fast Food"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["American Gangster", "Four Weddings and a Funeral", "The Informant!", "The Front"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Iron Man 2", "The Cold Light of Day", "Courage Under Fire", "Chasing Amy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Maniac", "Arthur 3: The War of the Two Worlds", "Malcolm X", "Shanghai Knights"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Hercules in New York", "Paycheck", "Avalon", "Antwone Fisher"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Fallen", "Temptation: Confessions of a Marriage Counselor", "Evolution", "Speed 2: Cruise Control"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["The Green Mile", "The Normal Heart", "Best of Raw: Vol. 1", "A Century of Black Cinema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["1941", "Flawless", "Bedtime Stories", "Flesh and Blood"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Shark Tale", "City Hall", "Isi Ka Naam Zindagi", "Remember the Titans"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Gallipoli", "Power", "Where Eagles Dare", "Deep Blue Sea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Chaahat", "Royal Rumble", "All the Right Moves", "Glory"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Bucky Larson: Born to Be a Star", "One Fine Day", "Raw Deal", "The Bone Collector"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["The General's Daughter", "Fast Food", "Under Capricorn", "The Pelican Brief"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Crimson Tide", "Meeting Evil", "Joseph: King of Dreams", "Don't Drink the Water"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["North", "Man of the Year", "Cry Freedom", "Kick-Ass 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Battle in Seattle", "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory", "The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King", "Training Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["The Skeleton Dance", "Kung Fu Panda 2", "Another Woman", "Ricochet"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["The Hurricane", "The Grifters", "The Work of Director Michel Gondry", "The Guiding Light"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Out of Time", "Play Misty for Me", "Ek Tha Tiger", "That Thing You Do!"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Rasigan", "Devil in a Blue Dress", "The Object of My Affection", "Titan A.E."], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Don 2", "Sleepers", "Wilma", "The Good Shepherd"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Saroja", "Invictus", "Too Young the Hero", "Mississippi Masala"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Ace Ventura: When Nature Calls", "Rounders", "Much Ado About Nothing", "Jurassic Park"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Doogal", "The Suburbans", "Ender's Game", "The Book of Eli"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Hum", "Diner", "The Phantom of the Opera", "Half Past Autumn"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["The Happening", "Presumed Innocent", "Virtuosity", "The People Speak"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Moneyball", "White Water Summer", "Bachelor Party", "License to Kill"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["The Lake House", "2 Guns", "Cowboys & Aliens", "Parampara"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Ricky Stanicky", "Coimbatore Mappillai", "Dalai Lama Renaissance", "The Equalizer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["The Gnome-Mobile", "Scooby-Doo", "Heart Condition", "Dark Shadows"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Mad City", "Try Seventeen", "A Soldier's Story", "London 2012 Olympic Opening Ceremony: Isles of Wonder"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Ils se mari\u00e8rent et eurent beaucoup d'enfants", "Philadelphia", "Green Zone", "Dying Young"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Denzel Washington?", "answers": ["Unstoppable", "Dragons Forever", "Shooters", "Too Late for Divorce"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Abraham Lincoln?", "answers": ["Lincoln's Gettysburg Address", "Shanghai Knights", "Apocalypse Now Redux", "It's Father's Fault"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Abraham Lincoln?", "answers": ["Full Frontal", "My Neighbor Totoro", "Atlanta Symphony Golden Anniversary", "Batman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Abraham Lincoln?", "answers": ["Tooth Fairy", "Kelly's Heroes", "A Tribute to John F. Kennedy from the Arts", "Half Baked"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Abraham Lincoln?", "answers": ["Stepmom", "The Perfect Tribute", "Peepli Live", "The Farmer's Wife"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Richard Kuklinski?", "answers": ["The World According to Garp", "Daddy and Them", "Rich and Strange", "The Iceman Tapes: Conversations with a Killer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Mystic Pizza", "The Robber Bride", "The American", "Spirit: Stallion of the Cimarron"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Oscar", "The Normal Heart", "Showtime", "Four Weddings and a Funeral"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Devil in a Blue Dress", "Steel Magnolias", "Copper Mountain", "Donald in Mathmagic Land"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["The Train Robbers", "Footloose", "Duplicity", "The Green Mile"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Flags of Our Fathers", "2 Guns", "Something to Talk About", "Hollywoodland"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Zoolander", "Fireflies in the Garden", "Exit Strategy", "Fire on the Amazon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["The Dead Pool", "Seven Pounds", "Ponyo", "Eat Pray Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["No Way Out", "Closer", "Analyze This", "Miss Congeniality"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["The Hurricane", "Zelig", "Sivakasi", "Confessions of a Dangerous Mind"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Deva", "Pretty Woman", "Beetlejuice", "Jeet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Side Effects", "Conan the Barbarian", "Pushing Tin", "Mona Lisa Smile"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["16 Blocks", "The Man with One Red Shoe", "Michael Collins", "Olympus Has Fallen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["The Mexican", "Bambi", "Raw Deal", "Naye Nagme: Vol. 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Ocean's Eleven", "Machine Gun Preacher", "Soul Men", "Somebody to Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Larry Crowne", "Gods of Egypt", "The Bumblebee Flies Anyway", "The Dark Knight"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Practical Magic", "Lucky Number Slevin", "Charlie Wilson's War", "The Libertine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Snakes on a Plane", "Stand Up Guys", "Chocolat", "Pr\u00eat-\u00e0-Porter"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Think Like A Man", "Full Frontal", "The Robot Boy", "Meet the Browns"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["The Thin Red Line", "Mary Reilly", "Knowing", "Looking for Richard"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Conspiracy Theory", "Itsy Bitsy Spider", "The Money Pit", "Rush Hour 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["August: Osage County", "The Chronicles of Riddick: Dark Fury", "Frankie and Johnny", "Cyborg 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Flatliners", "Maid's Room: Return of the Master", "Mike Hammer: Murder Takes All", "The Faculty"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Stepmom", "Chak De India", "Joe", "Jayne Mansfield's Car"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["In the Land of Blood and Honey", "The Face: Jesus in Art", "I Love Trouble", "Tum Mere Ho"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Temptation: Confessions of a Marriage Counselor", "Working Girl", "Chain Reaction", "Satisfaction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Everyone Says I Love You", "S.W.A.T.", "House of D", "Spy Hunter"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["My Best Friend's Wedding", "Force 10 from Navarone", "Super", "Unbroken"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["America's Sweethearts", "Radio Flyer", "The Weather Man", "Chaos"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Ferdinand the Bull", "The Lion King", "Notting Hill", "Andaz Naya Naya"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Find Me Guilty", "Tyler Perry's Madea's Family Reunion", "Ocean's Twelve", "Hoshi o Katta Hi"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["The Other Guys NYPD Recruitment Video", "Mirror Mirror", "Saboteur", "Frankenstein"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["The Singing Detective", "Dying Young", "Garv", "Domestic Disturbance"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["A Home of a Million Gold", "The Vanishing", "Blood Red", "The Longest Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Valentine's Day", "Adaptation", "Race to Witch Mountain", "Beavis and Butt-head Do America"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Sleeping with the Enemy", "Message in a Bottle", "Signs", "Scenes from Django Unchained - UK Winner"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Soul Men", "Erin Brockovich", "Merry Mirthquakes", "Northern Lights"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["A River Runs Through It", "Robin Williams: Weapons of Self-Destruction", "Hook", "Lethal Weapon"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Changing Lanes", "Runaway Bride", "Return of the Killer Tomatoes", "Happy New Year"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Khuda Gawah", "Perfect Stranger", "Hansel & Gretel: Witch Hunters", "The Pelican Brief"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Grand Champion", "Kaal", "Cop Out", "Jackie Brown"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Charlotte's Web", "Fast & Furious 7", "Insomnia", "Paradise"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Julia Roberts?", "answers": ["Antwone Fisher", "Our Father", "The Ant Bully", "Made in America"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Despicable Me 2", "The Mission", "Chori Chori Chupke Chupke", "Baazigar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["What's Eating Gilbert Grape", "The Chronicles of Riddick: Dark Fury", "Stand by Me", "Devdas"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Rocky Balboa", "Next", "Spring Breakers", "Chennai Express"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Khamoshi: The Musical", "Never Say Goodbye", "Mr. & Mrs. Smith", "A Century of Black Cinema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Chennai Kadhal", "Much Ado About Nothing", "From Hell", "Riddle"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Paul Blart: Mall Cop", "Sinbad: Legend of the Seven Seas", "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham", "Midnight in Paris"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Duplicate", "Cahill U.S. Marshal", "Walking Tall", "Lions for Lambs"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Pardes", "Heroes", "London 2012 Olympic Opening Ceremony: Isles of Wonder", "Trucks"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Cast Away", "The Shootist", "Darr", "4 the People"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind", "Stop-Loss", "Planet of the Apes", "Swades"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Kuch Kuch Hota Hai", "Trespasses", "Igor", "High School Musical 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Creepshow 2", "A Match Made by God", "Who Do I Gotta Kill?", "The Bounty"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["The Machine", "Sonic the Hedgehog", "Stainboy's Day Off", "Don: The Chase Begins Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Moonstruck", "Radio Flyer", "Aravaan", "Chaahat"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["The Scorpion King", "Argo", "Dil To Pagal Hai", "What's Done in the Dark"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Mandela: Long Walk to Freedom", "Baadshah", "The Chain Reaction", "The Iron Giant"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["As Long as I Live", "Der Fuehrer's Face", "Frankenweenie", "Mystic River"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["The Lost World: Jurassic Park", "My One and Only", "Hey Ram", "How the West Was Won"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Like Stars on Earth", "Solaris", "Knockaround Guys", "Karan Arjun"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Mohabbatein", "Lone Survivor", "Happy Feet", "The Dead Pool"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Catch .44", "Dickie Roberts: Former Child Star", "Don 2", "Heat"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Sleepover", "Madea's Big Happy Family: The Play", "I am Here", "Stage Fright"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["The Brothers Grimm", "Traveller", "She's the Man", "Heyy Babyy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Ra.One", "The Corruptor", "Without Evidence", "Ender's Game"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["The Good Son", "Celebrating AFI", "Toys", "Chalte Chalte"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Satisfaction", "Being Flynn", "Color of Night", "Deewana"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Annie Hall", "Saathiya", "The Skin Game", "Attack Force Z"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Blow Out", "The Founding of a Republic", "Arena", "Happy New Year"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["All the Right Moves", "Wild Wild West", "Yeh Lamhe Judaai Ke", "Batman vs. Superman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Untitled Miami Athletes Project", "Cloud Atlas", "The Ides of March", "Maya Memsaab"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Apollo at 70: A Hot Night in Harlem", "The Truman Show", "Chak De India", "Crank: High Voltage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Swiss Family Robinson", "Ponyo", "X-Men", "Student of the Year"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Celebrity News Reels: Hollywood's Most Infamous Couples and Ugliest Breakups", "Baabul", "Jack & Jill", "Kal Ho Naa Ho"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Dil Se", "Fist of Legend", "The Robot Boy", "The Quiet Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["S.W.A.T.", "Riding the Bullet", "Koyla", "The Lawnmower Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Black", "The New Shaolin Temple", "Found a Groom", "In the Name of the King: A Dungeon Siege Tale"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["The Lodger: A Story of the London Fog", "Goodfellas", "O.S.O.", "Champagne"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Hope Springs", "Billu Barber", "So Undercover", "The Last Samurai"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Spy Game", "Shahenshah", "Yes Boss", "Burn After Reading"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Nighthawks", "Shakti: The Power", "Unbroken", "Innerspace"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["McLintock!", "Hum Tumhare Hain Sanam", "A River Runs Through It", "Kill Bill Volume 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Ram Jaane", "The Mexican", "Donald in Mathmagic Land", "Pudhiya Geethai"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["XXX: State of the Union", "Troy", "Kaal", "Capone"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["The Shawshank Redemption", "Mohra", "The Manchurian Candidate", "My Name is Khan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Armour of God", "The Brave Heart Will Take the Bride", "Spy Kids 3-D: Game Over", "Creepshow 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Josh", "Pirates of the Caribbean: At World's End", "Rocky II", "Zelig"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Phir Bhi Dil Hai Hindustani", "Born on the Fourth of July", "Internal Affairs", "The Curious Case of Benjamin Button"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["Airheads", "Veer-Zaara", "Yuvan Yuvathi", "The Ant Bully"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["The Shawshank Redemption", "The Chronicles of Riddick", "Rocky IV", "Anjaam"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["The Incredibles", "I'm Still Here: Real Diaries of Young People Who Lived During the Holocaust", "Forty Deuce", "Chasing Mavericks"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Shahrukh Khan?", "answers": ["The Last Song", "Something Like a Business", "Kekk\u00f4 Kamen: Forever", "Ashoka the Great"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["4 the People", "Lord of War", "Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events", "Conan the Destroyer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Trespass", "Aravaan", "Flawless", "Every Time We Say Goodbye"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Mizugumo Monmon", "The King", "The Recruit", "The War"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["February 14", "Dreamcatcher", "We're the Millers", "Pom Poko"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Kiki's Delivery Service", "The Defender", "Yuvan Yuvathi", "Confessions of a Teenage Drama Queen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Hot Mess", "American Teacher", "Rambo", "Pattiyal"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Thiruthani", "Big Daddy", "Dil Kya Kare", "Good Time Gang"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Chennai Kadhal", "Sixteen Candles", "Drillbit Taylor", "The Night Listener"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Muniyandi Vilangial Moonramandu", "Illegal Aliens", "Jhoom Barabar Jhoom", "Raging Bull"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Solitary Man", "Veyyil", "A Madea Christmas", "Cold Dead Hand with Jim Carrey"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Kuruvi", "Seval", "Christine", "Confessions of a Dangerous Mind"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["The Italian Job", "Kanden Kadhalai", "Morning Glory", "The Pelican Brief"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Angels and Demons", "Sharaabi", "Arumugam", "Adalat"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Stardust Memories", "Thamizhan", "Enter the Dragon", "Kadhal FM"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Bodyguard", "Comic Relief 2007", "Thambikku Indha Ooru", "Annie Hall"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["The United States of Leland", "Jack", "Emmtan-Magan", "Jay and Silent Bob Strike Back"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Boys", "Suspect Zero", "Leprechaun", "Sainik"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Stone Cold Steve Austin: The Bottom Line on the Most Popular Superstar of All Time", "Pazhani", "Joe Kidd", "Ek Rishtaa: The Bond of Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Stop-Loss", "Supercross", "The Mummy Returns", "Sky"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Mystic Pizza", "City Hunter", "Azhagai Irukkirai Bayamai Irukkirathu", "Friends"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Nepali", "Die Hard", "Once Upon a Time in China III", "Nausica\u00e4 of the Valley of the Wind"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Grudge Match", "Amar Akbar Anthony", "Antz", "Chellamae"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["American Sniper", "Kicking & Screaming", "Rocky", "Koodal Nagar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bharath?", "answers": ["Ainthu Ainthu Ainthu", "Hope Springs", "Coming to America", "Sainik"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Stuff", "The Avengers: Age of Ultron", "Camp Cucamonga", "Humko Deewana Kar Gaye"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Before Night Falls", "Kachche Dhaage", "Arrietty", "Wishful Thinking"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["A Perfect World", "Megamind: The Button of Doom", "Toy Story", "A Nightmare on Elm Street"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Abraham Lincoln: Vampire Hunter", "Blow", "De Dana Dan", "Naalaiya Theerpu"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["The Fisher King", "Happy Feet Two", "Alice in Wonderland", "The 39 Steps"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Rajavin Parvaiyile", "Aadhi", "Cliffhanger", "Dead Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["The Ninth Gate", "Hope Springs", "The Patriot", "The Man Who Shot Liberty Valance"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Nothing Too Good for a Cowboy", "How to Fish", "Conan the Destroyer", "Edward Scissorhands"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["The Man Who Cried", "Circus World", "Naalaiya Theerpu", "Dil Hai Ke Manta Nahin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["From Paris with Love", "Transcendence", "The Son of No One", "Shaft"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["War of the Worlds", "Shanghai Knights", "Pirates of the Caribbean 5", "Soul Plane"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["From Hell", "Sivakasi", "Mona Lisa Smile", "Brazil"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Pilot Season", "Corpse Bride", "Patriot Games", "Heyy Babyy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Taarzan: The Wonder Car", "Chocolat", "Speed 2: Cruise Control", "Housefull 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Sleepy Hollow", "Meet Joe Black", "Crank", "Battlefield Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Pirates of the Caribbean: On Stranger Tides", "We Own the Night", "How to Train Your Dragon 3", "Don's Plum"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Nick of Time", "Madhurey", "Gia", "Cape Fear"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Laughing Out Loud: America's Funniest Comedians", "Bol Bachchan", "Platoon", "FernGully: The Last Rainforest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["The Imaginarium of Dr. Parnassus", "Love", "Fight Club", "Interview with the Vampire: The Vampire Chronicles"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Friday the 13th", "The Spirit", "Small Time Crooks", "Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Scent of a Woman", "Toy Story 3", "Once Upon a Time in Mexico", "The Fifth Element"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Deva", "Happy Birthday", "The Power of One", "Pirates of the Caribbean: At World's End"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Exit Strategy", "Private Resort", "Sangharsh", "Coogan's Bluff"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Boobie", "The Journey of Natty Gann", "A Civil Action", "The Tourist"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Ed Wood", "Super Rhino", "The Italian Job", "Itihaas"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Donnie Brasco", "Shadow of a Doubt", "Jupiter Ascending", "The Fugitive"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["G-Force", "Gundaraj", "Don Juan DeMarco", "The Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Charlie and the Chocolate Factory", "Deewana Mujh Sa Nahin", "All the Pretty Horses", "Iron Monkey"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["The Libertine", "Last Hero in China", "The Parent Trap", "Untitled The Departed 2 Sequel"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["How to Train Your Dragon 2", "New York Stories", "Rush Hour", "Freddy's Dead: The Final Nightmare"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["It Could Happen to You", "Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street", "Enter the Dragon", "Kachche Dhaage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["The Brave", "Munna Bhai Chale Amerika", "Pipe Dream", "Fantasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Amazing Love", "Boiler Room", "Rango", "Rio Grande"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Finding Neverland", "Enter the Dragon", "The Mountain Eagle", "Fist of Legend"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Kevin Hart: Laugh at My Pain", "Turbo", "Mumbai Diaries", "The Lone Ranger"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Anna Nicole Smith: Exposed", "Star Trek", "The Object of My Affection", "Hugo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Joe Versus the Volcano", "Into the Woods", "Mehbooba", "War"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Back to the Future Part II", "Slow Burn", "Children of the Corn IV: The Gathering", "The Best Thief in the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man's Chest", "Ronin", "Saudagar", "The Avengers"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["The Warlords", "Awwal Number", "The Preacher's Wife", "Ils se mari\u00e8rent et eurent beaucoup d'enfants"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Gossip with the Girls", "Batman Forever", "The Rum Diary", "Don: The Chase Begins Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["The Manchurian Candidate", "Force 10 from Navarone", "Arizona Dream", "Little Big Soldier"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Earth", "We're Back! A Dinosaur's Story", "What's Eating Gilbert Grape", "Confessions of a Teenage Drama Queen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["The Astronaut's Wife", "Convention", "Man on the Moon", "Wanted"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["End of the Harvest", "Satisfaction", "When You're Strange", "Flatliners"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Lakeview Terrace", "Casino Royale", "Where the Day Takes You", "Dark Shadows"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Cry-Baby", "No Place to Hide", "Sin City", "The Machine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Benny & Joon", "Good Time Gang", "R.I.P.D.", "What Dreams May Come"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Attila", "Secret Window", "Sivakasi", "Elf"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Public Enemies", "Lions for Lambs", "Horton Hears a Who!", "Dragon Fight"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Johnny Depp?", "answers": ["Fried Green Tomatoes", "Awakenings", "Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl", "Stay Hungry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Maybe Baby", "Ace Ventura: When Nature Calls", "So Undercover", "Tim Janis: Beautiful America"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Stuff", "Saboteur", "Short Fuse", "High School Musical 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Foxcatcher", "Single Moms Club", "The Last Song", "The Villain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["The Zero Theorem", "The Great Debaters", "Moonrise Kingdom", "Hannah Montana: The Movie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Rock Mafia Presents: The Big Bang", "Movie 43", "G.I. Joe: The Rise of Cobra", "In the Face of Demolition"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Sunny Leone Loves HD Porn", "The Girl Who Stares", "Sonic the Hedgehog", "Mrs. Soffel"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["The Bonfire of the Vanities", "Wanted", "35 and Ticking", "Super Rhino"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Mr. Wonderful", "Kelly's Heroes", "Hannah Montana & Miley Cyrus: Best of Both Worlds Concert", "End of the Line"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["The Lady Vanishes", "Sunny Leone Loves HD Porn", "LOL: Laughing Out Loud", "Horton Hears a Who!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Driving Miss Daisy", "Get Smart", "Across the Tracks", "Bolt"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Big Fish", "Daddy", "Mixed Nuts", "Commando"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Hanover Street", "The Shawshank Redemption", "Family Bond", "The Object of My Affection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Nothing in Common", "Pom Poko", "Van Helsing", "Dazed and Confused"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Tales from Earthsea", "The Thin Red Line", "The Fearless Hyena", "She Wore a Yellow Ribbon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["From up on Poppy Hill", "The Third Wheel", "Pyrates", "Meet the Parents"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["'Salem's Lot", "Lupin the 3rd: The Castle of Cagliostro: Special Edition", "Riddle", "Spanglish"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Looking for a Home", "That Thing You Do!", "Reach Me", "Mission: Impossible"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Thuppakki", "Seven Years in Tibet", "Mizugumo Monmon", "Ocean Heaven"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Castle in the Sky", "Shakti: The Power", "Hannah Montana & Miley Cyrus: Best of Both Worlds Concert", "Bangkok Dangerous"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Spirited Away", "Kambakth Ishq", "Presidential Reunion", "A Midsummer Night's Sex Comedy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Ronin", "Dazed and Confused", "The Place Beyond the Pines", "Princess Mononoke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Tezz", "Reservoir Dogs", "Independence Day", "Howl's Moving Castle"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Something to Talk About", "Whisper of the Heart", "Machete Kills", "Black"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["200 Cigarettes", "Mei and the Kittenbus", "The Rundown", "Zanjeer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Evolution", "The Truth About Charlie", "A Sumo Wrestler's Tail", "Corpse Bride"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Ponyo", "Shooters", "Demolition Man", "O.S.O."], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Casino Royale", "Gigli", "Nausica\u00e4 of the Valley of the Wind", "The Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["The Terminal", "Office Space", "Arrietty", "Tim"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["On Your Mark", "Steamboat Willie", "Clerks II", "World's Greatest Dad"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Sora Iro no Tane", "Hum Aapke Hain Kaun...!", "OMG \u2013 Oh My God!", "Linda Lovelace for President"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Changeling", "RocknRolla", "Bobby", "Porco Rosso"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Frankenweenie (1984)", "Alpha Dog", "Daddy", "My Neighbor Totoro"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Porco Rosso: The Last Sortie", "Armour of God II: Operation Condor", "Madhurey", "Presidential Reunion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Kaze Tachinu", "Bewitched", "Khiladi", "Infancy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["WWE Tagged Classics 2003: Royal Rumble", "The Story of Yanagawa's Canals", "The Imaginarium of Dr. Parnassus", "Jurassic Park"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["He's Just Not That Into You", "Out of the Furnace", "Hoshi o Katta Hi", "xXx"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["The Phantom of the Opera", "Hum Dil De Chuke Sanam", "The Vanishing", "Mr. Dough and the Egg Princess"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Running with Scissors", "The Wind Rises", "The Last Boy Scout", "Men Seeking Women"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Hitch", "Qayamat Se Qayamat Tak", "Azhagai Irukkirai Bayamai Irukkirathu", "Castle in the Sky: Bonus Material"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Robin Hood: Prince of Thieves", "Afsana Pyaar Ka", "K\u016bs\u014d no Sora Tobu Kikaitachi", "Inglourious Basterds"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Yaadon Ki Baaraat", "Kujiratori", "Confessions of a Teenage Drama Queen", "Madea's Witness Protection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Critters 3", "Con Air", "Sainik", "Kiki's Delivery Service"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Golmaal 3", "The Substitute", "The Castle of Cagliostro", "Raja Hindustani"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Hayao Miyazaki?", "answers": ["Koro no Daisanpo", "Crossing Over", "Frost on Satire", "Shark"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["Let Go", "The Tuxedo", "High Plains Drifter", "Family Bond"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["The Skin Game", "Bangkok Dangerous", "The Night Listener", "35 and Ticking"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["Happy New Year", "Torn Curtain", "The Protector", "Not Easily Broken"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["Arumugam", "Hotel Transylvania", "Think Like A Man", "Born to Defence"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["Joker", "Scary Movie", "Southland Tales", "Chennai Kadhal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["Soul Plane", "Pretty Woman", "Dick Tracy", "The Ant Bully"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["Hitman", "Every Which Way but Loose", "This Is the End", "So Dear to My Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["The Dark Knight Rises", "Drillbit Taylor", "Mazes and Monsters", "Seven"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["Vijaypath", "The Manchurian Candidate", "Grudge Match", "It Could Happen to You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["Husbands and Wives", "Green Zone", "Ride Along", "White House Down"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["Along Came Polly", "Night Skies", "Stalk of the Celery Monster", "Extract"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["Maximum Overdrive", "The 40-Year-Old Virgin", "Last Hero in China", "In the Bag"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["G-Force", "Kevin Hart: Laugh at My Pain", "A Jet-Setters Dream", "Taking Lives"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["The Train Robbers", "The Other Guys", "Poison Ivy", "Extreme Movie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["OMG \u2013 Oh My God!", "Nothing Too Good for a Cowboy", "Kevin Hart: Let Me Explain", "A Perfect World"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["Kevin Hart: I'm a Grown Little Man", "Der Fuehrer's Face", "ReGeneration", "Champagne"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["Magnolia", "8", "T2 3-D:Battle Across Time", "Something Like a Business"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["Raising Arizona", "Robin Williams: Weapons of Self-Destruction", "Scary Movie 4", "Sky Captain and the World of Tomorrow"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["Playing for Keeps", "The Mission", "Bandits", "The Precious One"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["Left Behind", "Omkara", "The Harvest", "Little Fockers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["A Christmas Carol", "Exit Strategy", "The Net", "Shout"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["The Legend of Conan", "The Weekend", "Pink Cadillac", "Saawariya"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["Fool's Gold", "The Avengers: Age of Ultron", "Foreign Correspondent", "Unbecoming Age"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Hart?", "answers": ["Kiss of the Dragon", "Chaahat", "The Five-Year Engagement", "Clerks II"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Transporter 2", "Sand and Sorrow", "No Place to Hide", "The Protector"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Safe", "Pocahontas", "Convention", "Frenzy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Gnomeo & Juliet", "Red River", "1408", "Safe House"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Reach Me", "Butterfly on a Wheel", "Homefront", "America's Sweethearts"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Mary Poppins", "Manhattan", "The Godfather Part III", "The Brazilian Job"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Gardener of Eden", "The Favor", "ATL", "Chaos"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Toofan", "War", "Deep Blue Sea", "Baaghi: A Rebel for Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["The Wendell Baker Story", "Madea's Witness Protection", "Mean Machine", "Cujo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["American Hustle", "Dick", "Hercules: The Thracian Wars", "Blitz"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["The Karate Kid 2", "Death Race 2000", "Man on the Moon", "Collateral"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Signs of Life", "Veyyil", "Drive Angry", "The Expendables 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["WWE: King of the Ring 2000", "Happy Birthday", "Redemption", "Phir Bhi Dil Hai Hindustani"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Zila Ghaziabad", "The Appointment", "Liar Liar", "Heat"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Daddy", "Hum Dil De Chuke Sanam", "The Fifth Element", "Death Race"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Keeping Mum", "200 Cigarettes", "Echelon", "Glory"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["No Entry", "Kadhal FM", "Turn It Up", "My Best Friend's Wedding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Family Plot", "Cellular", "Blood Alley", "Disney's The Kid"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Kelly's Heroes", "The One", "The Bowling Ball", "The Pawnbroker"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["In the Name of the King: A Dungeon Siege Tale", "End of the Harvest", "Toy Story", "Transcendence"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Mandela: Long Walk to Freedom", "The Transporter", "The Ice Storm", "Diner"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["The Last Witch Hunter", "Crank: High Voltage", "The Avengers: Age of Ultron", "Phil Spector"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Ghosts of Mars", "The Private Lives of Pippa Lee", "Jersey Girl", "The Score"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Ultimate Fights", "Armageddon", "The Benchwarmers", "The Terminator"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Golmaal 3", "Batman Begins", "The Master", "Snatch"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Suhaag", "Love Part 2", "Saroja", "Killer Elite"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["The Expendables 3", "The Trouble with Harry", "The Spiderwick Chronicles", "The 'Burbs"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Sin City", "Saving Mr. Banks", "The Mechanic", "WWE Tagged Classics 2003: Royal Rumble"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Ram Jaane", "Crank", "Circle of Iron", "Being Human"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Merry Mirthquakes", "The Thin Red Line", "The Expendables", "Sonic the Hedgehog"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Coming to America", "State of Play", "The Basketball Diaries", "The Bank Job"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Fast & Furious 7", "Seven", "The Blind Side", "Legend of the Boneknapper Dragon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Temptation: Confessions of a Marriage Counselor", "Parker", "Gods of Egypt", "Laughing Out Loud: America's Funniest Comedians"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["The Italian Job", "The Great Debaters", "The Ladykillers", "Brock Lesnar: Here Comes the Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["The Wolf of Wall Street", "Spy Hunter", "Transporter 3", "Ace Ventura: When Nature Calls"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["13", "Golmaal 3", "When the Party's Over", "Agneepath"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Life of Crime", "London", "Minority Report: Bonus Material", "Antwone Fisher"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jason Statham?", "answers": ["Lonely Hearts", "The Big Trail", "Gangaajal", "Revolver"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Dracula 2000", "The Dilemma", "The Warlords", "Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Spirited Away", "Single Moms Club", "Step Up", "Air America"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["For Queen and Country", "The Secret Life of Bees", "10 Years", "Stepmom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Amistad", "X-Men: First Class", "So Dear to My Heart", "War of the Worlds"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Dear John", "End of the Harvest", "XXX: The Return of Xander Cage", "The War Wagon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["All in the Family", "White House Down", "Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull", "Rich and Strange"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Golmaal Returns", "Wanderlust", "Zelig", "The Trap"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Hero", "Money for Nothing", "Peter Pan", "Stop-Loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Parker", "Blitz", "The Vow", "For Colored Girls"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Ninaithen Vandhai", "Smokin' Aces", "Mary Reilly", "Jupiter Ascending"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Haywire", "Grand Canyon", "Oblivion", "Harrison's Flowers"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Since You've Been Gone", "Side Effects", "The Searchers", "Wizards of Waverly Place: The Movie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Don Jon", "The Front", "Platoon", "Dragons Forever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Madea's Big Happy Family", "Raging Bull", "Every Which Way but Loose", "G.I. Joe: The Rise of Cobra"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Wanted", "In Harm's Way", "The Secret Policeman's Other Ball", "The Lego Movie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Bol Bachchan", "The Man Who Cried", "D\u00e9j\u00e0 Vu", "Foxcatcher"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["The Weather Man", "Assassins", "I Can Do Bad All by Myself", "The Contortionist's Handbook"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Hello Brother", "Duplicate", "Seeking Justice", "Supercross"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Joe Versus the Volcano", "Hannah and Her Sisters", "Kiss of the Dragon", "Coach Carter"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["xXx", "Baghban", "The 6th Day", "Magic Mike 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Bad Boys", "Peter Pan", "She's the Man", "A Love Song for Bobby Long"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Namastey London", "Captain America: The Winter Soldier", "28 Days", "A Guide to Recognizing Your Saints"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["The Secret Policeman's Other Ball", "Rock of Ages", "Frenzy", "Magic Mike"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["The Switch", "Fighting", "Goodbye Lover", "Ronin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Looking for a Home", "This Is the End", "Orphan", "The Bucket List"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Maximum Overdrive", "The Eagle", "Minority Report: Bonus Material", "Namastey London"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Rio Lobo", "Sarkar", "Our Father", "The Son of No One"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["The Virginity Hit", "Bouncers", "One Hundred and One Nights", "Battle in Seattle"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Suhaag", "Shakti: The Power", "Morgan and Destiny's Eleventeenth Date: The Zeppelin Zoo", "Miss Congeniality"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Havoc", "Captain America: The Winter Soldier", "The Ugly Truth", "No Way Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Shout", "Doing Time on Maple Drive", "Ion", "Blackmail"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["The Perfect Tribute", "21 Jump Street", "Desperado", "Porco Rosso"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["The Rundown", "Kannukkul Nilavu", "Rhinestone", "Poor Things"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Public Enemies", "Dragon Fight", "Inside Man", "Bhoothnath"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["The Polar Express", "Look Who's Talking Too", "22 Jump Street", "Welcome to Collinwood"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Parkland", "Angela & Viril", "New Police Story", "G.I. Joe: Retaliation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Channing Tatum?", "answers": ["Apocalypto", "Lions for Lambs", "Step Up 2: The Streets", "Tyler Perry's Madea's Family Reunion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Eraser", "Der Fuehrer's Face", "She Wore a Yellow Ribbon", "Vampire's Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Avenging Angelo", "Kuruvi", "Happy Feet Two", "Red Heat"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Killer at Large: Why Obesity is America's Greatest Threat", "Extraordinary Measures", "Cleaner", "I Love Trouble"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Vettaikkaaran", "The Kid & I", "Sin City", "Vampire's Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Toy Story 2", "Small Time Crooks", "Total Recall", "The Assassination of Jesse James by the Coward Robert Ford"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Wilde Salome", "Ils se mari\u00e8rent et eurent beaucoup d'enfants", "The Vow", "Sabotage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Afsana Pyaar Ka", "The Dark Knight", "Happy Anniversary and Goodbye", "Wilma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Heart Stopper", "Empire State", "Talladega Nights: The Ballad of Ricky Bobby", "Terminator 2: Judgment Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Too Young to Die?", "Eight Crazy Nights", "An Orphan's Tragedy", "Escape Plan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Hercules in New York", "Suburbicon", "The Night Listener", "Paul"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Downhill", "The Last Witch Hunter", "Conan the Barbarian", "Aladdin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Christmas in Connecticut", "Har Dil Jo Pyar Karega", "Suits", "Kujiratori"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Under Suspicion", "Suspect Zero", "Ted", "The 6th Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Commando", "The 40-Year-Old Virgin", "The Corruptor", "Daylight"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Signs", "Ion", "Kiki's Delivery Service", "The Legend of Conan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Last Action Hero", "Unbreakable", "Super Rhino", "Strangers on a Train"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Boris and Natasha: The Movie", "Cry Macho", "Edge of Tomorrow", "Jaan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Predator", "Apocalypto", "The Lion King", "The Appointments of Dennis Jennings"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Ishq", "Unknown Soldier", "The Brothers Grimm", "The Mission"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Maggie", "Left Behind", "Nerrukku Ner", "Turn It Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Pattiyal", "The Villain", "Blood Work", "No Place to Hide"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Terminator 5", "Tim and Eric's Billion Dollar Movie", "Surviving Christmas", "The Comancheros"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["The Marriage Counselor", "The Contortionist's Handbook", "The Last Stand", "Mangal Pandey: The Rising"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["The Truth About Charlie", "T2 3-D:Battle Across Time", "Braveheart", "Mighty Aphrodite"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Stage Fright", "Red Sonja", "Shadowmancer", "The Good German"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["The Man Who Shot Liberty Valance", "Hanover Street", "Orphan", "Kindergarten Cop"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Captive", "Lakeview Terrace", "Tumko Na Bhool Payenge", "Sleepwalkers"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Nine Months", "Casper", "Batman & Robin", "Nighthawks"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Boobie", "The Fever", "Scavenger Hunt", "In the Bag"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Kadhalukku Mariyadhai", "The Terminator", "Bon Voyage", "Stolen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Collateral Damage", "Hitch", "Action Replayy", "Bouncers"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Beowulf", "The Expendables 3", "Joe", "Khushi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Star Wars Episode V: The Empire Strikes Back", "Junior", "Staying Alive", "Perfect"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Look Who's Talking", "Heroes", "After Earth", "Stay Hungry"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Gangaajal", "In Love and War", "High School Musical 2", "The Expendables 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Lincoln's Gettysburg Address", "Besharam", "The I Love Lucy 50th Anniversary Special", "Leatherheads"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Copper Mountain", "Spy Game", "The 'Burbs", "Raw Deal"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Kick-Ass", "End of Days", "Unthinkable", "Vincent"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Terminator 3: Rise of the Machines", "Raja Hindustani", "Don Jon", "Machete Kills"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["The Running Man", "Edge of Darkness", "Khiladi", "Lifeboat"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Around the World in 80 Days", "A Love Song for Bobby Long", "The Zero Theorem", "Northern Lights"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Once Upon a Time in China II", "Jingle All the Way", "Wild Hogs", "The Longest Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Twins", "Talaash: The Hunt Begins...", "Menace II Society", "From up on Poppy Hill"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Jurassic Park", "The Jayne Mansfield Story", "Changing Lanes", "Natural Born Killers"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Shootout at Wadala", "Bringing Out the Dead", "Snitch", "Beretta's Island"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Triplets", "Miss Congeniality 2: Armed and Fabulous", "Tears of the Sun", "Antwone Fisher"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Hum Aapke Hain Kaun...!", "Mr. Wonderful", "A River Runs Through It", "Conan the Destroyer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "answers": ["Donnie Brasco", "Kalifornia", "True Lies", "The Eagle"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nelson Mandela?", "answers": ["Mandela: Long Walk to Freedom", "Die Hard", "Rascals", "Once More"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["One Fine Day", "Renaissance Man", "8mm", "Judwaa"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Flipper", "Tere Naam", "Austin Powers: International Man of Mystery", "Saving Private Ryan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Baaghi: A Rebel for Love", "Total Recall", "Love Actually", "Beretta's Island"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Chori Chori Chupke Chupke", "The Taking of Pelham 123", "Everything Is Illuminated", "After Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["The Panic in Needle Park", "The Survivors", "Revenge for Jolly!", "Lucky: No Time for Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["The Longest Yard", "Tumko Na Bhool Payenge", "Shooter", "Kaal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Salaam-e-Ishq: A Tribute to Love", "August Rush", "Back to the Future Part II", "Island in the Sky"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Reindeer Games", "Aladdin", "Partner", "James Michener's Dynasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Marigold", "Circle of Iron", "The Quick and the Dead", "Rumble Fish"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Predator", "World War Z", "Bodyguard", "Kabhi Kabhie"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Satisfaction", "Phantoms", "Money for Nothing", "Yuvvraaj"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Jaanemann", "Signs", "Fast Five", "Fort Apache"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Har Dil Jo Pyar Karega", "Seven", "Tears of the Sun", "Children of the Corn: The Final Sacrifice"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Kekk\u00f4 Kamen: Forever", "Paradise", "Nim's Island", "Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Where Eagles Dare", "Bandhan", "The Terminal", "Notorious"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Ek Tha Tiger", "The Patriot", "Royal Rumble", "Criminal Law"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Hum Aapke Hain Kaun...!", "Frankenstein", "The Dark Half", "Hansel & Gretel: Witch Hunters"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["The Dark Side of the Sun", "Kuch Kuch Hota Hai", "Sin City", "American Breakdown"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["16 Blocks", "Kurbaan", "One Fine Day", "Ladder 49"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Biwi Ho To Aisi", "Ram Jaane", "Hannah Montana & Miley Cyrus: Best of Both Worlds Concert", "National Treasure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Sholay", "Flesh and Blood", "Chal Mere Bhai", "Dear John"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Talaash: The Hunt Begins...", "Longtime Companion", "The Hobbit: There and Back Again", "Baabul"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Lambert the Sheepish Lion", "Morgan and Destiny's Eleventeenth Date: The Zeppelin Zoo", "Maine Pyaar Kyun Kiya?", "Braveheart: Bonus Material"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Radio Flyer", "Fast & Furious 6", "Khamoshi: The Musical", "Trucks"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Karan Arjun", "Hatari!", "Sinatra", "Bollywood Dreams"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Turner & Hooch", "Morning Glory", "Main Aur Mrs Khanna", "The Eiger Sanction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Biwi No.1", "Azhagiya Tamil Magan", "John Q", "Cupid & Cate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Saawan... The Love Season", "Winnie the Pooh and the Blustery Day", "Gallipoli", "Ocean Heaven"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Domestic Disturbance", "Tim and Eric's Billion Dollar Movie", "Mrs. Doubtfire", "Andaz Apna Apna"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["The Green Berets", "Fast & Furious 7", "Abhimaan", "Hum Saath-Saath Hain: We Stand United"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["In the Face of Demolition", "Rooster Cogburn", "Ainthu Ainthu Ainthu", "Saajan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Rang De Basanti", "The Green Berets", "Dulhan Hum Le Jayenge", "Good Will Hunting"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["The One", "Dil To Pagal Hai", "Yeh Hai Jalwa", "Mystic Pizza"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Corpse Bride", "Catch .44", "Tears of the Sun", "Saawariya"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Arthur 3: The War of the Two Worlds", "Saugandh", "George Wallace", "Garv"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Kyon Ki", "Say Anything...", "The Rum Diary", "Dead Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Alice & Viril", "Son of Sardaar", "Lethal Weapon 3", "K-19: The Widowmaker"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Ted", "Maine Pyar Kiya", "Best of Raw: Vol. 1", "Ender's Game"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["The Fifth Element", "London Dreams", "WWE: WrestleMania 27: Vol. 2", "Apocalypse Now Redux"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Practical Magic", "Mujhse Shaadi Karogi", "Spy Kids", "Big"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Pyaar Kiya To Darna Kya", "The Substitute", "The Substitute", "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Unity", "Ready", "Men in Black: Alien Attack", "Margaret"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["We're the Millers", "Club Paradise", "No Entry", "Return of the Killer Tomatoes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Why Did I Get Married", "Hope Floats", "Just Go With It", "Veer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Peekay", "Dabangg", "In the Face of Demolition", "Space Cowboys"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Dabangg 2", "Legalese", "My Least Favorite Career", "The Secrets of Jonathan Sperry"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Diljale", "Confessions of a Teenage Drama Queen", "Dus", "That's My Boy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Jeet", "Any Which Way You Can", "Dragon Fight", "The Office Party"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Family Bond", "The Weather Man", "Zookeeper", "Hum Dil De Chuke Sanam"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["Lincoln's Gettysburg Address", "Top Gun 2", "Being Flynn", "Wanted"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Salman Khan?", "answers": ["The Greatest Story Ever Told", "Outbreak", "Hello Brother", "Lock Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["When Corruption Was King", "Apocalypse Now", "Cruising", "Murder!"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Independence Day", "Chasing Amy", "Rock Star", "Jurassic Park"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["We Are One: The Obama Inaugural Celebration at the Lincoln Memorial", "Outbreak", "Broken City", "Three O'Clock High"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["The Perfect Storm", "The Paradine Case", "Race to Witch Mountain", "Pet Sematary"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["One Fine Day", "Andaz Naya Naya", "Spy Hunter", "Invincible"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Dil To Pagal Hai", "Yaarana", "Driving Miss Daisy", "Fear"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Bandits", "Ek Hi Raasta", "Four Brothers", "The Scorpion King"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["The Slaughter Rule", "Celebrity", "Good Time Gang", "Snake in the Eagle's Shadow"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Sky", "Scenes from Django Unchained - UK Winner", "Date Night", "Annie Hall"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["The Lodger: A Story of the London Fog", "The Color of Money", "He's Just Not That Into You", "Boogie Nights"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["The Horse Soldiers", "The Other Guys", "Harrison's Flowers", "Lookin' to Get Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Three Kings", "Cars", "Priya: The Charming Girl of India", "Actress"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Live by Night", "Shaft", "Lone Survivor", "Kadhalukku Mariyadhai"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Star Wars Holiday Special", "The Happening", "The Prince of Egypt", "August Rush"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Foxfire", "Peepli Live", "The Italian Job", "Zanjeer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["2 Guns", "True Crime", "Terminator 5", "Raw Deal"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["The Terminator", "Die Hard", "To the Limit", "I Heart Huckabees"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Wild Wild West", "Shooter", "Hancock", "Wishful Thinking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["The Yards", "1941", "Once More", "Qayamat Se Qayamat Tak"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["August: Osage County", "Hannah and Her Sisters", "We Own the Night", "Hancock 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Untitled The Departed 2 Sequel", "The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey", "Eliza Graves", "The King of Comedy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Frantic", "Who Shot Patakango?", "The Corruptor", "Hello Brother"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Too Late for Divorce", "The Basketball Diaries", "Scooby-Doo", "The Karate Kid 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Rain Man", "To the Limit", "The Beguiled", "Renaissance Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Love Is All There Is", "Anchorman: The Legend of Ron Burgundy", "Rumble in the Bronx", "Transformers: Age of Extinction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Not Easily Broken", "The Departed", "Something Like a Business", "Hellfighters"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Ninaithen Vandhai", "Pari", "The Horse Soldiers", "The Fighter"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Contraband", "Rang De Basanti", "We the Peeples", "1408"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["The Substitute", "Paradise", "Batman", "The Big Trail"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Pain & Gain", "Firewall", "Miracles", "Avalon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["The Men Who Stare at Goats", "Jayne Mansfield's Car", "Three Mississippi", "Nim's Island"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Juvies", "RocknRolla", "Diner", "Rio Lobo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Tim Janis: Beautiful America", "Starter for 10", "Copper Mountain", "Planet of the Apes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Welcome to Collinwood", "The Man", "Ted", "Rambo III"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["The Switch", "WWE: King of the Ring 2002", "Mohabbatein", "Cocaine Cowboys"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Rang De Basanti", "The Producers", "Bulletproof", "Traveller"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Max Payne", "Nick of Time", "Chasing Mavericks", "Die Hard 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Tears of the Sun", "The Big Hit", "Paparazzi", "Los Bandoleros"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["The Great Buck Howard", "The Brazilian Job", "Funny People", "Romance & Cigarettes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Be Cool", "The Truth About Charlie", "Mann", "Kevin Hart: Laugh at My Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Soul Men", "Charlotte's Web", "The Lovely Bones", "Winter's Tale"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mark Wahlberg?", "answers": ["Kung Fu Panda", "Entourage", "Chori Chori Chupke Chupke", "Risky Business"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["The Big White", "Namastey London", "Rocky II", "Lay the Favorite"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["The Slaughter Rule", "Paint Your Wagon", "Die Hard", "Karan Arjun"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Two of a Kind", "Say Anything...", "The New Shaolin Temple", "G.I. Joe: Retaliation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Planet Terror", "Khamoshi: The Musical", "Mr. Bean's Holiday", "Taarzan: The Wonder Car"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Bodyguard", "Laffapalooza! #1", "Alpha Dog", "Gigli"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Bachelorette", "Sudden Impact", "Scary Movie", "Perfect Stranger"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["The Frozen Ground", "Color of Night", "The Godfather Saga", "Punch-Drunk Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Carriage Ghost", "Sabrina", "Last Man Standing", "The 6th Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Death Becomes Her", "One More Kiss", "Solitary Man", "Tremors"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["The Big Picture", "Bachelor Party", "RED 2", "1911"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Cop Out", "The Pacifier", "Glory Daze", "London Dreams"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Striking Distance", "Pushing Tin", "Babylon A.D.", "Conan the Barbarian"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["The Expendables 2", "Christine", "Porco Rosso", "Signs"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["The Fifth Element", "Revolution", "Class", "Mission: Impossible"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Champagne", "She's the Man", "Corpse Bride", "Live Free or Die Hard"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Mangal Pandey: The Rising", "The American", "Welcome to Collinwood", "The Whole Nine Yards"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["A Good Day to Die Hard", "Sainik", "The Dilemma", "Born on the Fourth of July"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Hell's Kitchen", "Lucky Number Slevin", "Kekk\u00f4 Kamen: Forever", "Dolphin Tale"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Ra.One", "Cellular", "Over the Hedge", "Abraham Lincoln: Vampire Hunter"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Hoshi o Katta Hi", "She Wore a Yellow Ribbon", "Die Hard with a Vengeance", "My Dog Skip"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Cat's Eye", "The Jackal", "Mystic Pizza", "The Skin Game"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Escape to Victory", "Surrogates", "Finding Neverland", "Being Human"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["The Samaritan", "Get Smart", "The Siege", "Commando"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Ra.One", "Unbreakable", "The Young Master", "Full Frontal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["3 Idiots", "The Last Boy Scout", "Shooters", "Casa de Mi Padre"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Sin City: A Dame to Kill For", "The Thing Called Love", "Punch-Drunk Love", "Boys"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Moonrise Kingdom", "Outbreak", "Shakespeare in Love", "Men in Black: Alien Attack"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Pink Cadillac", "Tears of the Sun", "Marnie", "Love and Death"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Half Nelson", "Die Hard 2", "OMG \u2013 Oh My God!", "Total Recall"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["The Appointment", "Mona Lisa Smile", "Fire with Fire", "Transformers: Age of Extinction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["16 Blocks", "Club Paradise", "Sabrina", "A Time for Killing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["A Jet-Setters Dream", "Sin City", "Burn After Reading", "Big"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Bandits", "The Spiderwick Chronicles", "Mystic River", "Rosewater"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Priyamudan", "Blind Date", "Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom", "Destiny Turns on the Radio"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["The Horse Soldiers", "JFK", "The Sixth Sense", "The Jungle Book"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["New York Stories", "Hudson Hawk", "Sleeper", "Deewana Mujh Sa Nahin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["The Last Song", "Hostage", "The Peacemaker", "Boss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["RED", "Alice & Viril", "The Five-Year Engagement", "Rumble Fish"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Look Who's Talking", "Pari", "Glory Daze", "Mike Hammer: Murder Takes All"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Playing for Keeps", "Hansel and Gretel", "Kill Bill Volume 1", "Mercury Rising"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Suhaag", "Unity", "X-Men", "The Story of Us"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Last Vegas", "Gundaraj", "Rocky III", "Looper"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["One Eight Seven", "Armageddon", "Without Limits", "Avenging Angelo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Disney's The Kid", "Bollywood Dreams", "No Way Out", "As Long as I Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Oliver Twist", "Transformers: Age of Extinction", "The Magic of Belle Isle", "Setup"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Stephen King's Desperation", "Catch .44", "Aakrosh", "Creepshow 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["12 Monkeys", "The Fearless Hyena", "The Sorcerer's Apprentice", "We're the Millers"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Saturday Night Fever", "Pulp Fiction", "Der Fuehrer's Face", "Cinderella"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Fast & Furious", "Reservoir Dogs", "Kyon Ki", "Beavis and Butt-head Do America"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Thulladha Manamum Thullum", "The Chain Reaction", "K-19: The Widowmaker", "Hart's War"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Bruce Willis?", "answers": ["Judge Dredd", "Rich and Strange", "The Cold Light of Day", "Jodhaa Akbar"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rich Christiano?", "answers": ["End of the Harvest", "Hudson Hawk", "Finders Keepers", "Perfect Stranger"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rich Christiano?", "answers": ["Notting Hill", "The Dark Knight Rises", "Naam", "Unidentified"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rich Christiano?", "answers": ["Amazing Love", "8", "Dead Man", "The Book of Eli"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rich Christiano?", "answers": ["Joseph: King of Dreams", "The Appointment", "Extreme Movie", "Dolan's Cadillac"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rich Christiano?", "answers": ["Super", "The Vow", "Time Changer", "Aitraaz"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rich Christiano?", "answers": ["The Secrets of Jonathan Sperry", "Jerry Maguire", "S.W.A.T.", "Pulp Fiction"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Rich Christiano?", "answers": ["Second Glance", "Dan in Real Life", "Find Me Guilty", "Kevin Hart: Laugh at My Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["The Purple Rose of Cairo", "Starter for 10", "You Don't Know Jack", "Gods of Egypt"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["What's Eating Gilbert Grape", "City of Ember", "Khamoshi: The Musical", "Fast Times at Ridgemont High"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["The Paradine Case", "Junior", "Catch Me If You Can", "Simon Birch"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Men in Black", "Too Late for Divorce", "Saving Private Ryan", "Nishabd"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers", "Memoirs of a Geisha", "Dragnet", "Coriolanus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Edison", "The Tommyknockers", "Bachelor Party", "The Running Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["The Good Life", "No Way Out", "Money for Nothing", "My Big Fat Greek Wedding"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Something to Talk About", "The King", "The Money Pit", "The Mangler"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Never Say Never Again", "Once Upon a Time in America", "Cars", "First Blood"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["The Spy Next Door", "The Family That Preys", "License to Wed", "The Green Mile"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Sooryavansham", "Lethal Weapon 3", "Squirrels to the Nuts", "Cast Away"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Satisfaction", "Toy Story", "Untitled Terrence Malick project", "Step Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["The Prince of Egypt", "Sleepless in Seattle", "Winnie the Pooh and the Blustery Day", "The Best Thief in the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Hercules: The Thracian Wars", "Wrestling Ernest Hemingway", "The Ladykillers", "Ali"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Time Share", "Doctor Who and the Curse of Fatal Death", "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind", "Punchline"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Forrest Gump", "Dumbo", "Deewane", "Leprechaun"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Return to Horror High", "Chasing Mavericks", "Moonrise Kingdom", "The Bonfire of the Vanities"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Charlie Wilson's War", "The Ides of March", "Emmtan-Magan", "Diary of a Mad Black Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Twin Dragons", "Murder!", "Frenzy", "Radio Flyer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Critters 3", "Junior", "The Polar Express", "Steamboat Willie"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["The Warlords", "Two of a Kind", "The Lost Symbol", "Surrogates"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Angels and Demons", "No Way Out", "No Entry", "Project A"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Parkland", "Inglourious Basterds", "Air Force One", "Awwal Number"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["National Geographic: Beyond the Movie: Pearl Harbor", "Hollywoodland", "Where the Wild Things Are", "National Lampoon's Animal House"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Toy Story 2", "Batman Begins", "Sweet and Lowdown", "Udhaya"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["The 'Burbs", "Youth", "Last Vegas", "Michael Clayton"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Glory", "La escribana de uraba", "The Horse Soldiers", "Mazes and Monsters"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Kevin Hart: Let Me Explain", "The Proposal", "Splash", "The Outlaw Josey Wales"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Small Time Crooks", "Trouble with the Curve", "The Man with One Red Shoe", "Combat Academy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Hugo", "Thuppakki", "Band of Brothers", "Badlanders"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Toy Story 3", "Man of the Year", "The Lawnmower Man", "Rumble Fish"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Philadelphia", "In the Line of Fire", "The Five Senses", "The Naked Gun 33\u2153: The Final Insult"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Cloud Atlas", "Fire on the Amazon", "The Proposal", "The Grifters"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Collateral", "Kevin Hart: I'm a Grown Little Man", "Raajneeti", "The Terminal"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Big", "Something Evil", "Planet Terror", "Twin Dragons"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Love Is All There Is", "The Country Bears", "Aatank Hi Aatank", "Larry Crowne"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Nothing in Common", "Face/Off", "Lord of War", "Evolution"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Captain Phillips", "Knowing", "Family Plot", "Rain Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["The Great Buck Howard", "Something to Talk About", "Hitman", "Sinatra"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Celeste and Jesse Forever", "All the Best: Fun Begins", "A League of Their Own", "Surrogates"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Kuruvi", "Any Which Way You Can", "Wilma", "The Da Vinci Code"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["The Founding of a Republic", "Hatari!", "You've Got Mail", "Curdled"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Saving Mr. Banks", "Stephen King's Desperation", "Three Kings", "Torn Curtain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Dirty Harry", "Taxi Driver", "Every Time We Say Goodbye", "Igor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Birdy", "Itihaas", "That Thing You Do!", "Shakes the Clown"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Across the Tracks", "Mad Max", "The Accidental Spy", "Turner & Hooch"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Sesame Street: Singing with the Stars", "Road to Perdition", "The Match Girl", "88 Minutes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Volunteers", "Legends of the Fall", "Lay the Favorite", "Copper Mountain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Simon Birch", "Daddy's Little Girls", "Joe Versus the Volcano", "The Big Hit"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["Amazing Love", "The Face: Jesus in Art", "Kal Ho Naa Ho", "Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Hanks?", "answers": ["The Purple Rose of Cairo", "Whatever Works", "Apollo 13", "Once Upon a Time Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Marnie", "Bandhan", "Matchstick Men", "Sleepwalkers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["The Langoliers", "The Mosquito Coast", "The Final Cut", "Sleepless in Seattle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Runaway Bride", "Tales from Earthsea", "The Mist", "Khamoshi: The Musical"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["The Sum of All Fears", "Parker", "Dying Young", "Cujo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["The Expendables 3", "Cat's Eye", "The Conversation", "Billy Madison"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["The Talented Mr. Ripley", "Die Hard 2", "Children of the Corn", "The Spy Next Door"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Trucks", "Madea's Witness Protection", "The Great Buck Howard", "Bhoothnath"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Hot Shots! Part Deux", "WrestleMania XXX", "Creepshow 2", "In the Name of the King: A Dungeon Siege Tale"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["After Earth", "The Shining", "Looking for a Home", "Windtalkers"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["I Confess", "Rose Red", "Diljale", "Baaghi: A Rebel for Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Hansel and Gretel", "Children of the Corn IV: The Gathering", "Next", "The Undefeated"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["The Topkapi Affair", "Dolores Claiborne", "Priyamaanavale", "Kindergarten Cop"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["The Game of Their Lives", "In the Face of Demolition", "The Family That Preys", "Dreamcatcher"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["The Running Man", "Blossoms & Blood", "Riddick", "Daulat Ki Jung"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["2 Guns", "Ricochet", "Dolan's Cadillac", "That Darn Cat!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["50 First Dates", "The Lawnmower Man", "Minsara Kanna", "Shakespeare in Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Dilwale", "Aladdin", "Pardes", "Christine"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Pet Sematary", "Jaws", "Akele Hum Akele Tum", "Kung Fu Panda 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Bambi", "Misery", "The Fan", "Castle in the Sky: Bonus Material"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Kadhal FM", "Message in a Bottle", "Maximum Overdrive", "Close Encounters of the Third Kind"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Meet Joe Black", "The Thin Red Line", "Ajnabee", "Creepshow"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["The Jackal", "Step Brothers", "Stuck on You", "Quicksilver Highway"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Earth Girls Are Easy", "Carrie", "Eddie Presley", "Besharam"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["One Hour Photo", "Apt Pupil", "The Conversation", "Wild at Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Chennai Express", "Graveyard Shift", "Pilot Season", "Out of Sight"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["The Bonfire of the Vanities", "Chain Reaction", "Hearts in Atlantis", "2 Guns"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Men in Black", "True Grit", "The Dead Zone", "Cleopatra"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["WWE Tagged Classics 2003: No Way Out", "1408", "The Expendables", "CZ12"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["The Shawshank Redemption", "The Kid & I", "Safe", "Flying Swords of Dragon Gate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["The Big Boss", "Man of the Year", "Silver Bullet", "Johnny English"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["The Dark Tower", "Cupid & Cate", "The Bourne Identity", "Where the Truth Lies"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Arrietty", "Needful Things", "Ghajini", "Spirited Away"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Housefull 2", "Sangram", "The Dark Half", "Orphan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Blade Runner", "'Salem's Lot", "Love Potion No. 9", "The Animal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Kick-Ass", "The Stand", "Family Bond", "Gamer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Sometimes They Come Back... Again", "What's New Pussycat?", "City of Ember", "In Love and War"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Rosewater", "U Me Aur Hum", "The Topkapi Affair", "Stand by Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Apollo at 70: A Hot Night in Harlem", "The Talented Mr. Ripley", "Ek Rishtaa: The Bond of Love", "The Mangler"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Imagine", "White Water Summer", "It", "Cars"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Jack", "Stage Fright", "The Green Mile", "Anchorman 2: The Legend Continues"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Secret Window", "Extract", "Divine Secrets of the Ya-Ya Sisterhood", "To the Limit"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["The Jubilee Girl", "Stephen King's Desperation", "Crossing Over", "The Talented Mr. Ripley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Maid's Room: Return of the Master", "Gun Shy", "Rumble in the Bronx", "The Tommyknockers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Blue Valentine", "The Night Flier", "Mike Hammer: Murder Takes All", "Spanglish"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["We're Back! A Dinosaur's Story", "Azhagai Irukkirai Bayamai Irukkirathu", "Too Young the Hero", "Thinner"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["A Night at the Roxbury", "Sometimes They Come Back", "Across the Tracks", "Coogan's Bluff"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["The Panic in Needle Park", "Salem's Lot", "The Object of My Affection", "Lagaan: Once Upon a Time in India"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Firestarter", "Inside Man", "Ab Tumhare Hawale Watan Saathiyo", "Veyyil"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Riding the Bullet", "Ready", "Innerspace", "Toy Story 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Meet the Fockers", "Knightriders", "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", "The Libertine"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Stephen King?", "answers": ["Raajneeti", "Cop Out", "Children of the Corn: The Final Sacrifice", "Paul Blart: Mall Cop"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Lego: The Piece of Resistance", "She Wore a Yellow Ribbon", "Azhagai Irukkirai Bayamai Irukkirathu", "Peter Pan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["The Paradine Case", "National Geographic: Beyond the Movie: Pearl Harbor", "Fun and Fancy Free", "The Man Without a Face"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Flags of Our Fathers", "The Running Man", "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", "Jaanemann"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["True Women", "The Local Stigmatic", "Mary Poppins", "FernGully: The Last Rainforest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["The Fearless Hyena", "Dumbo", "Playing by Heart", "Left Behind"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Spanglish", "OMG \u2013 Oh My God!", "Gangaajal", "The Reluctant Dragon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Princess Protection Program", "Lethal Weapon 4", "Dirty Harry", "Winnie the Pooh and the Blustery Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["You Don't Mess with the Zohan", "Green Street", "Fantasia", "The Beach"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Turn It Up", "Ajnabee", "Curly Sue", "So Dear to My Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Melody Time", "Lucky Number Slevin", "On Your Mark", "The Brave"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Raging Bull", "Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man's Chest", "The Dark Side of the Sun", "American Teacher"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["The Campaign", "Doogal", "Attila", "The Skeleton Dance"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["The Blind Side", "Unstoppable", "The Mummy - Tomb of the Dragon Emperor", "The Haunted Mansion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Cop Out", "Hercules: The Thracian Wars", "I Now Pronounce You Chuck and Larry", "The Country Bears"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["The Journey of Natty Gann", "Seven Years in Tibet", "The Sword in the Stone", "The Foot Shooting Party"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["The Parent Trap", "Changeling", "Khamoshi: The Musical", "La escribana de uraba"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Madea Goes to Jail", "Death Proof", "Meet the Browns", "Pirates of the Caribbean: On Stranger Tides"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Kiss of the Dragon", "The Air I Breathe", "Romeo + Juliet", "The Jungle Book"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Sleepover", "Bambi", "1408", "Far and Away"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Mrs. Brown", "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", "True Romance", "X-Men: First Class"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["The Chain Reaction", "How to Train Your Dragon", "Hancock 2", "How to Swim"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Der Fuehrer's Face", "Kung Fu Panda 3", "Transcendence", "Being Human"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Sleeping Beauty", "Sky Captain and the World of Tomorrow", "Bronco Billy", "Kujiratori"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Taxi Driver", "The Three Caballeros", "Celebration of Gospel: Taking You Higher", "Elysium"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Life or Something Like It", "Heart", "Snatch", "Swiss Family Robinson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["The Fugitive", "Great Expectations", "Ferdinand the Bull", "Anger Management"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Paul Blart: Mall Cop", "Lambert the Sheepish Lion", "Kadhal FM", "De Dana Dan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Munna Bhai Chale Amerika", "Stone", "Squirrels to the Nuts", "Plane Crazy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Hum", "That Darn Cat!", "Under Capricorn", "Housefull 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Homefront", "Face/Off", "Make Mine Music", "Howl's Moving Castle"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Turn It Up", "The Big Trail", "Star Wars Episode II: Attack of the Clones", "Alice in Wonderland"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Bounce", "Husbands and Wives", "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", "The Virginity Hit"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["In the Bag", "The Tuxedo", "Fire with Fire", "Machete Kills"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Number Seventeen", "Two for the Money", "The Gauntlet", "Pirates of the Caribbean: At World's End"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Song of the South", "Island of Fire", "Kung Fu Panda Holiday", "Django Unchained"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Steel Magnolias", "City of Angels", "Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl", "The Virginity Hit"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["The Great Debaters", "Coolie", "Revenge for Jolly!", "Pinocchio"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["The Brave", "Babes in Toyland", "Longtime Companion", "Capone"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Heyy Babyy", "The Happiest Millionaire", "Master Spy: The Robert Hanssen Story", "Ghilli"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Shaolin Temple", "The Italian Job", "Donald in Mathmagic Land", "The River Wild"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["16 Blocks", "Pollyanna", "Suhaag", "Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Flowers and Trees", "Sin City: A Dame to Kill For", "Shout", "Cruising"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Hum Aapke Hain Kaun...!", "Three Little Pigs", "Ghost Rider", "Mei and the Kittenbus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Practical Magic", "Cape Fear", "Funny People", "Saludos Amigos"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Too Young to Die?", "The Wise Little Hen", "Platoon", "Mad Max"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Windtalkers", "Steamboat Willie", "Lonely Hearts", "Don Jon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Star Wars Episode VI: Return of the Jedi", "Cinderella", "Wrestling with Angels: Playwright Tony Kushner", "Snake Eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["The Myth", "How to Fish", "The Sugarland Express", "The Spiderwick Chronicles"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", "Baaghi: A Rebel for Love", "Witness", "Extreme Movie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Another Cinderella Story", "Class", "Death to Smoochy", "The Gnome-Mobile"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Edge of Darkness", "The 39 Steps", "Andaz Apna Apna", "Basic"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Pocahontas", "Working Girl", "Ricky Stanicky", "Wild at Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Drive Angry", "G-Force", "The Patriot", "Unbreakable"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Mad Max", "Sunny Leone Loves HD Porn", "Singles", "Drillbit Taylor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["When the Party's Over", "Daredevil", "Mrs. Soffel", "Bangkok Dangerous"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["The One", "Number Seventeen", "10 Years", "Tim"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Gods of Egypt", "Maximum Overdrive", "The Italian Job", "Mad Max 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Tomorrow Never Dies", "Armour of God", "Mad Max Beyond Thunderdome", "Ocean's Twelve"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["The Face: Jesus in Art", "Cleopatra", "Garv", "Bad Boys"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["The Deer Hunter", "Earth Girls Are Easy", "Tequila Sunrise", "Shakespeare in Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Just for Laughs: Stand-Up: Vol. 3: Launching Pad", "The Passion of the Christ", "Frost/Nixon", "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Miss Congeniality", "Apocalypto", "Reindeer Games", "Crank: High Voltage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Alex Cross", "Casino Royale", "Sonic the Hedgehog", "What Lies Beneath"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["CZ12", "Lethal Weapon", "Mei and the Kittenbus", "True Romance"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Emmtan-Magan", "Ransom", "Winter's Tale", "Joe"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["America's Sweethearts", "Bedtime Stories", "Beavis and Butt-head Do America", "Lethal Weapon 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Driving Miss Daisy", "Eliza Graves", "Lambert the Sheepish Lion", "Stolen Summer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Blackadder: Back & Forth", "Kaze Tachinu", "Conspiracy Theory", "Pain & Gain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["The Man Without a Face", "The Man Who Cried", "Star Wars Episode VI: Return of the Jedi", "Great Expectations"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Unbreakable", "Under Suspicion", "Summer City", "1408"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["The Expendables 3", "The Castle of Cagliostro", "Oscar", "Tomorrowland"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Interview with the Vampire: The Vampire Chronicles", "Braveheart", "Out of the Furnace", "Happy Feet Two"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Tyler Perry's Laugh to Keep from Crying", "Gallipoli", "Omkara", "Mars Attacks!"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Machete Kills", "Apocalypse Now", "Man About Town", "Sora Iro no Tane"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Maverick", "Daredevil", "Dick", "The Ladies Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["An American Tail: Fievel Goes West", "Paparazzi", "The Oxford Murders", "City of Ember"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["The Fever", "Scavenger Hunt", "Mean Machine", "The Million Dollar Hotel"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Parampara", "Get the Gringo", "Snake Eyes", "Minority Report"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Spy Hunter", "The Third Wheel", "The Farmer's Wife", "The Bounty"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Rasigan", "Twins", "Mad Max: Fury Road", "Turner & Hooch"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Empire of the Sun", "The Singing Detective", "Junior", "The Incredibles"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Minority Report", "Endrendrum Kadhal", "Laffapalooza! #1", "Shadowmancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["The Sex and Violence Family Hour", "Fanaa", "The Beaver", "Family Plot"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Gone Baby Gone", "Romeo Must Die", "We Were Soldiers", "Journey to Shiloh"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Hamlet", "Thunderbolt and Lightfoot", "Meeting Evil", "Captain Corelli's Mandolin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["LOL: Laughing Out Loud", "J. Edgar", "Attack Force Z", "The Final Cut"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Forever Young", "Turner & Hooch", "R.I.P.D.", "Cool World"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Love Is All There Is", "8", "Hansel & Gretel: Witch Hunters", "Payback"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Lethal Weapon 2", "Our Father", "Cat's Eye", "Zandalee"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial", "Behind the Candelabra", "A Walk to Remember", "Celebrating AFI"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Signs", "Fifty Shades of Blue", "The Defender", "Dial M for Murder"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Pulp Fiction", "Hannah Montana & Miley Cyrus: Best of Both Worlds Concert", "What Women Want", "Independence Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Collateral", "The Year of Living Dangerously", "Fanaa", "The Power of One"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Death Race", "The River", "Second Glance", "Rocky"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Eyes of an Angel", "Nerrukku Ner", "The High and the Mighty", "Leonard Cohen: I'm Your Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["A Jet-Setters Dream", "Air America", "Khiladiyon Ka Khiladi", "Blood Red"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Hugo", "Baazi", "The Chain Reaction", "Dear Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Lethal Weapon 4", "Django Unchained", "Foxcatcher", "Minority Report"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Bird on a Wire", "End of the Harvest", "Windtalkers", "Celebrity News Reels: Hollywood's Most Infamous Couples and Ugliest Breakups"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["End of the Harvest", "Chicken Run", "88 Minutes", "The Pleasure Garden"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mel Gibson?", "answers": ["Criminal Law", "1911", "The Appointment", "Braveheart: Bonus Material"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Digging to China", "Police Story 2", "The Dark Tower", "Sometimes They Come Back"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Rush Hour 2", "Tyler Perry's Laugh to Keep from Crying", "The Aviator", "Collateral"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Along Came Polly", "Derailed", "Twin Dragons", "The Goonies"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Losing Chase", "Friends", "Rumble in the Bronx", "The Journey of Natty Gann"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Miracles", "Foxcatcher", "Michael", "The Wolf of Wall Street"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["New Police Story", "Tai Chi Master", "Evan Almighty", "Clerks II"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Assassins", "The Lego Movie", "This Boy's Life", "Little Big Soldier"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Total Recall", "Spellbound", "Shinjuku Incident", "Dear John"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Shanghai Knights", "The Zero Theorem", "The Legend 2", "Chain Reaction"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Cat's Eye", "The Fearless Hyena", "Driven", "Without Limits"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Rob-B-Hood", "Extreme Movie", "The Color Purple", "Star Wars Episode III: Revenge of the Sith"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Thelma & Louise", "Pilot Season", "Turner & Hooch", "CZ12"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Kung Fu Panda 2", "How the West Was Won", "Legalese", "Sleepless in Seattle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Snake in the Eagle's Shadow", "Speed 2: Cruise Control", "Made in America", "Old School"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Dragons Forever", "Pazhani", "Titan A.E.", "Balto"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Armour of God II: Operation Condor", "Bird", "Princess Mononoke", "Jewel of the Sahara"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Jaane Tu Ya Jaane Na", "Master Spy: The Robert Hanssen Story", "1911", "Shadow of a Doubt"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Bad Lieutenant: Port of Call New Orleans", "The Karate Kid", "ATL", "Anchorman 2: The Legend Continues"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Riddick", "Dragon Lord", "Secret Agent", "Mazes and Monsters"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Ultimate Fights", "The Master", "Madea's Class Reunion", "Kung Fu Panda"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Gorgeous", "Semi-Pro", "Seven", "Sonic the Hedgehog"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["The Skin Game", "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind", "Trapped", "City Hunter"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Regarding Henry", "Arabian Nights", "One Fine Day", "Mr. Nice Guy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Dumb & Dumber", "Rush Hour 3", "Men in Black 3", "Desi Boyz"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["The Family Man", "Police Story 3: Super Cop", "Raising Arizona", "On Your Mark"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Around the World in 80 Days", "Doom", "Next", "Devdas"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Pulp Fiction", "Crime Story", "Dhoom 3: Back in Action", "War of the Worlds"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Fireflies in the Garden", "The Notebook", "The Passion of the Christ", "Wheels on Meals"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["The Forbidden Kingdom", "Battle in Seattle", "Bol Bachchan", "Rich and Strange"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Dream for an Insomniac", "The Tuxedo", "Leonard Cohen: I'm Your Man", "To the Limit"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["She's the Man", "Thunderbolt", "Thirupaachi", "Romeo + Juliet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Man About Town", "Rocky", "The Myth", "Nausica\u00e4 of the Valley of the Wind"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["While You Were Sleeping", "The Young Master", "Pyar To Hona Hi Tha", "The Running Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["All in the Family", "Lookin' to Get Out", "XXX: The Return of Xander Cage", "Men of Honor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Armour of God", "Safe", "Air Force One", "The Lady Vanishes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Drillbit Taylor", "Stalk of the Celery Monster", "Shanghai Noon", "Bananas"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["The Mangler", "A Jet-Setters Dream", "Marley & Me", "Drunken Master"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Baazi", "Gone Girl", "The Shawshank Redemption", "The Accidental Spy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Youth", "The Medallion", "Cocaine Cowboys", "The Sea Chase"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["The Dead Pool", "Horrible Bosses", "Titan A.E.", "The Legend of Drunken Master"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Every Which Way but Loose", "The Spy Next Door", "Cry Macho", "The Country Bears"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Jaanemann", "Dosti: Friends Forever", "Sivakasi", "The Big Brawl"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Snake Eyes", "Erotibot", "The New Shaolin Temple", "Conan the Destroyer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["What's Done in the Dark", "One Eight Seven", "Mike Hammer: Murder Takes All", "Police Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["The Taking of Pelham 123", "Who Am I?", "Shaft", "Joe Kidd"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Flesh and Blood", "The Tourist", "Phenomenon", "Police Story 4: First Strike"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Management", "Mr. Tadano's Secret Mission: From Japan with Love", "Ek Rishtaa: The Bond of Love", "The Expendables 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["Project A", "The Toxic Boy", "A Bucket of Blood", "Celebration of Gospel: Taking You Higher"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["World's Greatest Dad", "Once Bitten", "Island of Fire", "Two Weeks Notice"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["The Expendables 2", "Hide and Seek", "Nausica\u00e4 of the Valley of the Wind", "Rush Hour"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jackie Chan?", "answers": ["One Hundred and One Nights", "The Protector", "Trapped", "Crash"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Iron Monkey", "Only God Forgives", "Sleeper", "Saving Face"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["I'm Still Here: Real Diaries of Young People Who Lived During the Holocaust", "I Now Pronounce You Chuck and Larry", "Cowboys & Aliens", "Dynamo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Kurbaan", "Hollywood on Fire", "Logan's Run", "Good Deeds"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Murder in the First", "The Unbelievables", "Land of the Lost", "Hoshi o Katta Hi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["American Hustle", "Wild Wild West", "The Ides of March", "Boys on the Side"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Million Dollar Baby", "Going Overboard", "The Believer", "Casper"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Suits", "ReGeneration", "My Dog Skip", "Deewaar"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["The Story of Yanagawa's Canals", "De Dana Dan", "The Notebook", "The Five Senses"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Half Nelson", "On Your Mark", "Gorgeous", "Edge of Tomorrow"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["The Story of Yanagawa's Canals", "Coimbatore Mappillai", "Rudderless", "Untitled Terrence Malick project"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Edward Scissorhands", "The Quick and the Dead", "Stay", "The Boy in the Plastic Bubble"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Stage Fright", "How to Catch a Monster", "American Teacher", "Confessions of a Teenage Drama Queen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Seduced And Abandoned", "Bol Bachchan", "Dracula 2000", "Celebrity"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Kabhi Kabhie", "Lethal Weapon 4", "Remember the Titans", "Stolen Summer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Spanglish", "Magnum Force", "Fracture", "Men in Black"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["ATL", "Drive", "The Toxic Boy", "Diary of a Mad Black Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Night at the Museum: Battle of the Smithsonian", "Infancy", "Gangster Squad", "The Conversation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Bronco Billy", "Escape Plan", "Horrible Bosses", "Murder by Numbers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Gerry", "Meng li xi shi", "Air Force One", "The Place Beyond the Pines"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Tashan", "The Match Girl", "The Robber Bride", "Lars and the Real Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Joe", "Sivakasi", "The Slaughter Rule", "Dear Frankie"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Babylon A.D.", "Rear Window", "Runaway Bride", "Drunk History Christmas"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["The Skeleton Dance", "Valet Guys", "Edge of Darkness", "Blue Valentine"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Heyy Babyy", "The Jacket", "Don Juan DeMarco", "All Good Things"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Nothing Too Good for a Cowboy", "Two Weeks Notice", "Air America", "Life or Something Like It"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ryan Gosling?", "answers": ["Beyond All Boundaries", "The United States of Leland", "Windtalkers", "Daddy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Foreign Correspondent", "Jerry Maguire", "Fantastic Mr. Fox", "Cast Away"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Top Gun", "The Last Stand", "Snakes on a Plane", "Manhattan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Machine Gun Preacher", "Circle of Iron", "The Hardy Men", "Analyze This"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Dick Tracy", "Braveheart", "Jack Reacher", "The Night Flier"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Cocktail", "A Soldier's Story", "Hum Hain Rahi Pyar Ke", "Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Changing Lanes", "Eyes Wide Shut", "Hope Springs", "Love Love Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["A Sumo Wrestler's Tail", "Far and Away", "Rounders", "Sky"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Without Limits", "Boiler Room", "Walking Tall", "Gangaajal"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Rhinestone", "To the Wonder", "Tropic Thunder", "Hollywoodland"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Dazed and Confused", "Trapped", "Under the Sea 3D", "Celebrity News Reels: Hollywood's Most Infamous Couples and Ugliest Breakups"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Edge of Tomorrow", "One Eight Seven", "The Air Up There", "Kung Fu Panda Holiday"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Donnie Brasco", "Parker", "Elizabethtown", "The Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Walking Tall", "Shakti: The Power", "The Last Samurai", "Working Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Mission: Impossible II", "Raw Deal", "Jodhaa Akbar", "The Incredibles"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Lions for Lambs", "So Undercover", "The Local Stigmatic", "Night Skies"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Rain Man", "Sky Captain and the World of Tomorrow", "The Parent Trap", "Baaghi: A Rebel for Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Taps", "The Secret Life of Bees", "Men in Black 3", "The Truth About Charlie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Born to Defence", "WWE: The Videos: Vol. 1: Ramped Up", "Ghost Rider: Spirit of Vengeance", "Top Gun 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["The Panic in Needle Park", "The Color of Money", "Suhaag", "Sarfarosh"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Ab Tumhare Hawale Watan Saathiyo", "Interview with the Vampire: The Vampire Chronicles", "The Sons of Katie Elder", "Dirty Harry"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Days of Thunder", "Movie 43", "Hollywood Homicide", "The House Bunny"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Kurbaan", "Hitting It Hard", "WWE: WrestleMania 27: Vol. 2", "The Mask"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Minority Report", "School Ties", "Havoc", "Under the Sea 3D"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Stop! Or My Mom Will Shoot", "Deewangee", "Setup", "Northern Lights"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Magnolia", "Welcome to Collinwood", "The Tommyknockers", "K-19: The Widowmaker"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["All the Right Moves", "Knockaround Guys", "Big Jake", "Flowers and Trees"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Cowboys & Aliens", "Mandingo", "Vanilla Sky", "Paul"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Nick of Time", "Oblivion", "Naked in New York", "Dolan's Cadillac"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["The Langoliers", "The Contract", "Losin' It", "World War Z"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Silsila", "Cellular", "Since You've Been Gone", "Mission: Impossible"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Christmas in Connecticut", "Jay and Silent Bob Strike Back", "Valkyrie", "Hudson Hawk"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["One More Kiss", "Minority Report: Bonus Material", "The Unbelievables", "A Jet-Setters Dream"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["One Hundred and One Dalmatians", "Van Helsing", "The Grifters", "The Air Up There"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Diner", "Mission: Impossible 5", "Once Upon a Time in America", "Rush Hour"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Anger Management", "The Brave Heart Will Take the Bride", "A Few Good Men", "Jhoom Barabar Jhoom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["No Place to Hide", "Sendhoorapandi", "McQ", "Mission: Impossible \u2013 Ghost Protocol"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["The Shootist", "Sleepover", "Bronco Billy", "Mission: Impossible III"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["A Soldier's Story", "Let the Devil Wear Black", "Rock of Ages", "Hollywood Ending"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["The Dark Half", "Collateral", "Kal Ho Naa Ho", "Revolution"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["The Work of Director Michel Gondry", "Legend", "Bucky Larson: Born to Be a Star", "Shooter"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["XXX: The Return of Xander Cage", "Men of Honor", "Hook", "The Thetan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["American Gangster", "Police Story 3: Super Cop", "Arizona Dream", "Suspect Zero"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Yes Boss", "Dial M for Murder", "Knight and Day", "Poltergeist"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Color of Night", "Iron Monkey", "The Outsiders", "Max Payne"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Born on the Fourth of July", "The Whole Nine Yards", "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind", "Family Plot"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["For Colored Girls", "High Crimes", "Ask the Dust", "Arrietty"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Suspicion", "Snatch", "Risky Business", "Toy Story 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Ninaithen Vandhai", "The Bumblebee Flies Anyway", "Die Hard with a Vengeance", "The Firm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Minsara Kanna", "Endless Love", "Around the World in 80 Days", "Finding Forrester"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tom Cruise?", "answers": ["Mazes and Monsters", "The Bowling Ball", "Talladega Nights: The Ballad of Ricky Bobby", "War of the Worlds"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Child in the Night", "Abraham Lincoln: Vampire Hunter", "Vaseegara", "Tezz"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["The Jayne Mansfield Story", "Saludos Amigos", "Parkland", "Big Eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Muqaddar Ka Sikandar", "The Nightmare Before Christmas", "Minions", "How to Train Your Dragon 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Amar Akbar Anthony", "The Wizards Return: Alex vs. Alex", "Scavenger Hunt", "Edward Scissorhands"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Ocean's Eleven", "A League of Their Own", "Batman", "Dream for an Insomniac"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Happy Birthday", "Pazhani", "The Thin Red Line", "Sometimes They Come Back"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["In the Line of Fire", "Castle in the Sky", "True Romance", "Stalk of the Celery Monster"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Peepli Live", "Sunny Leone Loves HD Porn", "Used Guys", "Alice in Wonderland"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["The Wolf of Wall Street", "Misery", "Cabin Boy", "Domestic Disturbance"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["James and the Giant Peach", "Super", "Vettaikkaaran", "Three Little Pigs"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["The Karate Kid", "Pee-wee's Big Adventure", "Vertigo", "The Five Senses"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Along Came Polly", "Heart", "Lethal Weapon", "Big Fish"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["The Match Girl", "Maggie", "Transformers: Age of Extinction", "The Mechanic"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Eliza Graves", "Thick as Thieves", "Star Kid", "Empire State"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Beetlejuice", "Lucky Number Slevin", "The Score", "Boiler Room"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Hearts in Atlantis", "Dark Shadows", "Scarface", "16 Blocks"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Bon Voyage", "Lucky Numbers", "Troy", "The Robot Boy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["The Bowling Ball", "The Fearless Hyena", "Primary Colors", "The Dark Half"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Kuch Kuch Hota Hai", "Vincent", "Angela & Viril", "Limitless"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Romeo + Juliet", "Ed Wood", "Bicentennial Man", "Avalon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["9", "Blind Date", "Never Say Never Again", "Safe Haven"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Singles", "Kadhalukku Mariyadhai", "Popeye", "Dazed and Confused"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Amar Akbar Anthony", "Dil Kya Kare", "Corpse Bride", "The Brazilian Job"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Batman Forever", "Fantasia", "Babylon A.D.", "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Winter Passing", "Balto", "Time Share", "The Toxic Boy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["xXx", "Beowulf", "Mars Attacks!", "My Least Favorite Career"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Winter's Tale", "Frankenweenie (1984)", "Unidentified", "End of Days"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Five", "The Chronicles of Riddick: Dark Fury", "Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street", "Day Zero"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["The Girl Who Stares", "Step Up 2: The Streets", "Apocalypse Now", "Invictus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["School Ties", "Don: The Chase Begins Again", "Har Dil Jo Pyar Karega", "Hansel and Gretel"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Comic Relief 2007", "Lincoln's Gettysburg Address", "The Island of Doctor Agor", "WWE: WrestleMania 27: Vol. 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Frankenweenie", "Badlanders", "Alice", "Wizards of Waverly Place: The Movie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["The Adventures of Huck Finn", "Cinema16: American Short Films", "Capone", "The Counselor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["The Firm", "Biwi Ho To Aisi", "What Women Want", "Sleepy Hollow"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Hancock", "Sainik", "Khatta Meetha", "Spike & Mike's Classic Festival of Animation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Love Happens", "Stories USA", "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory", "The Bourne Identity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Chellamae", "Stainboy's Day Off", "Lakeview Terrace", "Domestic Disturbance"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Unthinkable", "Batman Returns", "Deep Throat Part II", "Striking Distance"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Tim Burton?", "answers": ["Minsara Kanna", "Planet of the Apes", "The Producers", "I am Here"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Indiana Jones and the Raiders of the Lost Ark", "Tum Mere Ho", "Saawariya", "Butterfly on a Wheel"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Fool's Gold", "Baghban", "Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom", "You've Got Mail"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Lincoln", "Kilroy", "Manhattan Murder Mystery", "Dalai Lama Renaissance"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Yeh Lamhe Judaai Ke", "Charlie Wilson's War", "A Time for Killing", "Naajayaz"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Dan in Real Life", "Crossing Over", "Cyborg 2", "Unleashed"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Unbecoming Age", "Simon Birch", "Clear and Present Danger", "Attila"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Riddle", "Blade Runner", "Three O'Clock High", "Bird"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Grown Ups", "CZ12", "Syriana", "42"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Unidentified", "Jaan", "Outbreak", "Random Hearts"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Khiladi 786", "Star Wars Episode IV: A New Hope", "Longtime Companion", "Nishabd"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Spanglish", "Presumed Innocent", "JFK", "Singham"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Stuck on You", "Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade", "That's My Boy", "The Big Trail"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Hollywood Homicide", "It Could Happen to You", "Johnny Suede", "The Big Brawl"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Patriot Games", "Song of the South", "Jamaica Inn", "Unbecoming Age"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Valkyrie", "Hanover Street", "Tears of the Sun", "Ash Wednesday"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["The Cable Guy", "Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull", "Blackmail", "Friends"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Daylight", "Fried Green Tomatoes", "Himmatwala", "K-19: The Widowmaker"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Shahjahan", "Carbon Copy", "The Devil's Rain", "One Hundred and One Nights"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Endrendrum Kadhal", "The Conversation", "Tequila Sunrise", "The Lego Movie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Kung Fu Panda Holiday", "The Devil's Own", "Sora Iro no Tane", "Love Actually"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Star Wars Holiday Special", "Behind the Candelabra", "Going Overboard", "Cool World"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Star Wars Episode VI: Return of the Jedi", "The Legend", "Interview with the Vampire: The Vampire Chronicles", "Changing Lanes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["The Jungle Book", "The Bone Collector", "Star Wars Episode V: The Empire Strikes Back", "Rope"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Planet of the Apes", "Diner", "Smokin' Aces", "Apocalypse Now"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Luv", "Hart's War", "Kids From Shaolin", "Kaalia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Rope", "Ender's Game", "Beretta's Island", "Torn Curtain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Grindhouse", "Nights in Rodanthe", "What Lies Beneath", "Green Zone"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Thamizhan", "Spanglish", "Red Surf", "Sabrina"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["London Dreams", "Invitation Only", "The Italian Job", "Frantic"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["The Green Mile", "The Contortionist's Handbook", "The Counselor", "Journey to Shiloh"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Revenge for Jolly!", "Yohan: Adhyayam Ondru", "American Graffiti", "Akele Hum Akele Tum"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Untitled Terrence Malick project", "Force 10 from Navarone", "Deadfall", "A Good Day to Die Hard"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Capone", "The Front", "Whisper of the Heart", "James Michener's Dynasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Zanjeer", "Extraordinary Measures", "The Skeleton Dance", "Happy Feet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Drive Angry", "Working Girl", "Arumugam", "Escape Plan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["The Paradine Case", "Rambo: First Blood Part II", "Stay Hungry", "The Fugitive"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["The Gauntlet", "When the Party's Over", "Cowboys & Aliens", "Superstar"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Unleashed", "The Specialist", "Valet Guys", "Firewall"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["All in the Family", "Star Kid", "Sholay", "Zabriskie Point"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["The Comancheros", "The Precious One", "Happy Birthday", "Air Force One"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Days of Thunder", "Getting Straight", "Ainthu Ainthu Ainthu", "Hannah Montana: The Movie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Office Space", "Mission: Impossible III", "Apocalypse Now Redux", "Blind Date"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["The Langoliers", "Dolan's Cadillac", "Witness", "Grudge Match"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Khiladi", "Vanilla Sky", "The Frisco Kid", "Stardust Memories"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["The Expendables", "Regarding Henry", "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham", "Ajnabee"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["The Chronicles of Riddick", "City Hunter", "Morning Glory", "Edge of Tomorrow"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Wake of the Red Witch", "Red Sonja", "Heroes", "Look Who's Talking"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Twin Dragons", "The Mosquito Coast", "Zandalee", "Lagaan: Once Upon a Time in India"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["Lone Survivor", "Thirupaachi", "The Big Hit", "Six Days Seven Nights"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["The Defender", "The Expendables 3", "Baghban", "Reach Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Harrison Ford?", "answers": ["The Legend of Drunken Master", "Firestarter", "Ciudad", "Paranoia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Jamaica Inn", "In the Line of Fire", "George Wallace", "Toys"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man's Chest", "Bad Boys II", "The Notebook", "Robots"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["August Rush", "Maid's Room: Return of the Master", "The Fever", "The Jayne Mansfield Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["The Tree of Life", "The Sword in the Stone", "The Angriest Man in Brooklyn", "Bad Lieutenant: Port of Call New Orleans"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["How to Swim", "Butterfly on a Wheel", "Happy Feet Two", "Back to the Future Part II"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Hamlet", "Finding Forrester", "Dumb & Dumber", "Treasure Island"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Ferdinand the Bull", "Ask the Dust", "Club Paradise", "Tere Naam"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Hulchul", "Mann", "In Love and War", "The Night Listener"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Tees Maar Khan", "Bicentennial Man", "Thirupaachi", "Qayamat: City Under Threat"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Much Ado About Nothing", "Bollywood Dreams", "Deconstructing Harry", "Chinese Coffee"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["OMG \u2013 Oh My God!", "Interiors", "We Were Soldiers", "Popeye"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["The Anna Nicole Smith Story", "Moment by Moment", "Nine Months", "Peepli Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Good Will Hunting", "Fast & Furious", "Office Killer", "Elephant White"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["The Three Caballeros", "Fathers' Day", "Yuvan Yuvathi", "Angels and Demons"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Chain Reaction", "\"Dr. Wai in \"\"The Scripture with No Words\"\"\"", "Madea Goes to Jail", "The Big White"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Aladdin", "Rambo", "Turbo", "A Time to Kill"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Star Wars Episode V: The Empire Strikes Back", "Kekk\u00f4 Kamen: Premium", "Kisses in the Dark", "Jumanji"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Mrs. Soffel", "Blackmail", "What Dreams May Come", "Sleepers"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Ghulam", "House of D", "A Place in Time", "Mrs. Soffel"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Attack Force Z", "What's Done in the Dark", "Live Free or Die Hard", "Patch Adams"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Jingle All the Way", "Awakenings", "Contagion", "It"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Old Dogs", "Sangharsh", "Bringing Out the Dead", "Spirit: Stallion of the Cimarron"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["The Sorcerer and the White Snake", "One Hour Photo", "Wake of the Red Witch", "The Trouble with Harry"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Rat Race", "FernGully: The Last Rainforest", "Life of Crime", "Total Recall"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Sweet and Lowdown", "Rango", "The Birdcage", "Planet 51"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Dead Poets Society", "The Loved One", "I Confess", "Tum Mere Ho"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Meet the Fockers", "Rounders", "The Heart Is But A Child", "Flubber"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Death Race", "Naam", "A.I. Artificial Intelligence", "As Long as I Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Man of the Year", "Ponyo", "The Stand", "Serpico"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Children of the Corn", "Hancock", "Jack", "Action Replayy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Akira", "Sleepy Hollow", "Hook", "Since You've Been Gone"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Blackadder: Back & Forth", "Death to Smoochy", "Four Weddings and a Funeral", "World War Z"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Lagaan: Once Upon a Time in India", "The Air I Breathe", "The Final Cut", "Actress"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Insomnia", "Small Time Crooks", "War Horse", "The Newton Boys"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Aladdin and the King of Thieves", "Revenge for Jolly!", "Marlowe", "Hey Ram"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Rain Man", "Awwal Number", "The Big Wedding", "Collateral"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Jism 2", "Flawless", "World's Greatest Dad", "The Red Curtain Trilogy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Apollo 13", "Happy Feet", "Haywire", "Hancock"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Abbot Hai Teng of Shaolin", "RV", "National Treasure: Book of Secrets", "Hot Shots! Part Deux"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Spirited Away", "Once Upon a Time in China and America", "Night at the Museum: Battle of the Smithsonian", "Patriot Games"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Jakob the Liar", "Snitch", "The Peacemaker", "Barood"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Death Sentence", "Shark", "The Survivors", "Topaz"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["The War Wagon", "Awwal Number", "Dead Again", "Pretty Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Robin Williams: Weapons of Self-Destruction", "The Avengers: Age of Ultron", "The Office Party", "Gamer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Bangkok Dangerous", "The River Wild", "Pulp Fiction", "License to Wed"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Air Force One", "Mad Max Beyond Thunderdome", "The World According to Garp", "War of the Worlds"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["The Fisher King", "Coming to America", "Suits", "Hammy's Boomerang Adventure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["The Robot Boy", "The Happening", "Being Human", "Full Frontal"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Looking for a Home", "Sleeping Beauty", "Night at the Museum", "Kekk\u00f4 Kamen: Royale"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robin Williams?", "answers": ["Jaws", "Along Came Polly", "S.W.A.T.", "Mrs. Doubtfire"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["The Benchwarmers", "Birdy", "The Forbidden Kingdom", "Mr. Wonderful"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Talladega Nights: The Ballad of Ricky Bobby", "Legalese", "Birdy", "Firelight"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Riddick: Blindsided", "The Hudsucker Proxy", "Ajnabee", "Too Young the Hero"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Romance & Cigarettes", "Hitman", "The Punisher", "Suspect Zero"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Harrison's Flowers", "Spy Hunter", "Miracle Run", "The Three Caballeros"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["The Client", "Phenomenon", "Machine Gun Preacher", "The Cable Guy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Bullets Over Broadway", "Jhoom Barabar Jhoom", "Confessions of a Teenage Drama Queen", "Kujiratori"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["100 Years of Comedy", "Old Dogs", "The Best Thief in the World", "Tezz"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Rio Lobo", "Goodbye Lover", "Pushing Tin", "Another Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Sin City: A Dame to Kill For", "Murder in Mind", "Jo Jeeta Wohi Sikandar", "Horrible Bosses"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Angels in America", "Anand", "Speed 2: Cruise Control", "The Castle of Cagliostro"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Cupid & Cate", "Jaws", "Fanaa", "A Guide to Recognizing Your Saints"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Now You See Me", "Boys on the Side", "The Naked Gun 33\u2153: The Final Insult", "Striking Distance"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Howl", "Cloud Atlas", "The Sons of Katie Elder", "Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["The Last Stand", "The Legend of Bagger Vance", "RED 2", "The Last Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Bambi", "Aladdin", "Baadshah", "Let the Devil Wear Black"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Pu-239", "Dil Se", "Dick", "The Maker"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Taps", "The Mountain Eagle", "The Simple Life of Noah Dearborn", "The Parent Trap"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["John Q", "Police Story", "Saved!", "Pr\u00eat-\u00e0-Porter"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["The Year of Living Dangerously", "Red Dragon", "The Robot Boy", "Deuce Bigalow: European Gigolo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Sleepless in Seattle", "Two for the Money", "Legend of the Boneknapper Dragon", "Signs of Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Shutter Island", "My Dog Skip", "The Portrait of a Lady", "Oscar"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Office Space", "Solitary Man", "Boss", "The Libertine"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Stardust", "Lethal Weapon 2", "She's So Lovely", "Master Spy: The Robert Hanssen Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Men in Black: Alien Attack", "The Mummy Returns", "Wrestling with Angels: Playwright Tony Kushner", "Color of Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Unity", "National Treasure: Book of Secrets", "Yaarana", "Reckless"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["The Good Girl", "Irokoishi", "Pipe Dream", "Chicken Run"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["42", "Angels and Demons", "The Spiderwick Chronicles", "Saving Mr. Banks"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Attack Force Z", "Eddie Presley", "Fried Green Tomatoes", "The Mangler"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Pushing Tin", "RED", "The Spirit", "Antz"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Khushi", "R.I.P.D.", "The Untouchables", "The Young Master"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Desperado", "Love", "Les Passages", "The Spy Next Door"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Short Fuse", "Madea's Witness Protection", "Zila Ghaziabad", "Django Unchained"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["The Assassination of Jesse James by the Coward Robert Ford", "Old School", "Kicking & Screaming", "The Bourne Supremacy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Grand Canyon", "Spy Kids", "Arthur and the Vengeance of Maltazard", "On Your Mark"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Pocahontas", "The Substitute", "Winter's Tale", "Naked in New York"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["The Switch", "SugarTime", "Rascals", "The Fighter"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["The Shootist", "Kung Fu Panda Holiday", "The Robber Bride", "Saving Private Ryan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["The Five Senses", "Ladder 49", "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham", "Green Zone"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Longtime Companion", "Echelon", "To the Limit", "So Dear to My Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Mary-Louise Parker?", "answers": ["Where the Truth Lies", "A Place for Annie", "Raju Chacha", "The Godfather"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Beyond All Boundaries", "Sweet and Lowdown", "Gabbar", "Frankenweenie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Pirates of the Caribbean: On Stranger Tides", "Child in the Night", "Joe Kidd", "Steamboat Willie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Urban Cowboy", "Black Mask", "Pistol", "The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Radio Flyer", "Serpico", "Foxcatcher", "Gorgeous"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Rajavin Parvaiyile", "'Salem's Lot", "Picture Perfect", "Boobie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["A Place in Time", "Black and White", "Blood Red", "The Heart Is But A Child"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Stone Cold Steve Austin: The Bottom Line on the Most Popular Superstar of All Time", "Rocky V", "Coriolanus", "Green Street"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Don", "Fight for Your Right Revisited", "Smokin' Aces", "Menace II Society"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["The Ninth Gate", "English Vinglish", "The Adventures of Tom Thumb and Thumbelina", "Swordsman II"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Good Deeds", "Revenge for Jolly!", "Glengarry Glen Ross", "Nights in Rodanthe"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Marnie", "Internal Affairs", "Jung", "Kung Fu Panda: Secrets of the Masters"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Eyes Wide Shut", "The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey", "Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom", "Six Days Seven Nights"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Flipper", "Soul Men", "No Place to Hide", "Aitraaz"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["9", "The Majestic", "Payback", "The World According to Garp"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Kadhalukku Mariyadhai", "XXX: The Return of Xander Cage", "The Five Senses", "The Hobbit: There and Back Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Sinatra", "Contagion", "Back to the Future Part II", "An American Tail: Fievel Goes West"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Leonard Cohen: I'm Your Man", "Flubber", "Chains of Gold", "North"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Hanover Street", "Spy Kids 3-D: Game Over", "Something Like a Business", "Grease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Club Paradise", "The Romantics", "Velayudham", "A Place in Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Jo Jeeta Wohi Sikandar", "Happy Feet Two", "Misery", "Gia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["The Lion King", "The Good German", "Avalon", "Thambikku Indha Ooru"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Happy Feet", "The Talented Mr. Ripley", "Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl", "Fathers' Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["The War", "Shout", "Magic Mike", "Speed"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Try Seventeen", "Notorious", "Tim Janis: Beautiful America", "Parampara"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["This Means War", "Marnie", "The Bumblebee Flies Anyway", "The Journey of Natty Gann"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["The Ice Storm", "Friends", "The Other Guys", "Los Bandoleros"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["The Faculty", "Stage Fright", "Billy Madison", "Much Ado About Nothing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers", "Homefront", "Tropic Thunder", "Heart Stopper"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Treasure Island", "World War Z", "The Ides of March", "Whisper of the Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Chains of Gold", "Full Frontal", "The Good Son", "Finding Neverland"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Endless Love", "Nanban", "Attila", "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Sin City", "Phool Aur Kaante", "The Love Guru", "The Goree Girls"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Premonition", "Quicksilver Highway", "The Oxford Murders", "Stone Cold Steve Austin: The Bottom Line on the Most Popular Superstar of All Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Oliver Twist", "The Color of Money", "Hamlet", "Ishq"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["New Police Story", "Legalese", "The Heat", "The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["February 14", "Public Enemies", "Maniac", "The Vanishing"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["I Love You Phillip Morris", "Dil Se", "Cast Away", "Open Windows"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Death Sentence", "Andaaz", "Scary Movie 4", "Forever Young"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Conan the Barbarian", "Fallen", "Pawnshop Chronicles", "The Negotiator"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Ash Wednesday", "Nights in Rodanthe", "Villu", "'Salem's Lot"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Red River", "Hitch", "Bobby", "Everyone Says I Love You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Jakob the Liar", "The Night Listener", "The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring", "Maine Pyar Kiya"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["The Negotiator", "The War Wagon", "Paradise", "The Last Witch Hunter"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull", "Celeste and Jesse Forever", "Platoon", "Hart's War"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Dear John", "Under the Sea 3D", "Day-O", "OMG \u2013 Oh My God!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Natural Born Killers", "Drillbit Taylor", "Apollo at 70: A Hot Night in Harlem", "Everything Is Illuminated"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Kung Fu Panda 2", "Day Zero", "Syriana", "Swades"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Cry Macho", "Deep Blue Sea", "Deep Impact", "Fort Apache"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Elijah Wood?", "answers": ["Fast Times at Ridgemont High", "Remember the Titans", "Red Dragon", "The Adventures of Huck Finn"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Kindergarten Cop", "Now You See Me", "Joker", "Benny & Joon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["The Medallion", "Ultimate Fights", "The Bucket List", "Drunken Master"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["The Sum of All Fears", "Sweet Time Together", "Chisum", "Aankhen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Shinjuku Incident", "Along Came a Spider", "Random Hearts", "The Dead Pool"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["The Rookie", "Marvin's Room", "Flying Swords of Dragon Gate", "Glory"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["J. Edgar", "North", "What's Done in the Dark", "Edison"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Saving Private Ryan", "Conan the Barbarian", "Enemy of the State", "Star Wars Episode V: The Empire Strikes Back"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Simon Birch", "Unforgiven", "Lawaaris", "Man of the Year"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Paul Blart: Mall Cop", "High Crimes", "Hanover Street", "Nick of Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["War of the Worlds", "I'm Still Here: Real Diaries of Young People Who Lived During the Holocaust", "Phenomenon", "Signs of Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["The Love Guru", "The Searchers", "Midnight in Paris", "Eyes Wide Shut"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["One Hundred and One Nights", "Mr. Bean's Holiday", "Big Fish", "The Maiden Heist"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Wild at Heart", "The Story of Us", "Promised Land", "The Power of One"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["The Singing Detective", "Masti: Sanam Teri Kasam", "Bruce Almighty", "Revenge for Jolly!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Sangharsh", "Fight Club", "Qayamat: City Under Threat", "Driving Miss Daisy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Under Suspicion", "Children of the Corn", "Why Did I Get Married", "Sleepers"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["To Catch a Thief", "Andaz Naya Naya", "Blue", "Chain Reaction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["22 Jump Street", "Two Weeks Notice", "Leprechaun", "Unleashed"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Hitch", "Jumanji", "Elizabethtown", "Dolphin Tale"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Glengarry Glen Ross", "She's Having a Baby", "The Shawshank Redemption", "Jhoom Barabar Jhoom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["...And Justice for All", "Heart Stopper", "Circle of Iron", "Scent of a Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["The Magic of Belle Isle", "An American Tail: Fievel Goes West", "Pecan Pie", "Flying Swords of Dragon Gate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Bounce", "Firefox", "She's the One", "Batman Begins"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["The Color of Money", "Bodyguard", "Robin Hood: Prince of Thieves", "The Office Party"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Hey Ram", "Gun Shy", "Hansel & Gretel: Witch Hunters", "The Contract"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Twister", "Fanaa", "RED", "Punchline"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Besharam", "English Vinglish", "Joe Versus the Volcano", "The Dark Knight"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Gone Baby Gone", "Vanilla Sky", "Born to Defence", "Insomnia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Dreamcatcher", "The Tall Guy", "Sea of Love", "Birdy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Street Smart", "The Will Smith Music Video Collection", "Ghost Rider", "Seeking a Friend for the End of the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Two Weeks Notice", "Thunderbolt", "Sangharsh", "The Dark Knight Rises"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Meeting Evil", "Deep Impact", "Body of Lies", "The Rundown"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Son of Sardaar", "Oblivion", "The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring", "Power"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Bad Lieutenant: Port of Call New Orleans", "Monte Carlo", "The Story of Us", "Wanted"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Rails & Ties", "The New Legend Of Shaolin", "Brubaker", "The Dark Tower"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Behind the Candelabra", "Lean on Me", "Thunderbolt and Lightfoot", "City Hall"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Chellamae", "Blades of Glory", "Lucky Number Slevin", "Office Space"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["A Sumo Wrestler's Tail", "End of the Harvest", "Tezz", "Amistad"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Escape Plan", "Broadway Danny Rose", "Evan Almighty", "Poor Things"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Thick as Thieves", "Melinda and Melinda", "The Newton Boys", "Tears of the Sun"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Playing by Heart", "The Legend", "Dil Chahta Hai", "Feast of Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Collateral", "Mona Lisa Smile", "The Deer Hunter", "Outbreak"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Shark Tale", "Benny & Joon", "Going Overboard", "Hard Rain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["The Tourist", "Love Is All There Is", "Trapped", "The Pawnbroker"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Stand Up Guys", "Parker", "Stage Fright", "Million Dollar Baby"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Seven", "Hollywood Ending", "Journey 3: From the Earth to the Moon", "Flawless"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Youth", "The Three Caballeros", "Kiss the Girls", "The Aviator"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Lego: The Piece of Resistance", "The Lawnmower Man", "The Green Berets", "Deep Throat Part II"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["The Secret Policeman's Other Ball", "Unknown Soldier", "The Searchers", "Invictus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Jupiter Ascending", "An Unfinished Life", "Indiana Jones and the Raiders of the Lost Ark", "Two for the Money"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Morgan Freeman?", "answers": ["Olympus Has Fallen", "Evolution", "A Love Song for Bobby Long", "Jung"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Avalon", "Clerks II", "A League of Their Own", "Knockaround Guys"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Daddy's Little Girls", "Find Me Guilty", "2 Guns", "Celebration of Gospel: Taking You Higher"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Priyamaanavale", "Horrible Bosses", "Saving Private Ryan", "The Dark Tower"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Once Upon a Time in China II", "The Last Witch Hunter", "Har Dil Jo Pyar Karega", "The Dead Zone"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Friends with Money", "Revolutionary Road", "Innerspace", "The Machine"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Riddick: Blindsided", "The Ice Storm", "Slow Burn", "Maine Pyar Kiya"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["That Darn Cat!", "Boiler Room", "Dazed and Confused", "Patriot Games"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Zanjeer", "Strays", "Loverboy", "Return to Horror High"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["The Chronicles of Riddick", "The Man in the Iron Mask", "The Mexican", "Body of Lies"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Fast & Furious 6", "Unknown Soldier", "Turner & Hooch", "The Sorcerer's Apprentice"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Porco Rosso: The Last Sortie", "Multi-Facial", "Rumble in the Bronx", "I Love You Phillip Morris"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Tooth Fairy", "Anything Else", "The Chronicles of Riddick: Dark Fury", "The Monuments Men"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Phir Bhi Dil Hai Hindustani", "Fast & Furious 7", "Mercury Rising", "Legend of the Lost"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["100 Years of Comedy", "Riddick", "Dead Man", "Eddie Presley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["The Legend of Cain", "I Now Pronounce You Chuck and Larry", "The Fast and the Furious", "Police Story 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["American Hustle", "Lara Croft Tomb Raider: The Cradle of Life", "Ainthu Ainthu Ainthu", "A Man Apart"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["The Pacifier", "Bolt", "Six Days Seven Nights", "Bean"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Flawless", "Get Smart", "A Christmas Carol", "The Iron Giant"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["The Man Without a Face", "Lonely Hearts", "Curious George", "Fast Five"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Guardians of the Galaxy", "Besharam", "Havoc", "Annie Hall"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Fast & Furious", "Pinocchio", "Snake in the Eagle's Shadow", "Aitraaz"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Pushing Tin", "The Beguiled", "Austin Powers: International Man of Mystery", "XXX: The Return of Xander Cage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Eddie Presley", "Shark Tale", "The Green Mile", "xXx"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Lore", "Pitch Black", "Jaan", "The Big Brawl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["Stolen Summer", "All the Right Moves", "Brock Lesnar: Here Comes the Pain", "Babylon A.D."], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Vin Diesel?", "answers": ["The Face: Jesus in Art", "The Birds", "Sainik", "Los Bandoleros"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Cusack?", "answers": ["The House Bunny", "The Journey of Natty Gann", "XXX: The Return of Xander Cage", "Talaash"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Cusack?", "answers": ["Zandalee", "Igor", "Ils se mari\u00e8rent et eurent beaucoup d'enfants", "Melody Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Cusack?", "answers": ["Drunk History Christmas", "The Transporter", "Money for Nothing", "Riddick"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Cusack?", "answers": ["Don", "The Karate Kid 2", "A Fistful of Dollars", "The Grifters"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Cusack?", "answers": ["Going Overboard", "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", "Bernard and the Genie", "Con Air"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Cusack?", "answers": ["The Brothers Grimm", "A Perfect World", "Making Sandwiches", "Sixteen Candles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Cusack?", "answers": ["The Descendants", "Dumbo", "Two for the Money", "The Numbers Station"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Cusack?", "answers": ["Class", "Marley & Me", "Star Wars Episode IV: A New Hope", "Lupin the 3rd: The Castle of Cagliostro: Special Edition"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Cusack?", "answers": ["Say Anything...", "The Night Listener", "Windtalkers", "Collateral Damage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Cusack?", "answers": ["You've Got Mail", "One Crazy Summer", "High Risk", "The Net"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["The Big Brawl", "Orphan", "Machine Gun Preacher", "The Lost Symbol"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Life Is Beautiful", "Heroes", "Sabotage", "Beowulf & Grendel"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Elephant White", "Around the World in 80 Days", "Azhagai Irukkirai Bayamai Irukkirathu", "The Ugly Truth"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Mohra", "The United States of Leland", "Dynamo", "The Mexican"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Jewel of the Sahara", "Housefull", "Grindhouse", "Since You've Been Gone"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Death Race 2000", "The Expendables", "Midnight Run", "Chasing Mavericks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["'Salem's Lot", "Lara Croft Tomb Raider: The Cradle of Life", "Laffapalooza! #1", "Celebrating AFI"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Butterfly on a Wheel", "Ek Rishtaa: The Bond of Love", "Saugandh", "The Forbidden Kingdom"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Playing for Keeps", "Get Smart", "Guardians of the Galaxy", "12 Monkeys"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["The Garden of Last Days", "Family Bond", "Critters 3", "Fast Times at Ridgemont High"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Infamous", "Phir Hera Pheri", "Olympus Has Fallen", "Ainthu Ainthu Ainthu"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Mad City", "The Witches", "Gamer", "Happy Gilmore"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Poove Unakkaga", "Who Am I?", "Tomorrow Never Dies", "Happy Feet"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Temptation: Confessions of a Marriage Counselor", "Scavenger Hunt", "Like Stars on Earth", "Attila"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["How to Train Your Dragon 2", "The Avengers: Age of Ultron", "Lincoln's Gettysburg Address", "Speed 2: Cruise Control"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Pee-wee's Big Adventure", "That Darn Cat!", "Erotibot", "Reign of Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Raising Arizona", "Mr Deeds", "Gift of the Night Fury", "Beavis and Butt-head Do America"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["True Grit", "How to Train Your Dragon 3", "Matchstick Men", "Shootout at Wadala"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Finders Keepers", "300", "Chinese Coffee", "The Bourne Identity"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Law Abiding Citizen", "Going Overboard", "Kevin Hart: Let Me Explain", "Air America"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Ace Ventura: Pet Detective", "Safe Haven", "The Bourne Ultimatum", "Movie 43"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["The Pleasure Garden", "All the Pretty Horses", "Gods of Egypt", "The Scorpion King"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["I Confess", "A Fistful of Dollars", "50 First Dates", "The Phantom of the Opera"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["The Fighter", "Batman & Robin", "Legend of the Lost", "Coriolanus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Fast Food", "Pirates of the Caribbean: On Stranger Tides", "In Love and War", "Casino"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["New York Stories", "The Bounty Hunter", "North by Northwest", "North by Northwest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["The Expendables 2", "Tales of the Black Freighter", "The Thunderstorm", "Lara Croft: Tomb Raider"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Lars and the Real Girl", "Nim's Island", "The Fast and the Furious", "Half Nelson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["The Front", "One More Kiss", "The Kid", "Bollywood Dreams"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Mrs. Brown", "Police Story 4: First Strike", "Singles", "Ghost Rider: Spirit of Vengeance"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Sabrina", "RocknRolla", "Margaret", "Murder in the First"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Endless Love", "Horton Hears a Who!", "Dear Frankie", "Royal Rumble"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Pazhani", "Harrison's Flowers", "Rocky Balboa", "Black Snake Moan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Snake Eyes", "Hey Ram", "Shooters", "Mann"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Dracula 2000", "FernGully: The Last Rainforest", "Diner", "The Campaign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["How the Grinch Stole Christmas!", "Madea's Class Reunion", "How to Train Your Dragon", "The Devil's Advocate"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Fried Green Tomatoes", "The Robot Boy", "The Game of Their Lives", "Loverboy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["The Cherry Orchard", "The Sword in the Stone", "Stop! Or My Mom Will Shoot", "It's Father's Fault"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Abbot Hai Teng of Shaolin", "S.W.A.T.", "Laughing Out Loud: America's Funniest Comedians", "Timeline"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Thunder Run", "Kujiratori", "The Haunted Mansion", "Kalifornia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Gerard Butler?", "answers": ["Firelight", "Legend of the Boneknapper Dragon", "Devil in a Blue Dress", "Kung Fu Panda 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Mission: Impossible II", "Lahu Ke Do Rang", "Star Wars Episode III: Revenge of the Sith", "Everybody's Fine"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Say Anything...", "Traveller", "The Good Shepherd", "Once Upon a Time in China"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Garv", "Meet the Parents", "That Darn Cat!", "No Entry"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Analyze This", "Deadfall", "Mad Max", "Khamoshi: The Musical"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Lawaaris", "Kannukkul Nilavu", "Any Which Way You Can", "The Family"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Half Nelson", "Midnight Run", "Shark Tale", "Mary Reilly"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Inside Man", "Men of Honor", "Empire State", "Hotel Transylvania"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Lahu Ke Do Rang", "The Skeleton Dance", "Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man's Chest", "The Fan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Getaway", "Manhattan Murder Mystery", "The King of Comedy", "Tyler Perry's Madea's Family Reunion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Bewitched", "A Bronx Tale", "Azhagiya Tamil Magan", "Pollyanna"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["How to Train Your Dragon 3", "Taxi Driver", "Pilot Season", "The Farmer's Wife"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Grudge Match", "Once Upon a Time in China", "Superstar", "Midnight in Paris"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Zandalee", "Once Upon a Time in America", "Sangram", "Flowers and Trees"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Up in the Air", "The Godfather Saga", "American Hustle", "Arthur and the Vengeance of Maltazard"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Chandni Chowk to China", "Raging Bull", "Anchorman 2: The Legend Continues", "Coming to America"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Lawaaris", "Zookeeper", "Being Flynn", "Xtreme City"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Hide and Seek", "Peekay", "Footloose", "Attack Force Z"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["The Mission", "The Comancheros", "Loverboy", "The Lords of Flatbush"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["The Million Dollar Hotel", "The Sea Chase", "Amblin", "Limitless"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["The American", "Eddie Presley", "The Untouchables", "Chalte Chalte"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["The Dark Tower", "Bad Boys", "Mean Streets", "The United States of Leland"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Jakob the Liar", "Kadhalukku Mariyadhai", "Casino", "The Mexican"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Sarfarosh", "Graveyard Shift", "Righteous Kill", "Biwi No.1"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Return of the Killer Tomatoes", "The Defender", "The Zero Theorem", "Jackie Brown"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Fu gui fu yun", "Last Vegas", "The Office Party", "Don 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Sharaabi", "Great Expectations", "Edge of Darkness", "From Paris with Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["The Greatest Story Ever Told", "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", "Running with Scissors", "Brazil"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["WWE: King of the Ring 2002", "Clerks II", "Husbands and Wives", "Machete"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Who Do I Gotta Kill?", "Cape Fear", "Austin Powers: International Man of Mystery", "Stay"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["My Big Fat Greek Wedding", "Diljale", "The Deer Hunter", "Cyborg 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Baabul", "Daddy", "Battle in Seattle", "Heat"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Rhinestone", "Menace II Society", "Awakenings", "Oldboy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Frankenstein", "Kill Bill: Vol. 3", "North by Northwest", "WWE Tagged Classics 2003: Royal Rumble"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["A Mighty Heart", "Edison", "Stardust", "The Accidental Spy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["The Fighter", "Killing Season", "The Truman Show", "Speed"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Saathiya", "Little Fockers", "Twister", "The Dead Pool"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["The Dark Knight Rises", "Angel Heart", "Logan's Run", "Out of the Furnace"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Kyon Ki", "Toy Story 3", "Stolen", "Killer Elite"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Red Lights", "Good Time Gang", "Eight Crazy Nights", "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Naseeb", "The Score", "Braveheart", "No Entry"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["All in the Family", "The Godfather Part II", "From Dusk till Dawn", "Badlanders"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Haywire", "The Big Wedding", "Do the Right Thing", "Ocean's Twelve"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["New Year's Eve", "Ram Jaane", "Fail Safe", "Alice in Wonderland"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Stone", "Get Carter", "The Lady Vanishes", "Spider-Plant Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["The Mexican", "Beyond Borders", "Half Nelson", "Flawless"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Boys", "The Goonies", "Meet the Fockers", "Baadshah"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["The Story of Yanagawa's Canals", "It's Father's Fault", "1900", "Collateral Damage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Rocky II", "Shooters", "Sleepers", "Flowers and Trees"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Imagine", "Van Helsing", "Under Suspicion", "Silver Linings Playbook"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["The Five-Year Engagement", "Psycho", "The Dark Half", "Ronin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Robert De Niro?", "answers": ["Machine Gun Preacher", "Goodfellas", "Mela", "Kick-Ass"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Who Am I?", "Deuce Bigalow: European Gigolo", "The Vanishing", "Top Gun"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["The Longest Yard", "Rush Hour 3", "Northern Lights", "Friends with Money"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Tokyo Species", "Love Today", "The Net", "Bucky Larson: Born to Be a Star"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["The Paradine Case", "Billy Madison", "Nepali", "Cars"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Rio Grande", "Click", "Zakhm", "Night at the Museum"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Aitraaz", "Patiala House", "Couch", "The Fifth Element"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["I Am Legend", "The Mummy - Tomb of the Dragon Emperor", "Striking Distance", "Hotel Transylvania"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Zookeeper", "The Searchers", "The Final Cut", "Kuch Kuch Hota Hai"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Bedtime Stories", "Sweet and Lowdown", "Jeet", "Mr. & Mrs. Smith"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["The Fever", "Bullets Over Broadway", "Shakes the Clown", "Snatch"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Grown Ups", "Blood Work", "Fort Apache", "Carrie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Blossoms & Blood", "Lincoln's Gettysburg Address", "The Undefeated", "Gerry"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Ocean Heaven", "One Fine Day", "Swordsman II", "The Wedding Singer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King", "Alice in Wonderland", "50 First Dates", "Frankenweenie (1984)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["The Medallion", "Beowulf", "Zakhm", "The House Bunny"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Celebration of Gospel: Taking You Higher", "Just Go With It", "Ishq", "The Weekend"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["When Corruption Was King", "The Legend of Cain", "Mixed Nuts", "Solaris"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Who Do I Gotta Kill?", "Phantoms", "Reign Over Me", "Qayamat: City Under Threat"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Dalai Lama Renaissance", "Main Aur Mrs Khanna", "Semi-Pro", "The Animal"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Brannigan", "Funny People", "End of the Line", "Misery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Confessions of a Teenage Drama Queen", "Holi", "Priyamudan", "Raw Deal"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Little Nicky", "The Rundown", "Every Which Way but Loose", "Gigli"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["City Hall", "A League of Their Own", "Bewafaa", "Blended"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Rosewater", "Going Overboard", "Holi", "Hamlet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Mr Deeds", "Nine Months", "Extraordinary Measures", "Miss Congeniality"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Top Gun 2", "The Adjustment Bureau", "Hancock", "Happy Gilmore"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Paul Blart: Mall Cop", "The Talented Mr. Ripley", "Kicking & Screaming", "The Lords of Flatbush"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Two Weeks Notice", "Arabian Nights", "Wake of the Red Witch", "Grown Ups 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Dead Again", "Dickie Roberts: Former Child Star", "Rocky", "Old Dogs"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Spanglish", "Big Jake", "The Undefeated", "Money for Nothing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Punch-Drunk Love", "Mr. Dough and the Egg Princess", "The Jackal", "Kekk\u00f4 Kamen: Royale"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Sesame Street: Singing with the Stars", "Porco Rosso", "Starter for 10", "Tim Janis: Beautiful America"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["GOTTI: In The Shadow Of My Father", "Youth", "That's My Boy", "Main Aur Mrs Khanna"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Muniyandi Vilangial Moonramandu", "Captain Corelli's Mandolin", "Valet Guys", "Legend of the Lost"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Confessions of a Dangerous Mind", "Gamer", "Coneheads", "Logan's Run"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Anger Management", "Cat's Eye", "8mm", "Isi Ka Naam Zindagi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Jaane Tu Ya Jaane Na", "World's Greatest Dad", "Airheads", "Deadfall"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["American Breakdown", "The Benchwarmers", "Driven", "The Rum Diary"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Kung Fu Panda: Secrets of the Masters", "Rounders 2", "Big Daddy", "Jhoom Barabar Jhoom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["The Bourne Supremacy", "The Waterboy", "Three Kings", "Winter Passing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Saving Face", "Stuff", "Bulletproof", "Curdled"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Johnny Suede", "Jack & Jill", "The Marriage Counselor", "Flawless"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Eight Crazy Nights", "Coimbatore Mappillai", "Maybe Baby", "The Paradine Case"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["You Don't Mess with the Zohan", "Star Wars Episode IV: A New Hope", "Revolution", "Frost/Nixon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Adam Sandler?", "answers": ["Stalk of the Celery Monster", "James Michener's Dynasty", "I Now Pronounce You Chuck and Larry", "Lucky Number Slevin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Edward Scissorhands", "Phantoms", "The Romantics", "Golmaal Returns"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Armageddon", "The Big Boss", "Besharam", "Goodbye Lover"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Half Nelson", "Hum Tumhare Hain Sanam", "A Man Apart", "Joseph: King of Dreams"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Knight and Day", "Anna Nicole Smith: Exposed", "Stolen Summer", "Time Changer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Live by Night", "Meet the Parents", "Shadow of a Doubt", "Unidentified"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["The Perfect Storm", "The 6th Day", "Argo", "Death Race 2000"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Gigli", "Cat's Eye", "Ed Wood", "Get the Gringo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Never Say Never Again", "200 Cigarettes", "Good Time Gang", "Half Nelson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["The Hobbit: There and Back Again", "Apocalypse Now", "Daddy", "Elysium"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Ronin", "Jaanwar", "Daddy and Them", "Poltergeist"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["The Good Girl", "Unbecoming Age", "Reindeer Games", "Rosewater"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Kevin Hart: I'm a Grown Little Man", "The Foot Shooting Party", "Chasing Amy", "Camp Cucamonga"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Hollywoodland", "The Mummy Returns", "My Name is Khan", "Comic Relief IV"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Lucky Number Slevin", "Happy Gilmore", "21 Jump Street", "Jay and Silent Bob Strike Back"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Maggie", "Forces of Nature", "Snakes on a Plane", "Blitz"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Dalai Lama Renaissance", "The Sum of All Fears", "Blue Valentine", "Contraband"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Cliffhanger", "Smokin' Aces", "Celeste and Jesse Forever", "Black Snake Moan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Dazed and Confused", "Say Anything...", "All in the Family", "Mystic River"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["The Happening", "Stolen", "Office Killer", "Toy Story 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Mazes and Monsters", "Baaghi: A Rebel for Love", "Shade", "Gone Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Delhi Belly", "Remember the Titans", "Kyon Ki", "Gone Baby Gone"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Reservoir Dogs", "Glory Daze", "The Eagle", "ReGeneration"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Yeh Hai Jalwa", "Daredevil", "The Manxman", "Paul"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Be Cool", "La escribana de uraba", "Catch .44", "National Geographic: Beyond the Movie: Pearl Harbor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Snatch", "Picture Perfect", "State of Play", "Love Actually"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Heart Stopper", "Vettaikkaaran", "The Town", "Reign of Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Extract", "Red Surf", "Butterfly on a Wheel", "Lawaaris"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Pearl Harbor", "Grease", "Planet of the Apes", "Wheels on Meals"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Grease", "The Object of My Affection", "Crank: High Voltage", "He's Just Not That Into You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Hansel and Gretel", "The Vanishing", "Bounce", "Adaptation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Love Love Love", "Pink Cadillac", "Surviving Christmas", "Nenjinile"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Going All the Way", "White House Down", "Race to Witch Mountain", "Khushi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Rumble in the Bronx", "The Secret Policeman's Other Ball", "Boiler Room", "Three Mississippi"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["The Medallion", "People I Know", "Stop-Loss", "Good Will Hunting"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Since You've Been Gone", "Man About Town", "Sometimes They Come Back", "Police Story 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["The Believer", "Men in Black 3", "The People Speak", "Toys"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Raju Chacha", "Twilight Zone: The Movie", "Marlowe", "Dogma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Marley & Me", "Batman vs. Superman", "The Secret Policeman's Other Ball", "The Preppie Murder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Changing Lanes", "The Country Bears", "The Coriolis Effect", "Payback"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Shakespeare in Love", "Hellfighters", "What's New Pussycat?", "Half Past Autumn"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["School Ties", "Street Smart", "1911", "Invictus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Salt 2", "K\u016bs\u014d no Sora Tobu Kikaitachi", "Clerks II", "A Tribute to John F. Kennedy from the Arts"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Striking Distance", "Wild Things", "Paycheck", "Close Encounters of the Third Kind"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["The Founding of a Republic", "To the Wonder", "Life or Something Like It", "The Landlord"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Apollo 13", "Inception", "Zandalee", "The Company Men"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Stop! Or My Mom Will Shoot", "The Third Wheel", "Shakti: The Power", "Frankenstein"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Beowulf & Grendel", "Celebrating AFI", "Jersey Girl", "Crash"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ben Affleck?", "answers": ["Qayamat: City Under Threat", "Anand", "Gridiron Gang", "Mallrats"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Payback", "Brock Lesnar: Here Comes the Pain", "Look Who's Talking Too", "The Quick and the Dead"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Make Mine Music", "I Am Legend", "What's Eating Gilbert Grape", "Man About Town"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Solitary Man", "Diner", "Firewall", "Revolutionary Road"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["What's Done in the Dark", "Catch Me If You Can", "ATL", "Shaolin Temple 3: Martial Arts of Shaolin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["The Departed", "Domestic Disturbance", "The Sugarland Express", "Angel Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["The Aviator", "Notorious", "The Running Man", "Red Dragon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["The Red Curtain Trilogy", "Bewitched", "The Company Men", "Princess Protection Program"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Kabhi Kabhie", "Charlotte's Web", "The Beach", "Confessions of a Dangerous Mind"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Dan in Real Life", "Trucks", "FernGully: The Last Rainforest", "Live by Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["K\u016bs\u014d no Sora Tobu Kikaitachi", "Havoc", "Return of the Killer Tomatoes", "Django Unchained"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["The Front", "Los Bandoleros", "The Outlaw Josey Wales", "The 11th Hour"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Hannah Montana: The Movie", "Blow Out", "Mujhse Shaadi Karogi", "Shutter Island"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["The Hudsucker Proxy", "Body of Lies", "Benny & Joon", "The Chain Reaction"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["The Basketball Diaries", "Miracle Run", "Love Actually", "Fathers' Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["The Great Gatsby", "Edge of Darkness", "Eraser", "The Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["The Animal", "Romeo + Juliet", "Snake in the Eagle's Shadow", "Mr. & Mrs. Smith"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Night at the Museum", "Titanic", "Supercross", "Surrogates"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers", "Hotel Transylvania", "Aadhi", "Sinatra"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Nenjinile", "J. Edgar", "The Year of Living Dangerously", "The Wise Little Hen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Gardener of Eden", "The Last Stand", "...And Justice for All", "Pearl Harbor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Total Eclipse", "The Mechanic", "RV", "Rubberface"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["The Topkapi Affair", "Poison Ivy", "Ninaithen Vandhai", "Stalk of the Celery Monster"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Madea's Class Reunion", "Akira", "Escape Plan", "Enemy of the State"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Red Riding Hood", "The Passion of the Christ", "Seven Years in Tibet", "The Tuxedo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Road to Perdition", "Orphan", "Clear and Present Danger", "Triplets"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["The Man in the Iron Mask", "Casper", "Grease", "Confessions of a Dangerous Mind"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Baadshah", "Gangs of New York", "Mr. & Mrs. Smith", "Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Top Gun", "Don's Plum", "Stuff", "Legend of the Boneknapper Dragon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Anchorman: The Legend of Ron Burgundy", "Chisum", "Blood Diamond", "The Coriolis Effect"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Coriolanus", "Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade", "Angela & Viril", "Celebrity"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Fort Apache", "Inception", "The Thing Called Love", "Black and White"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Critters 3", "Chal Mere Bhai", "The Wise Little Hen", "Strays"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Ek Hi Raasta", "Out of the Furnace", "Yaadon Ki Baaraat", "Kisses in the Dark"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Air America", "Brazil", "Hatya: The Murder", "Xtreme City"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Deadfall", "Chain Reaction", "Chain Reaction", "This Boy's Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["The Wolf of Wall Street", "The Merchant of Venice", "The Good Shepherd", "How the West Was Won"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["Thuppakki", "Marvin's Room", "The Local Stigmatic", "Star Wars Episode II: Attack of the Clones"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Leonardo DiCaprio?", "answers": ["London", "The Foot Shooting Party", "Thambikku Indha Ooru", "The Tuxedo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Linda Lovelace?", "answers": ["Love Is All There Is", "Wilma", "Deep Throat Part II", "Coolie"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Linda Lovelace?", "answers": ["Pyaar Kiya To Darna Kya", "Tees Maar Khan", "Linda Lovelace for President", "Rush Hour"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Anna Nicole Smith?", "answers": ["Street Fury: Envy", "Journey 3: From the Earth to the Moon", "Endrendrum Kadhal", "Baazigar"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Anna Nicole Smith?", "answers": ["The Boy in the Plastic Bubble", "Blitz", "To the Limit", "Baadshah"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Anna Nicole Smith?", "answers": ["9", "Shootout at Wadala", "The Anna Nicole Smith Story", "Star Wars Holiday Special"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Anna Nicole Smith?", "answers": ["Master Spy: The Robert Hanssen Story", "Exit Strategy", "The Naked Gun 33\u2153: The Final Insult", "Every Which Way but Loose"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Anna Nicole Smith?", "answers": ["The Adjustment Bureau", "Enemy of the State", "The Hudsucker Proxy", "Hook"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Anna Nicole Smith?", "answers": ["Family Plot", "The Frisco Kid", "Illegal Aliens", "Stardust Memories"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Anna Nicole Smith?", "answers": ["Bobby", "Anna Nicole Smith: Exposed", "Annie Hall", "Don: The Chase Begins Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Anna Nicole Smith?", "answers": ["Austin Powers: International Man of Mystery", "Miss Cast Away", "Fantasia", "The Marriage Counselor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Anna Nicole Smith?", "answers": ["Skyscraper", "8", "The Untouchables", "The Color of Money"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Total Eclipse", "Thelma & Louise", "Flight", "Fried Green Tomatoes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Moonstruck", "Sin City", "The Assassination of Jesse James by the Coward Robert Ford", "Hitch"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["12 Years a Slave", "The Mummy - Tomb of the Dragon Emperor", "Comic Relief 2007", "The Ninth Gate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["One More Kiss", "Fallen", "Kick-Ass", "The Rainmaker"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Emmtan-Magan", "Johnny Suede", "Silver Linings Playbook", "\"Dr. Wai in \"\"The Scripture with No Words\"\"\""], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Mona Lisa Smile", "Kick-Ass 2", "Star Wars Holiday Special", "Frost/Nixon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Hello Brother", "Temptation: Confessions of a Marriage Counselor", "Running with Scissors", "Phenomenon"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Devdas", "Kung Fu Panda: Secrets of the Masters", "Sweet Time Together", "Ocean's Twelve"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Pom Poko", "Curdled", "Stolen", "Sleepers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["K-19: The Widowmaker", "Everything Must Go", "Happy Feet Two", "Dumb & Dumber"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Omkara", "Snatch", "Saawariya", "The Sex and Violence Family Hour"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Moment by Moment", "Ocean's Thirteen", "Aankhen", "Dance Me to the End of Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["The Private Lives of Pippa Lee", "The Mechanic", "Gallipoli", "Rails & Ties"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["The Medallion", "8mm", "Killing Them Softly", "Hum Aapke Hain Kaun...!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Veer-Zaara", "The Long Kiss Goodnight", "The Guiding Light", "No Way Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["The Departed", "Ultimate Fights", "Once Upon a Time in Mexico", "Seval"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Babel", "Lethal Weapon 3", "Open Windows", "How to Train Your Dragon 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["World War Z", "Silsila", "Mad City", "G-Force"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Titan A.E.", "Young and Innocent", "Ocean's Eleven", "Deconstructing Harry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["MegaMind", "Dil Kya Kare", "The Survivors", "Saboteur"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Fantasia", "Needful Things", "Seven", "The Beaver"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Johnny English", "No Place to Hide", "Red Riding Hood", "The Normal Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Circle of Iron", "Toy Story", "Hook", "Cutting Class"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Spy Game", "Hellfighters", "Pink Cadillac", "Heat"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Kalifornia", "Vijaypath", "Bachelor Party", "Redemption"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Clerks II", "The Mexican", "Minority Report: Bonus Material", "Song of the South"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["A Mighty Heart", "The Jayne Mansfield Story", "The Wicker Man", "Antwone Fisher"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["A River Runs Through It", "Soul Plane", "Interiors", "Scent of a Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["The Favor", "The Notebook", "Chasing Amy", "The Frozen Ground"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Transporter 3", "Sora Iro no Tane", "The Tree of Life", "High Plains Drifter"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Minions", "Arrietty", "Burn After Reading", "D\u00e9j\u00e0 Vu"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Pale Rider", "We Owe It to Our Children", "Across the Tracks", "After Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Drowning Mona", "Dil To Pagal Hai", "Black", "The Devil's Own"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["The Mosquito Coast", "Solaris", "The Pawnbroker", "Seven Years in Tibet"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Scarecrow", "Legends of the Fall", "Speed", "Phil Spector"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Friday the 13th", "How to Swim", "Josh", "Moneyball"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Manhattan Murder Mystery", "Too Young to Die?", "28 Days", "Live Free or Die Hard"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Cool World", "Ultimate Fights", "That's My Boy", "A Nightmare on Elm Street"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["The Dark Side of the Sun", "Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom", "Invincible", "The Secret Life of Bees"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["12 Monkeys", "The Work of Director Michel Gondry", "...And Justice for All", "American Breakdown"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull", "Without Evidence", "True Romance", "Champagne"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Hoshi o Katta Hi", "Valley Girl", "Inglourious Basterds", "Transformers: Age of Extinction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Liar Liar", "Creepshow", "The Chain Reaction", "Fight Club"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Gundaraj", "The Counselor", "G-Force", "Kaze Tachinu"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["WWE: WrestleMania 27: Vol. 1", "The Curious Case of Benjamin Button", "Dulhan Hum Le Jayenge", "Lethal Weapon 4"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Troy", "Bulletproof", "Happy New Year", "Michael Clayton"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Mr. & Mrs. Smith", "Kung Fu Cult Master", "Shaolin Temple", "War Horse"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["The Shawshank Redemption", "Mallrats", "Red River", "Sinbad: Legend of the Seven Seas"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Angel Heart", "The Loved One", "Confessions of a Dangerous Mind", "Secret Window"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Interview with the Vampire: The Vampire Chronicles", "One More Kiss", "We Are One: The Obama Inaugural Celebration at the Lincoln Memorial", "In the Land of Blood and Honey"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Brad Pitt?", "answers": ["Stand by Me", "Meet Joe Black", "Red Riding Hood", "Playing by Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Joe Versus the Volcano", "Mr. Dough and the Egg Princess", "The Gauntlet", "Capone"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Tyler Perry's Madea's Family Reunion", "Fight Club", "The Sex and Violence Family Hour", "Hang 'Em High"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Hide and Seek", "Power", "Sudden Impact", "The Woodsman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Unbroken", "Jaanemann", "Bird", "Madea Goes to Jail"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["RED", "Letters from Iwo Jima", "The Third Wheel", "Stone Cold Steve Austin: The Bottom Line on the Most Popular Superstar of All Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["The Rookie", "The Marriage Counselor", "Rubberface", "Carriage Ghost"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Trouble with the Curve", "The Oxford Murders", "Wanderlust", "Dead Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["American Hustle", "Mad City", "Where Eagles Dare", "Lethal Weapon 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Thunderbolt and Lightfoot", "Merry Mirthquakes", "Oliver Twist", "Too Late for Divorce"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Contagion", "Mystic River", "Kuch Kuch Hota Hai", "Deewane"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Every Which Way but Loose", "LOL: Laughing Out Loud", "Used Guys", "Author! Author!"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Kurbaan", "Full Frontal", "Any Which Way You Can", "Apocalypse Now Redux"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Cellular", "Koro no Daisanpo", "A Guide to Recognizing Your Saints", "Two Mules for Sister Sara"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["16 Blocks", "Spy Kids", "Joe Versus the Volcano", "Paint Your Wagon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Unforgiven", "Maid's Room: Return of the Master", "Chasing Mavericks", "Insomnia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Awakenings", "Cupid & Cate", "The Punisher", "Coogan's Bluff"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Two If by Sea", "The Enforcer", "Brannigan", "A Century of Black Cinema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Escape from Alcatraz", "The Haunted Mansion", "The Fearless Hyena", "The War"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["D-Tox", "Blood Work", "Battle in Seattle", "The Third Wheel"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["A Perfect World", "Thick as Thieves", "Two Weeks Notice", "Wizards of Waverly Place: The Movie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Walking Tall", "When You're Strange", "Vishnu", "Play Misty for Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Grown Ups 2", "Changeling", "Why Did I Get Married", "The Astronaut's Wife"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Pale Rider", "Terminator 5", "Red Riding Hood", "Oldboy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["The Dark Side of the Sun", "Kelly's Heroes", "The Place Beyond the Pines", "Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man's Chest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Beetlejuice", "Anger Management", "Flubber", "Heartbreak Ridge"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["High Plains Drifter", "Forces of Nature", "Police Story 4: First Strike", "The American Can"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["The Lovely Bones", "Tightrope", "Gangs of New York", "Radio Days"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Gangaajal", "Frankenweenie", "Red Sonja", "Firefox"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["xXx", "Trucks", "Bringing Out the Dead", "Bronco Billy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["The Appointment", "In the Face of Demolition", "Squirrels to the Nuts", "The Bridges of Madison County"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Batman", "Into the Woods", "For a Few Dollars More", "Dragon Lord"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Dirty Harry", "Going All the Way", "Los Bandoleros", "Born to Defence"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["True Crime", "From Dusk till Dawn", "The Karate Kid", "MegaMind"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Planet 51", "Knowing", "The Dark Side of the Sun", "Space Cowboys"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Joe Kidd", "Escape to Victory", "Boobie", "Waqt: The Race Against Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["The Assassination of Jesse James by the Coward Robert Ford", "Surrogates", "Itsy Bitsy Spider", "The Eiger Sanction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Poltergeist", "Any Given Sunday", "In the Line of Fire", "The Kid & I"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["The Searchers", "WWE: WrestleMania 27: Vol. 1", "A Fistful of Dollars", "Mad Max"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Four Weddings and a Funeral", "Two Bits", "Invictus", "To Rome with Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Magnum Force", "Blood Diamond", "The Dark Side of the Sun", "Phir Bhi Dil Hai Hindustani"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Bbuddah... Hoga Terra Baap", "Murder by Numbers", "Million Dollar Baby", "Kekk\u00f4 Kamen: Royale"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["The Master", "The Hurricane", "J. Edgar", "Billu Barber"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Trapped", "Hereafter", "The Searchers", "Love Potion No. 9"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["The Beguiled", "Dick Tracy", "Used Cars", "Dying Young"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["The Substitute", "London 2012 Olympic Opening Ceremony: Isles of Wonder", "The Outlaw Josey Wales", "Extraordinary Measures"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["The Dead Pool", "All in the Family", "Ciudad", "Apocalypse Now"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Going Overboard", "Khuda Gawah", "Absolute Power", "Moonrise Kingdom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Whatever Works", "Cat's Eye", "Flags of Our Fathers", "The Night Listener"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Clint Eastwood?", "answers": ["Gran Torino", "Der Fuehrer's Face", "Pom Poko", "Mrs. Soffel"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["A Match Made by God", "Lahu Ke Do Rang", "Sleepover", "Live by Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Talaash: The Hunt Begins...", "Balto", "Dabangg", "Brubaker"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Aarzoo", "The Legend of Drunken Master", "MegaMind", "Casper"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Blue", "Absolute Power", "One Crazy Summer", "Magnolia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Bananas", "Battle in Seattle", "Barood", "Without Limits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["You Don't Know Jack", "The Incredibles", "Young and Innocent", "Rowdy Rathore"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Punchline", "Rounders", "Grown Ups 2", "Joker"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Saugandh", "The War", "Rang De Basanti", "Hitting It Hard"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["OMG \u2013 Oh My God!", "The Naked Gun 33\u2153: The Final Insult", "Chasing Amy", "Rocky II"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Jaanemann", "Anand", "Ricky Stanicky", "Bad Lieutenant: Port of Call New Orleans"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Housefull", "Abbot Hai Teng of Shaolin", "The Million Dollar Hotel", "When Corruption Was King"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["The Castle of Cagliostro", "Dhadkan", "Playing for Keeps", "The Maiden Heist"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Vanilla Sky", "Conan the Destroyer", "Rio Lobo", "Heyy Babyy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["How to Train Your Dragon 2", "Marvin's Room", "Patiala House", "It Could Happen to You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Total Eclipse", "Hum Tumhare Hain Sanam", "Sangharsh", "Everyone Says I Love You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Shakes the Clown", "Tashan", "James and the Giant Peach", "Saludos Amigos"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["The Bowling Ball", "Tees Maar Khan", "Green Zone", "Raakh"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["War Horse", "Khatta Meetha", "A Man Apart", "Tremors"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["A River Runs Through It", "The Sorcerer's Apprentice", "The Waterboy", "Hatya: The Murder"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Circle of Iron", "Fantasia", "Phir Hera Pheri", "Dumbo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Into the Woods", "Wake of the Red Witch", "Mujhse Shaadi Karogi", "Bambi"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Rumble Fish", "Humko Deewana Kar Gaye", "Blue Valentine", "To Rome with Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Khiladi", "I Love Trouble", "The High and the Mighty", "Shahjahan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Fun and Fancy Free", "1408", "Special 26", "Ion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial", "The Whole Nine Yards", "Bird on a Wire", "Khiladi 786"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Like Stars on Earth", "35 and Ticking", "Johnny English Reborn", "Once Upon a Time Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Time Changer", "In the Bag", "De Dana Dan", "Philadelphia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Fight Club", "Tyler Perry's Laugh to Keep from Crying", "Righteous Kill", "Bhool Bhulaiyaa"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Fallen", "Boss", "Looking for Richard", "The Family That Preys"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Scarecrow", "Blue Valentine", "Dosti: Friends Forever", "Ainthu Ainthu Ainthu"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Raakh", "Jodhaa Akbar", "The Office Party", "Bewafaa"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Rasigan", "Aitraaz", "Short Fuse", "Mela"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["World War Z", "Ek Rishtaa: The Bond of Love", "The Prince of Egypt", "A Man Apart"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Bedtime Stories", "Journey 2: The Mysterious Island", "Mohra", "Black Snake Moan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Vishnu", "The Ring", "Intolerable Cruelty", "Action Replayy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Eraser", "The Grifters", "Scary Movie", "Chandni Chowk to China"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Doom", "Abbot Hai Teng of Shaolin", "Last Man Standing", "Gabbar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Raakh", "Star Wars Episode V: The Empire Strikes Back", "Singh Is Kinng", "The Other Guys"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Sunny Leone Loves HD Porn", "Frankenweenie", "Pistol", "The Expendables 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Thunderbolt", "Jaanwar", "The Hobbit: There and Back Again", "The Adventures of Tintin: The Secret of the Unicorn"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Sainik", "Mission: Impossible \u2013 Ghost Protocol", "Ace Ventura: When Nature Calls", "Bananas"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["The Panic in Needle Park", "Lara Croft: Tomb Raider", "Namastey London", "Gravity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Grindhouse", "Think Like A Man", "Madea's Big Happy Family", "Housefull 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Kambakth Ishq", "Madhurey", "Joe Versus the Volcano", "The Lone Ranger"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Welcome", "Blended", "Brock Lesnar: Here Comes the Pain", "Hudson Hawk"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Peggy Sue Got Married", "Andaaz", "License to Wed", "Gorgeous"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["American Breakdown", "The Outsiders", "Khiladiyon Ka Khiladi", "Basic"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Hell's Kitchen", "Hoshi o Katta Hi", "Funny People", "Waqt: The Race Against Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Magnum Force", "Deadfall", "Ajnabee", "The New Legend Of Shaolin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Desi Boyz", "Fight Club", "Kanden Kadhalai", "GOTTI: In The Shadow Of My Father"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Akshay Kumar?", "answers": ["Thank You", "1911", "Blackmail", "Money for Nothing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Apollo 13", "The Firm", "The Trouble with Harry", "Anchorman 2: The Legend Continues"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Meet the Fockers", "Dead on Time", "Over the Hedge", "Dragon Lord"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Twin Dragons", "Aadhi", "Foxcatcher", "Ferdinand the Bull"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["The Pelican Brief", "Melinda and Melinda", "Stalk of the Celery Monster", "Jerry Maguire"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Angela & Viril", "Seeking a Friend for the End of the World", "Zookeeper", "School Ties"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Sangharsh", "The Majestic", "American Breakdown", "Angels in America"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Trespass", "Shooter", "Little Miss Sunshine", "Winnie the Pooh and the Blustery Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Poison Ivy", "Looking for Richard", "Madhosh", "Dinner for Schmucks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Oscar", "Best of Raw: Vol. 1", "Mizugumo Monmon", "Curly Sue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Avenging Angelo", "Land of the Lost", "Dan in Real Life", "The Polar Express"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["MegaMind", "The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King", "Hammy's Boomerang Adventure", "The Numbers Station"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Madea's Class Reunion", "The Ninth Gate", "The Survivors", "Hope Springs"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Charlotte's Web", "Get Smart", "Once Upon a Time in China", "A Guide to Recognizing Your Saints"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["The Rundown", "The Shootist", "The Iceman Tapes: Conversations with a Killer", "The Incredible Burt Wonderstone"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Hellfighters", "Stories USA", "Sleeper", "Fireflies in the Garden"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Donnie Brasco", "Date Night", "Mr. Dough and the Egg Princess", "Rounders 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Abraham Lincoln: Vampire Hunter", "Boss", "The Man Who Knew Too Much", "We Are One: The Obama Inaugural Celebration at the Lincoln Memorial"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Kuruvi", "Besharam", "Mr. Tadano's Secret Mission: From Japan with Love", "Sleepover"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Night Skies", "Nothing Too Good for a Cowboy", "Love Birds in Bondage", "Anchorman: The Legend of Ron Burgundy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Closer", "Crossing Over", "Silver Linings Playbook", "Bruce Almighty"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Conan the Destroyer", "Kiki's Delivery Service", "Despicable Me 2", "Moment by Moment"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Only God Forgives", "Evan Almighty", "Fallen", "Ishq"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Partner", "Despicable Me", "Once Upon a Time in China", "Hum Saath-Saath Hain: We Stand United"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Michael", "The 40-Year-Old Virgin", "Megamind: The Button of Doom", "What's Eating Gilbert Grape"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Horton Hears a Who!", "First Blood", "Baghban", "Domestic Disturbance"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Fun and Fancy Free", "Mission: Impossible II", "Suits", "Saludos Amigos"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Steve Carell?", "answers": ["Bewitched", "Kekk\u00f4 Kamen: Premium", "Jeet", "My Dog Skip"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Daddy and Them", "The Taking of Pelham 123", "The Preppie Murder", "The Slaughter Rule"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Limitless", "Dirty Harry", "Wrestling Ernest Hemingway", "Ocean Heaven"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["The New Legend Of Shaolin", "Little Miss Sunshine", "Marvin's Room", "Divine Secrets of the Ya-Ya Sisterhood"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Collateral Damage", "The Blind Side", "Ocean Heaven", "Lawaaris"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Don: The Chase Begins Again", "Smokin' Aces", "Who Do I Gotta Kill?", "Angela & Viril"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Miss Congeniality 2: Armed and Fabulous", "From Hell", "Something Evil", "My Best Friend's Birthday"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Boys", "28 Days", "Red Heat", "Surrogates"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Sarkar", "How to Train Your Dragon 2", "The Bumblebee Flies Anyway", "Our Father"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["The Dark Knight Rises", "Gun Shy", "Kick-Ass 2", "I Love You Phillip Morris"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["The Searchers", "Student of the Year", "Practical Magic", "Pet Sematary"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Juvies", "Celebrity News Reels: Hollywood's Most Infamous Couples and Ugliest Breakups", "The Portrait of a Lady", "The Net"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Dear Frankie", "Rudderless", "All About Steve", "Titanic"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["While You Were Sleeping", "Last Action Hero", "Assassins", "The Peacemaker"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["The Mask", "Nepali", "Celeste and Jesse Forever", "Love Potion No. 9"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Avenging Angelo", "Forces of Nature", "Shooter", "Princess Mononoke"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Two Weeks Notice", "Ed Wood", "The Secret Policeman's Other Ball", "Memoirs of a Geisha"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Die Hard", "In Love and War", "Husbands and Wives", "Tightrope"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Wanderlust", "Cahill U.S. Marshal", "Paa", "When the Party's Over"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Desi Boyz", "The Marriage Counselor", "Loverboy", "The Wedding Singer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Attila", "Revolution", "Gravity", "Race to Witch Mountain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Bounce", "The One", "Speed", "The Birds"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["The Heat", "Dead Again", "The Air I Breathe", "Johnny Suede"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Boys on the Side", "Crank", "Hope Floats", "The Night Listener"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Speed 2: Cruise Control", "Bean", "Invictus", "Day Zero"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Don's Plum", "The Thing Called Love", "Hannah and Her Sisters", "Gossip with the Girls"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Murder by Numbers", "The Bourne Identity", "Vanilla Sky", "My Least Favorite Career"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Green Street", "Bangkok Dangerous", "Two Mules for Sister Sara", "Infamous"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Sangram", "Men in Black II", "Hercules in New York", "Hangmen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Untitled Miami Athletes Project", "Maine Pyar Kiya", "Fire on the Amazon", "Moment by Moment"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Braveheart: Bonus Material", "Miss Congeniality", "Island of Fire", "Righteous Kill"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["The Paradine Case", "Fist of Fury", "Trespasses", "All the Right Moves"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["3 Idiots", "Making Sandwiches", "Die Hard", "Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["The Comancheros", "Brubaker", "The Passion of the Christ", "Premonition"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Who Shot Patakango?", "Swordfish", "12 Monkeys", "Nothing Too Good for a Cowboy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", "The Good Shepherd", "Nick of Time", "Demolition Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Ladder 49", "Grease", "Pari", "The Proposal"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["The Warlords", "Shakespeare in Love", "Minions", "Fool's Gold"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Found a Groom", "Antz", "Two If by Sea", "Hancock 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Moneyball", "The Lake House", "Tango & Cash", "Phantoms"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["The Langoliers", "Kicking & Screaming", "The Good Shepherd", "A Time to Kill"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Once Upon a Time in China II", "The Prince of Egypt", "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory", "The King of Comedy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["The Wolf of Wall Street", "Aarzoo", "Crash", "Rumor Has It\u2026"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["A Perfect World", "Yaarana", "Grown Ups", "The Vanishing"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sandra Bullock?", "answers": ["Fifty Shades of Blue", "Lock Up", "Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close", "The Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["The Samaritan", "Room 10", "Valkyrie", "The Coriolis Effect"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Dance Me to the End of Love", "Losin' It", "Sainik", "Ghosts of Mars"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Pulp Fiction", "12 Monkeys", "Revenge for Jolly!", "Super"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["The Company Men", "Conan the Barbarian", "Four Rooms", "Bad Lieutenant: Port of Call New Orleans"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Boobie", "America's Sweethearts", "Reservoir Dogs", "Office Space"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Fifty Shades of Blue", "The United States of Leland", "Stop-Loss", "Sukiyaki Western Django"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Stand by Me", "Taking Lives", "Kill Bill Volume 1", "The Faculty"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Vertigo", "Something Evil", "The Final Cut", "Little Nicky"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["The Portrait of a Lady", "The Machine", "Two Weeks Notice", "Natural Born Killers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Shout", "The Girl Who Stares", "Death Proof", "The 39 Steps"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Thinner", "X-Men: First Class", "Curdled", "Swades"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["True Romance", "Flubber", "Sweet Time Together", "The Work of Director Michel Gondry"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Iron Monkey", "Witness", "The Sons of Katie Elder", "For Queen and Country"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Christmas in Connecticut", "Terminator 2: Judgment Day", "Phenomenon", "Scenes from Django Unchained - UK Winner"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["The Faculty", "Under Suspicion", "Inglourious Basterds", "Once Upon a Time in China III"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["American Sniper", "Kill Bill: Vol. 3", "Fantasia", "Edward Scissorhands"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Echelon", "Winter's Tale", "Desperado", "1408"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Bhoothnath", "We the Peeples", "Adalat", "Eddie Presley"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Planet Terror", "Saudagar", "Empire of the Sun", "The Fan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["The Karate Kid 2", "Michael Clayton", "Sin City", "Gangs of New York"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["1911", "My Best Friend's Birthday", "Taking Lives", "Mississippi Masala"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Grindhouse", "Delhi Belly", "Soul Plane", "Raising Arizona"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Good Time Gang", "The Man Without a Face", "Django Unchained", "Solaris"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["From Dusk till Dawn", "Dolphin Tale", "Rang De Basanti", "Miss Congeniality 2: Armed and Fabulous"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["To the Limit", "The Score", "Destiny Turns on the Radio", "Only God Forgives"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Jackie Brown", "I Heart Huckabees", "Romeo + Juliet", "Fearless"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Kelly's Heroes", "Badlanders", "Wrestling with Angels: Playwright Tony Kushner", "Mission: Impossible II"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Hannah Montana & Miley Cyrus: Best of Both Worlds Concert", "'Salem's Lot", "Kill Bill Volume 2", "Kiki's Delivery Service"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["From Dusk Till Dawn 2: Texas Blood Money", "Turn It Up", "Mean Machine", "The Score"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Kisses in the Dark", "Akele Hum Akele Tum", "Sometimes They Come Back... Again", "Jawani Zindabad"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Love Birds in Bondage", "Sometimes They Come Back", "Any Which Way You Can", "Psycho"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Quentin Tarantino?", "answers": ["Endless Love", "Somebody to Love", "Never Say Never Again", "Firestarter"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["A Man Apart", "Into the Woods", "Behind the Candelabra", "The Great Debaters"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["The Departed", "Namastey London", "The Lost World: Jurassic Park", "People I Know"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["On Your Mark", "The Haunted Mansion", "Batman Forever", "Dogma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["The Beaver", "Happy Feet Two", "Besharam", "She's So Lovely"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Ride Along", "Saving Private Ryan", "Naked in New York", "The Devil's Own"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Suhaag", "EuroTrip", "The Lodger: A Story of the London Fog", "Mission: Impossible 5"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Contagion", "How the West Was Won", "Chaos", "Stuff"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Syriana", "Les Passages", "Mei and the Kittenbus", "Gair"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Veer", "Street Smart", "The Good Shepherd", "Rocky V"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Goodbye Lover", "Tai Chi Master", "Mr. Popper's Penguins", "True Grit"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Diner", "Titan A.E.", "The Outsiders", "Unstoppable"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Let Go", "Rounders 2", "Rumble Fish", "The Tuxedo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Dalai Lama Renaissance", "Pr\u00eat-\u00e0-Porter", "Chasing Amy", "Unity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["The Passion of the Christ", "F.I.S.T", "Signs of Life", "The Brothers Grimm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["The Talented Mr. Ripley", "The Beaver", "Original Sin", "Across the Tracks"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Spirit: Stallion of the Cimarron", "Action Replayy", "Stalk of the Celery Monster", "The Brave"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Itihaas", "Good Will Hunting", "Wanderlust", "GOTTI: In The Shadow Of My Father"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["What's New Pussycat?", "Nishabd", "In the Face of Demolition", "Geronimo: An American Legend"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["School Ties", "Valley Girl", "Sands of Iwo Jima", "Khushi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Thuppakki", "Andaz Apna Apna", "Youth", "The Bourne Supremacy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["The Da Vinci Code", "Conan the Barbarian", "Maggie", "Margaret"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["The Green Mile", "The Mighty Quinn", "Jersey Girl", "The Town"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Star Wars Episode II: Attack of the Clones", "Invictus", "Nishabd", "Dead Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Serpico", "Big Daddy", "RV", "The Bourne Ultimatum"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Confessions of a Dangerous Mind", "Gangs of New York", "The Italian Job", "Kiss the Girls"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Get the Gringo", "Suhaag", "Hellfighters", "The Informant!"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Dus", "Memoirs of a Geisha", "The Monuments Men", "Chains of Gold"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Laughing Out Loud: America's Funniest Comedians", "Office Space", "Ponyo", "Deewana Mujh Sa Nahin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Stuck on You", "The Manchurian Candidate", "The Other Guys NYPD Recruitment Video", "The Topkapi Affair"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Rio Lobo", "She's So Lovely", "Wild Wild West", "Inside Job"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["The Incredible Burt Wonderstone", "Rounders", "Golmaal Returns", "Alex Cross"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Premonition", "Finding Forrester", "Hero", "Children of the Corn IV: The Gathering"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["The Precious One", "Jingle All the Way", "The Rainmaker", "End of the Harvest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["3 Godfathers", "The Majestic", "State of Play", "Hugo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Adaptation", "Ocean's Thirteen", "Leatherheads", "Sweet Time Together"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Kung Fu Panda: Secrets of the Masters", "Courage Under Fire", "Cassandra's Dream", "The Mask"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Gerry", "Thunder Run", "Yaarana", "The Score"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Hereafter", "Heat", "Benny & Joon", "Shutter Island"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Madea's Witness Protection", "Oldboy", "American Teacher", "The Cold Light of Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Dil To Pagal Hai", "Boogie Nights", "The Bourne Identity", "One Hundred and One Dalmatians"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Hackers", "Linda Lovelace for President", "Mann", "All the Pretty Horses"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Nothing in Common", "The Dead Zone", "Who Do I Gotta Kill?", "Promised Land"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Hard Rain", "Aravaan", "We Bought a Zoo", "The Chain Reaction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Grand Canyon", "Ride Along", "The Zero Theorem", "Bedtime Stories"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Ocean's Eleven", "Born to Defence", "Batman Forever", "A Place in Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["The Legend of Bagger Vance", "The Skin Game", "The Front", "August: Osage County"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Johnny English Reborn", "Intolerable Cruelty", "Elysium", "Champagne"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Ocean's Twelve", "Everyone Says I Love You", "Every Time We Say Goodbye", "The Eagle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Dying Young", "The Adjustment Bureau", "Cold Dead Hand with Jim Carrey", "Charlie Wilson's War"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Cutting Class", "Mystic Pizza", "Little Miss Sunshine", "42"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Matt Damon?", "answers": ["Green Zone", "Casino Royale", "Rio Grande", "Play Misty for Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Bringing Out the Dead", "Cradle 2 the Grave", "Find Me Guilty", "Dirty Harry"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Invictus", "Lore", "Ghost Rider", "September"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Cinderella", "The Lodger: A Story of the London Fog", "Bulletproof", "Raising Arizona"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["True Women", "The Tree of Life", "I Can Do Bad All by Myself", "The Croods"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["The Bowling Ball", "Main Aur Mrs Khanna", "Lord of War", "Attack Force Z"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["In the Line of Fire", "The Maiden Heist", "Bangkok Dangerous", "Random Hearts"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Kick-Ass", "The Lone Ranger", "Youth", "1941"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["8mm", "Mission: Impossible", "Mean Machine", "The Son of No One"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["The Truman Show", "Psycho", "Valley Girl", "Hero"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Les Passages", "Delhi Belly", "The Good German", "The Sorcerer's Apprentice"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Winter's Tale", "Peggy Sue Got Married", "Red Dragon", "Batman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Cop Out", "Face/Off", "The Appointment", "The Big Wedding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["The Weather Man", "Toys", "8", "The Rainmaker"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Hey Ram", "G-Force", "Runaway Bride", "Badlanders"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["The Devil's Own", "Shout", "Adaptation", "While You Were Sleeping"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Left Behind", "Diner", "Love", "The Imaginarium of Dr. Parnassus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["100 Years of Comedy", "The Numbers Station", "The Frozen Ground", "Der Fuehrer's Face"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Kilroy", "Family Bond", "The Young Master", "Vampire's Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Three O'Clock High", "Deewangee", "The Rock", "Love Today"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Snake Eyes", "Something Evil", "Batman Returns", "Don's Plum"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Once Upon a Time in China", "Jack", "Last Man Standing", "Fast Times at Ridgemont High"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["National Treasure: Book of Secrets", "Virtuosity", "Elysium", "Housefull"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Day-O", "Too Young to Die?", "Moonstruck", "Lucky Numbers"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Behaving Badly", "Trespass", "Rambo: First Blood Part II", "Poove Unakkaga"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Naked in New York", "Song of the South", "Hairspray", "Grindhouse"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["The Ides of March", "Deadfall", "Thunder Run", "Untitled The Departed 2 Sequel"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["The Wicker Man", "Dil Se", "Killer Elite", "The Secrets of Jonathan Sperry"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Bad Lieutenant: Port of Call New Orleans", "My One and Only", "Fun and Fancy Free", "Couch"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Somebody to Love", "Vertigo", "Drive Angry", "Heat"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Lovesick", "Karan Arjun", "Dial M for Murder", "Next"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Leaving Las Vegas", "Udhaya", "Endrendrum Kadhal", "The Birdcage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Chalte Chalte", "Windtalkers", "Judwaa", "Nepali"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["2 Guns", "Semi-Pro", "Joe", "Rebecca"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["The Godfather", "The Maiden Heist", "Rumble Fish", "Once Bitten"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Pain & Gain", "Rebecca", "National Treasure", "Natural Born Killers"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Pitch Black", "It Could Happen to You", "Mr. & Mrs. Smith", "A Match Made by God"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Daddy and Them", "City of Angels", "Shakes the Clown", "Bol Bachchan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Seeking Justice", "Blood Work", "The Happening", "Juvies"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Con Air", "Eight Crazy Nights", "Crimes and Misdemeanors", "The Running Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Wild at Heart", "Thunder Run", "Knight and Day", "Fear"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Ghost Rider: Spirit of Vengeance", "Seval", "Deewaar", "28 Days"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["World Trade Center", "Seven Years in Tibet", "The Toxic Boy", "Pirates of the Caribbean: At World's End"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["The Game Plan", "A Place in Time", "In the Land of Blood and Honey", "Birdy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Love and Death", "Half Baked", "Full Frontal", "Knowing"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Knight and Day", "Gone in Sixty Seconds", "Scavenger Hunt", "Apocalypse Now"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Season of the Witch", "Basic", "Tim", "Loomis Fargo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Frankenweenie", "Stop! Or My Mom Will Shoot", "Matchstick Men", "Soul Men"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Short Fuse", "The Family Man", "Sky Captain and the World of Tomorrow", "The Happening"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Journey 3: From the Earth to the Moon", "The Thetan", "The 6th Day", "Stolen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Qayamat Se Qayamat Tak", "Captain Corelli's Mandolin", "The Best Thief in the World", "The Jungle Book"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicolas Cage?", "answers": ["Orphan", "Every Time We Say Goodbye", "Zandalee", "Children of the Corn IV: The Gathering"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Deep Blue Sea", "Tall in the Saddle", "Ender's Game", "It Could Happen to You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Made in America", "Three Kings", "Wake of the Red Witch", "Family Plot"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Malcolm X", "Song of the South", "Swordfish", "The Conqueror"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Frankenweenie", "Avenging Angelo", "The High and the Mighty", "Yohan: Adhyayam Ondru"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Blood Diamond", "Be Cool", "Yuvan Yuvathi", "The Alamo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["ReGeneration", "The Man Who Shot Liberty Valance", "Nick of Time", "Aarzoo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Khushi", "Small Time Crooks", "Rooster Cogburn", "Love Potion No. 9"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Bobby", "The Greatest Story Ever Told", "Naye Nagme: Vol. 2", "Mangal Pandey: The Rising"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Blow", "Angel and the Badman", "Jumanji", "She's the Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Hoshi o Katta Hi", "Stagecoach", "Nerrukku Ner", "What's New Pussycat?"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Apollo 13", "Heat", "Bachelorette", "Rio Bravo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["The Tourist", "The Longest Day", "Untitled Miami Athletes Project", "Drunken Master"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Chisum", "Pee-wee's Big Adventure", "Scarface", "JFK"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Orphan", "Eat Pray Love", "Copper Mountain", "Hellfighters"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Hatari!", "Unbecoming Age", "Tightrope", "Like Stars on Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["X-Men: First Class", "The Comancheros", "Hulchul", "The Toxic Boy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Seven Pounds", "Blue Steel", "Apt Pupil", "Don't Drink the Water"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["The 40-Year-Old Virgin", "The Sons of Katie Elder", "Biwi No.1", "Sangram"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Funny People", "The Contract", "McQ", "Killing Them Softly"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Unity", "Apt Pupil", "Rio Grande", "Air Force One"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["The Untouchables", "It's Father's Fault", "Hope Springs", "The Train Robbers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["4 the People", "Surrogates", "Cutting Class", "The War Wagon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Chocolat", "Happy Feet", "Contraband", "In Harm's Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["White Water Summer", "Circus World", "Jo Jeeta Wohi Sikandar", "The Bounty Hunter"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["The Big Trail", "Pr\u00eat-\u00e0-Porter", "The Will Smith Music Video Collection", "The Sorcerer's Apprentice"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Mela", "True Lies", "The Green Berets", "Frankie and Johnny"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Funny People", "American Breakdown", "Mangal Pandey: The Rising", "True Grit"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Hondo", "Life or Something Like It", "Top Gun", "Arena"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Sweet and Lowdown", "El Dorado", "Chicken Run", "Dulhan Hum Le Jayenge"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Thelma & Louise", "Despicable Me 2", "Legend of the Lost", "Author! Author!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Finding Neverland", "Blood Alley", "Secret Agent", "Bollywood Dreams"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Avalon", "Fort Apache", "The Legend of Bagger Vance", "The Proposal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Diner", "The Devil's Advocate", "Island in the Sky", "The Devil's Own"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Sands of Iwo Jima", "Rocky V", "Independence Day", "Rocky V"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Legend of the Boneknapper Dragon", "Sleepers", "How the West Was Won", "Rain Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Crank: High Voltage", "Alexander", "The Sea Chase", "Celebrating AFI"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Stardust Memories", "Master Spy: The Robert Hanssen Story", "She Wore a Yellow Ribbon", "Drive Angry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["The Shootist", "Partner", "Unleashed", "Being Flynn"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Mohra", "Unforgiven", "McLintock!", "The Samaritan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["The Shining", "Sachein", "Khushi", "The Undefeated"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Yohan: Adhyayam Ondru", "Lakeview Terrace", "Wanted", "Donovan's Reef"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Thunder Run", "3 Godfathers", "Captive", "No Way Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Patch Adams", "Feast of Love", "Going All the Way", "Red River"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["The Man Who Cried", "Tooth Fairy", "The Cowboys", "Braveheart: Bonus Material"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Big Jake", "Manglehorn", "Vincent", "Der Fuehrer's Face"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Drillbit Taylor", "Six Degrees of Separation", "Brannigan", "Road to Perdition"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Assassins", "Playing God", "The Horse Soldiers", "Thambikku Indha Ooru"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Child in the Night", "Under Suspicion", "The Quiet Man", "The Big Picture"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Rio Lobo", "Crossing Over", "Firelight", "Demolition Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Cabin Boy", "My Least Favorite Career", "Jay and Silent Bob Strike Back", "The Searchers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Wayne?", "answers": ["Cahill U.S. Marshal", "The Fugitive", "Rock Mafia Presents: The Big Bang", "Public Enemies"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Maria Ozawa?", "answers": ["Bandits", "The 'Burbs", "Machete Kills", "Kekk\u00f4 Kamen: Forever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Maria Ozawa?", "answers": ["A Century of Black Cinema", "Tokyo Species", "Arabian Nights", "Udhaya"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Maria Ozawa?", "answers": ["Hell's Kitchen", "Mr. Tadano's Secret Mission: From Japan with Love", "One More Kiss", "Bruce Almighty"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Maria Ozawa?", "answers": ["Christmas in Connecticut", "Actress", "The Country Bears", "The Campaign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Maria Ozawa?", "answers": ["Pretty Woman", "Bad Boys II", "One More Kiss", "Irokoishi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Maria Ozawa?", "answers": ["February 14", "Kekk\u00f4 Kamen: Royale", "Radio Days", "The Big Trail"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Maria Ozawa?", "answers": ["Winter Passing", "Unforgiven", "Kekk\u00f4 Kamen: Premium", "Pushing Tin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Maria Ozawa?", "answers": ["Date Night", "Used Cars", "Erotibot", "Gair"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Maria Ozawa?", "answers": ["Mela", "Carriage Ghost", "Looking for Richard", "Ek Rishtaa: The Bond of Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Maria Ozawa?", "answers": ["A Madea Christmas", "Blackadder: Back & Forth", "Bananas", "Invitation Only"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Maria Ozawa?", "answers": ["The Bank Job", "Maid's Room: Return of the Master", "The Kid & I", "Mr. Wonderful"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Ace Ventura: Pet Detective", "Yuvan Yuvathi", "Torn Curtain", "How the Grinch Stole Christmas!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Sabotage", "Losin' It", "Waqt: The Race Against Time", "Rasigan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Gabbar", "Champagne", "Mei and the Kittenbus", "Crossing Over"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Along Came Polly", "Horrible Bosses", "Frenzy", "Biwi No.1"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["The Chain Reaction", "The Man Who Knew Too Much", "Maximum Overdrive", "Child in the Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["The Skin Game", "Letters from Iwo Jima", "The Karate Kid 2", "Treasure Island"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["The Master", "I'm Still Here: Real Diaries of Young People Who Lived During the Holocaust", "Blackmail", "Rocky III"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Lifeboat", "The War", "Havoc", "Police Story 3: Super Cop"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Hatya: The Murder", "All the Right Moves", "The Sixth Sense", "Number Seventeen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Rang De Basanti", "Saudagar", "Khushi", "The Farmer's Wife"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Easy Virtue", "Sudden Impact", "Faster", "Chain Reaction"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["The Happening", "K\u016bs\u014d no Sora Tobu Kikaitachi", "Chaahat", "Notorious"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["The Wrong Man", "Legalese", "Raw Deal", "Terminator 2: Judgment Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Beowulf", "Foreign Correspondent", "Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull", "Rosewater"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Pari", "Rope", "The Terminator", "Blood Red"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["WWE: King of the Ring 2002", "Sainik", "The Manxman", "Bird on a Wire"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Semi-Pro", "Dial M for Murder", "Rush Hour", "xXx"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Hanover Street", "Escape Plan", "Mr. & Mrs. Smith", "English Vinglish"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Amblin", "The Trouble with Harry", "LOL: Laughing Out Loud", "Daulat Ki Jung"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Hudson Hawk", "The Birds", "Manglehorn", "Jungle Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Gone Girl", "Under Capricorn", "Shaolin Temple", "Mississippi Masala"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Criminal Law", "Mad Max: Fury Road", "Shadow of a Doubt", "Sooryavansham"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["The Lady Vanishes", "The Spirit", "Inception", "The New Legend Of Shaolin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Curious George", "The 39 Steps", "Grand Champion", "Melinda and Melinda"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Firefox", "Stephen King's Desperation", "Orphan's Song", "Saboteur"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Rear Window", "The Coriolis Effect", "Jeet", "Bhoothnath"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Disney's The Kid", "Topaz", "Aarakshan", "A River Runs Through It"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Pale Rider", "Fire with Fire", "Stagecoach", "Murder!"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Hannah Montana & Miley Cyrus: Best of Both Worlds Concert", "Premonition", "Rich and Strange", "The Last Samurai"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Red River", "Family Plot", "Apocalypto", "Amistad"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Howl's Moving Castle", "Marnie", "Fanaa", "Tashan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Poove Unakkaga", "North by Northwest", "Arizona Dream", "Baghban"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Jamaica Inn", "Child in the Night", "Dumb & Dumber", "The Birdcage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["World War Z", "Kadhalukku Mariyadhai", "The Paradine Case", "The Recruit"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Cruising", "Vertigo", "Ocean's Twelve", "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Look Who's Talking Now", "Kilroy", "Suspicion", "3 Godfathers"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["I Confess", "Edison", "Apocalypto", "Phenomenon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["SugarTime", "The Cherry Orchard", "Young and Innocent", "The Woodsman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["The War Wagon", "Spellbound", "Muniyandi Vilangial Moonramandu", "The Waterboy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Two Bits", "Bon Voyage", "Short Fuse", "White House Down"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Omkara", "Downhill", "New York Stories", "The Purple Rose of Cairo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Secret Agent", "Telling Lies in America", "Alpha Dog", "The Weekend"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Rebecca", "Ils se mari\u00e8rent et eurent beaucoup d'enfants", "Born to Defence", "Maya Memsaab"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Zabriskie Point", "The Ring", "Alice", "The One"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Found a Groom", "Jayne Mansfield's Car", "The Mountain Eagle", "Ek Rishtaa: The Bond of Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["To Catch a Thief", "Stay", "Night Skies", "Tequila Sunrise"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["The Pleasure Garden", "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", "The Thin Red Line", "Drunken Master"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Action Replayy", "The Cowboys", "Psycho", "Horton Hears a Who!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["The One", "Strangers on a Train", "OMG \u2013 Oh My God!", "Cinderella"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Batman vs. Superman", "Ride Along", "Stage Fright", "1900"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Being Human", "The Lodger: A Story of the London Fog", "Too Late for Divorce", "Jingle All the Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Toy Story 2", "A Jet-Setters Dream", "You Will Meet a Tall Dark Stranger", "Garv"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Money for Nothing", "Spy Kids 3-D: Game Over", "Planet 51", "Marvin's Room"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Hotel Transylvania", "Empire of the Sun", "Machete", "Hollywoodland"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Fashionista's Fantasy", "Deewana", "Thulladha Manamum Thullum", "Family Plot"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["The Running Man", "Rio Lobo", "XXX: The Return of Xander Cage", "Wizards of Waverly Place: The Movie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Gossip with the Girls", "The King", "Last Hero in China", "Extreme Movie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["The Love Guru", "Over the Hedge", "Horrible Bosses", "Monte Carlo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["The River", "Cop Out", "True Grit", "Behaving Badly"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Kekk\u00f4 Kamen: Royale", "The Godfather Part III", "Arwin!", "Grand Canyon"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Only God Forgives", "Pilot Season", "He's Just Not That Into You", "The Believer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Arthur and the Vengeance of Maltazard", "Ra.One", "Zakhm", "Devdas"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["How to Train Your Dragon", "Getaway", "The Panic in Needle Park", "Melinda and Melinda"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["The Wizards Return: Alex vs. Alex", "Internal Affairs", "Happy Gilmore", "Lord of War"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Mission: Impossible 5", "The Fighter", "Blue Valentine", "Hot Mess"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Cobra", "Ramona and Beezus", "Cruising", "Apollo at 70: A Hot Night in Harlem"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Witness", "Kadhalukku Mariyadhai", "Fifty Shades of Blue", "The Dark Knight Rises"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Spike & Mike's Classic Festival of Animation", "Rudderless", "Stand by Me", "Mad Max Beyond Thunderdome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Nilaave Vaa", "Savages", "Shinjuku Incident", "Another Cinderella Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey", "Blue", "Spring Breakers", "Deep Impact"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Arthur 3: The War of the Two Worlds", "Badlanders", "Wild at Heart", "Infancy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Cop Land", "Angels in America", "Horton Hears a Who!", "The War Wagon"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Small Time Crooks", "Princess Protection Program", "Too Late for Divorce", "Abhimaan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Playing for Keeps", "The Incredible Burt Wonderstone", "The Ides of March", "The Favor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Total Recall", "Band of Brothers", "The Cable Guy", "Thunderbolt and Lightfoot"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Simon Birch", "Xtreme City", "Frankenstein", "Rocky II"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Catch .44", "Half Baked", "Bruce Almighty", "Porco Rosso: The Last Sortie"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Fun with Dick and Jane", "Don Jon", "Wild at Heart", "Step Brothers"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Mixed Nuts", "Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull", "Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man's Chest", "Ace Ventura: When Nature Calls"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["London Dreams", "Finders Keepers", "Minority Report", "Raw Deal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["The Fighter", "Platoon", "The Dead Pool", "The Chronicles of Riddick: Dark Fury"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Dumb and Dumber To", "Billu Barber", "Soul Men", "The Polar Express"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Irokoishi", "The Final Cut", "Finding Neverland", "The Number 23"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Meet the Parents", "The Majestic", "The Heart Is But A Child", "Born on the Fourth of July"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Hum", "The Thetan", "Deep Blue Sea", "100 Years of Comedy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Think Like A Man", "Rumble Fish", "I Love You Phillip Morris", "The Final Cut"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Quicksilver Highway", "The Work of Director Michel Gondry", "Kids From Shaolin", "Mr Deeds"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["The Bounty", "The Bonfire of the Vanities", "The Truman Show", "Blackadder: Back & Forth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Edward Scissorhands", "Peggy Sue Got Married", "Talaash", "The Suburbans"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Eddie Presley", "How the Grinch Stole Christmas!", "The Firm", "Love Part 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["She's So Lovely", "Mike Hammer: Murder Takes All", "The Quick and the Dead", "Thiruthani"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["CZ12", "Doing Time on Maple Drive", "The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers", "Basic"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Seduced And Abandoned", "Margaret", "Mirror Mirror", "Ace Ventura: Pet Detective"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Carriage Ghost", "Under the Sea 3D", "The Untouchables", "WWE: WrestleMania 27: Vol. 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Twins", "Winter Passing", "The Frozen Ground", "Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["The Mask", "Hancock 2", "Devdas", "August Rush"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Sixteen Candles", "Presidential Reunion", "Zelig", "I Confess"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Rubberface", "Blitz", "The Heart Is But A Child", "The Bridges of Madison County"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Comic Relief IV", "Veer", "Beyond All Boundaries", "Open Windows"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Salt 2", "Earth Girls Are Easy", "Death Race 2000", "The Aviator"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Once Bitten", "The Maiden Heist", "Morgan and Destiny's Eleventeenth Date: The Zeppelin Zoo", "Nim's Island"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Lupin the 3rd: The Castle of Cagliostro: Special Edition", "A Jet-Setters Dream", "Cold Dead Hand with Jim Carrey", "Paycheck"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Along Came a Spider", "Mr. Popper's Penguins", "Love and Death", "Grand Champion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["The Incredibles", "Foxcatcher", "Hoshi o Katta Hi", "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["The Grifters", "True Grit", "Anna Nicole Smith: Exposed", "Batman Forever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Barood", "Manglehorn", "Riding the Bullet", "Laughing Out Loud: America's Funniest Comedians"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Two Mules for Sister Sara", "Drunk History Christmas", "Rocky", "Circle of Iron"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Beetlejuice", "Yes Man", "Mystic River", "This Is the End"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Up in the Air", "Kick-Ass 2", "Digging to China", "What Dreams May Come"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Loomis Fargo", "The Son of No One", "Jawani Zindabad", "City Hunter"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["The Naked Gun 33\u2153: The Final Insult", "Tremors", "Horton Hears a Who!", "When the Party's Over"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Revolver", "Ash Wednesday", "Liar Liar", "Mission: Impossible \u2013 Ghost Protocol"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["The Expendables 2", "The Bridges of Madison County", "The Adventures of Tom Thumb and Thumbelina", "Pecan Pie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Lucky: No Time for Love", "Hum Saath-Saath Hain: We Stand United", "All in Good Taste", "Kaalia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Cry Freedom", "Ek Tha Tiger", "Dumb & Dumber", "Gallipoli"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Used Guys", "O.S.O.", "Total Recall", "Hereafter"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Naseeb", "Ricky Stanicky", "The Big Picture", "Unbecoming Age"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Pink Cadillac", "Jewel of the Sahara", "The Numbers Station", "To the Limit"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Revolutionary Road", "A Christmas Carol", "Knightriders", "Rock Mafia Presents: The Big Bang"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Man on the Moon", "The Cowboys", "Son of Sardaar", "Thamizhan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["The Sex and Violence Family Hour", "February 14", "Matchstick Men", "Sleeper"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Kevin Hart: Let Me Explain", "Red River", "Ra.One", "Itsy Bitsy Spider"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jim Carrey?", "answers": ["Blackadder's Christmas Carol", "Illegal Aliens", "Frankenweenie (1984)", "Copper Mountain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Coolie", "Five", "The Lake House", "Disney's The Kid"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Office Space", "Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas", "Beauty Shop", "200 Cigarettes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Gone Baby Gone", "Scarecrow", "Joe", "Squirrels to the Nuts"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["John Q", "Ed Wood", "Melody Time", "Marley & Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Power", "The Object of My Affection", "High Risk", "Night Skies"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["The Switch", "Carrie", "Terminator 3: Rise of the Machines", "Ek Tha Tiger"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["The Goree Girls", "Song of the South", "Dogma", "Mumbai Diaries"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Jaan", "The Newton Boys", "It", "Born on the Fourth of July"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Love Happens", "Gia", "Luv", "Aatank Hi Aatank"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["The Man Who Cried", "Swades", "The Robber Bride", "She's the One"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Minsara Kanna", "Unity", "Turner & Hooch", "Shadowmancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Jersey Girl", "Ash Wednesday", "Aladin", "Rumor Has It\u2026"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["The Blind Side", "Rumble Fish", "Red Sonja", "Management"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Spy Kids", "Bulletproof", "Hollywoodland", "Wanderlust"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Domestic Disturbance", "For Queen and Country", "The High and the Mighty", "Life of Crime"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["The Nightmare Before Christmas", "Linda Lovelace for President", "Camp Cucamonga", "Airheads"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Blades of Glory", "Swiss Family Robinson", "He's Just Not That Into You", "Day Zero"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Don's Plum", "Miss You Already", "Star Wars Holiday Special", "Winter Passing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["The Dilemma", "Easy Virtue", "The Favor", "Dream for an Insomniac"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Trespasses", "Grease", "Picture Perfect", "The Longest Yard"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["The Bounty Hunter", "Every Time We Say Goodbye", "Once Upon a Time in Mexico", "Fire with Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Bon Voyage", "Derailed", "The Phantom of the Opera", "The Family That Preys"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Room 10", "Frost/Nixon", "Children of the Corn: The Final Sacrifice", "Broadway Danny Rose"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["The World According to Garp", "Rock Star", "Drive", "Captive"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Flawless", "National Treasure: Book of Secrets", "The Love Guru", "The Good Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Sarfarosh", "Convention", "Don", "Say Anything..."], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Donnie Brasco", "Bruce Almighty", "Cruising", "Miss Congeniality"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Stand Up Guys", "The Dead Pool", "The Thin Pink Line", "Heat"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["The Iron Giant", "Coimbatore Mappillai", "Pardes", "Adalat"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Downhill", "Time Changer", "Along Came Polly", "The Ugly Truth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Eat Pray Love", "Celebrity News Reels: Hollywood's Most Infamous Couples and Ugliest Breakups", "Jupiter Ascending", "Boss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["The Break-Up", "Somebody to Love", "Spring Breakers", "School Ties"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Sleepover", "The Virginity Hit", "Maid's Room: Return of the Master", "Friends with Money"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Get Shorty", "Madea's Class Reunion", "Always", "Horrible Bosses 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Great Expectations", "My Least Favorite Career", "Windtalkers", "Romance & Cigarettes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["'Til There Was You", "Speed 2: Cruise Control", "Drowning Mona", "Michael Clayton"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["We're the Millers", "The Contract", "Revolver", "Grand Canyon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Raja Hindustani", "Once Upon a Time in China", "Just Go With It", "Goodbye Lover"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Rio Lobo", "Naked in New York", "The Gauntlet", "Horrible Bosses"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Jennifer Aniston?", "answers": ["Kick-Ass 2", "The Last Boy Scout", "Leprechaun", "Thunderbolt"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Death Race 2000", "Matchstick Men", "Saludos Amigos", "Crank: High Voltage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Where the Truth Lies", "Namak Halaal", "We're the Millers", "Capone"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Dead Man", "Baazigar", "Rocky V", "Fool's Gold"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["The Alamo", "McLintock!", "Kal Ho Naa Ho", "Cobra"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Schindler's List", "Antz", "Jingle All the Way", "American Hustle"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Mary Poppins", "The Phantom of the Opera", "Demolition Man", "Christmas in Connecticut"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Snake in the Eagle's Shadow", "Avenging Angelo", "Joe Kidd", "A League of Their Own"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Rambo III", "2 Guns", "Extraordinary Measures", "Meeting Evil"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Knowing", "Andaz Naya Naya", "Rocky II", "Tim Janis: Beautiful America"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["The Bounty", "The Goree Girls", "The Expendables 2", "Heartbreak Ridge"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Batman", "Saturday Night Fever", "The Air Up There", "Judge Dredd"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["American Breakdown", "Paradise Alley", "Magic Mike", "Transformers: Age of Extinction"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Dial M for Murder", "Anchorman 2: The Legend Continues", "Entourage", "Grudge Match"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Ender's Game", "Signs", "Earth", "Over the Top"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["The Face: Jesus in Art", "The Good Life", "The Godfather Part III", "The Manchurian Candidate"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Hereafter", "The One", "WWE Tagged Classics 2003: Royal Rumble", "Nighthawks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["The 11th Hour", "Spy Kids 3-D: Game Over", "Diner", "Aankhen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["The Paradine Case", "The Lords of Flatbush", "Baazigar", "Sooryavansham"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Peekay", "No Place to Hide", "The Horse Soldiers", "Villu"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["City of Angels", "Rocky IV", "Lookin' to Get Out", "Face/Off"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Chennai Express", "Rambo: First Blood Part II", "Snake in the Eagle's Shadow", "Predator"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Nothing in Common", "Do the Right Thing", "Reach Me", "Daredevil"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["S.W.A.T.", "Zookeeper", "Menace II Society", "The Faculty"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["King Lear", "Apt Pupil", "Kung Fu Panda 3", "Daylight"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["I'm Still Here: Real Diaries of Young People Who Lived During the Holocaust", "Bandits", "Mandingo", "Safe"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Splash", "Rope", "First Blood", "One Crazy Summer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Brubaker", "Batman & Robin", "Rambo", "Bandits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Men in Black 3", "Bullet to the Head", "The Imaginarium of Dr. Parnassus", "Plane Crazy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["You Don't Know Jack", "Behind the Candelabra", "Lock Up", "Leatherheads"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Rocky III", "Fast Food", "Kung Fu Panda", "Legend of the Lost"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Criminal Law", "The Rookie", "The Simple Life of Noah Dearborn", "Shade"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Get Carter", "Family Bond", "Cast Away", "All in Good Taste"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Smokin' Aces", "D-Tox", "Tum Mere Ho", "The Longest Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Rango", "The Legend of Drunken Master", "The Expendables 3", "Hollywood Ending"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Cliffhanger", "Hum Aapke Hain Kaun...!", "Serpico", "Thank You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["The Birdcage", "Staying Alive", "Chocolat", "Hondo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Chori Chori Chupke Chupke", "Awwal Number", "Escape Plan", "Kevin Hart: Laugh at My Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Firelight", "Tango & Cash", "Carlito's Way", "Good Time Gang"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Fast Food", "Rhinestone", "Mangal Pandey: The Rising", "Mirror Mirror"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Apocalypto", "Havoc", "Trespass", "Driven"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Homefront", "Loverboy", "Fast & Furious 6", "The Green Mile"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Feast of Love", "Ab Tumhare Hawale Watan Saathiyo", "Grand Champion", "Assassins"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Once Upon a Time in America", "Lara Croft Tomb Raider: The Cradle of Life", "Yuvvraaj", "Stop! Or My Mom Will Shoot"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["The Majestic", "Cop Land", "Innerspace", "WWE: WrestleMania 27: Vol. 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["How the Grinch Stole Christmas!", "Alice in Wonderland", "Something Like a Business", "Rocky Balboa"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["The Big Boss", "Memoirs of a Geisha", "The Other Guys", "Rocky"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Castle in the Sky: Bonus Material", "Fu gui fu yun", "Escape to Victory", "The Normal Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Trespass", "Bicentennial Man", "The Specialist", "National Geographic: Beyond the Movie: Pearl Harbor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["The Expendables", "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", "The Producers", "Chennai Kadhal"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["Poltergeist", "Fun and Fancy Free", "Star Wars Episode IV: A New Hope", "Oscar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sylvester Stallone?", "answers": ["F.I.S.T", "Author! Author!", "Mission: Impossible III", "Aladin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Liberace?", "answers": ["The Fearless Hyena", "The River Wild", "Merry Mirthquakes", "The Punisher"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Liberace?", "answers": ["Igor", "The Dilemma", "The Loved One", "Magnolia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Eraser", "Donnie Brasco", "Premonition", "Color of Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["LOL: Laughing Out Loud", "Time Share", "The Local Stigmatic", "Lore"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Any Given Sunday", "End of Days", "Wanted", "Stagecoach"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Ali", "True Women", "The Insider", "A Love Song for Bobby Long"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Dazed and Confused", "Kilroy", "Insomnia", "Lucky: No Time for Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Scent of a Woman", "Inside Job", "Satyagraha", "All the Right Moves"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["The Bone Collector", "Imagine", "Bad Boys II", "Thunderbolt"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Happy Anniversary and Goodbye", "The Vow", "Grown Ups", "The Godfather Saga"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Reign of Fire", "Six Days Seven Nights", "The Godfather", "Song of the South"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Larry Crowne", "Swiss Family Robinson", "Dog Day Afternoon", "Adalat"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Billu Barber", "Frankie and Johnny", "Looking for a Home", "Shout"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Contagion", "Masti: Sanam Teri Kasam", "Nights in Rodanthe", "City Hall"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Bouncers", "Domestic Disturbance", "Author! Author!", "Perfect"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["The Son of No One", "Rose Red", "Stop-Loss", "Lara Croft: Tomb Raider"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Shahjahan", "Glengarry Glen Ross", "The Toxic Boy", "Sudden Impact"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["You've Got Mail", "Madea's Class Reunion", "The Recruit", "Three O'Clock High"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Sea of Love", "Kaze Tachinu", "The Adventures of Tom Thumb and Thumbelina", "Valley Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["The Man with One Red Shoe", "Lagaan: Once Upon a Time in India", "Johnny Suede", "The Merchant of Venice"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Tooth Fairy", "Righteous Kill", "Bananas", "Fist of Legend"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["...And Justice for All", "Ace Ventura: When Nature Calls", "Peter Pan", "The River Wild"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Munich", "The Godfather Part III", "The Beaver", "Radio Days"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["King Lear", "Maniac", "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory", "Mad Max 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Arthur and the Vengeance of Maltazard", "Soul Men", "Wilde Salome", "Mixed Nuts"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Phool Aur Kaante", "A Midsummer Night's Sex Comedy", "Old Dogs", "Serpico"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Bobby Deerfield", "Tees Maar Khan", "Jakob the Liar", "The Notebook"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Children of the Corn IV: The Gathering", "Phil Spector", "Primary Colors", "Conan the Barbarian"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Charlotte's Web", "Chinese Coffee", "Mean Streets", "The Kid"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Batman Returns", "Dick Tracy", "The Comancheros", "The Bounty Hunter"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Zelig", "S1m0ne", "WWE: The Videos: Vol. 1: Ramped Up", "Ils se mari\u00e8rent et eurent beaucoup d'enfants"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["CZ12", "Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace", "Dinner for Schmucks", "Gigli"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["All the Right Moves", "Say Anything...", "Carlito's Way", "'Til There Was You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Children of the Corn: The Final Sacrifice", "It", "You Don't Know Jack", "Thunder Run"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Patiala House", "The Devil's Advocate", "From Hell", "Argo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Captain America: The Winter Soldier", "Rambo: First Blood Part II", "WWE: King of the Ring 2000", "The Panic in Needle Park"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Arthur 3: The War of the Two Worlds", "Two Bits", "We Bought a Zoo", "The Singing Detective"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["XXX: The Return of Xander Cage", "Cinema16: American Short Films", "The Godfather Part II", "Pokiri"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Silsila", "Ocean's Eleven", "Body of Lies", "Angels in America"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Way of the Dragon", "The Lucky One", "Naye Nagme: Vol. 2", "GOTTI: In The Shadow Of My Father"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Crimson Tide", "Winter's Tale", "Revolution", "The Third Wheel"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["The Slaughter Rule", "Looking for Richard", "Since You've Been Gone", "Porco Rosso: The Last Sortie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Phenomenon", "Babylon A.D.", "Staying Alive", "88 Minutes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Edison", "Heat", "The Weekend", "Kiki's Delivery Service"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Red Dragon", "Mr. & Mrs. Smith", "The Eiger Sanction", "Manglehorn"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["I'm Still Here: Real Diaries of Young People Who Lived During the Holocaust", "Max Payne", "Friends with Money", "Stand Up Guys"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Pee-wee's Big Adventure", "People I Know", "Showtime", "The Farmer's Wife"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Scarface", "Singham", "Phantoms", "Convention"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Outbreak", "The Tree of Life", "Notting Hill", "Scarecrow"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Shark Tale", "'Salem's Lot", "Menace II Society", "Two for the Money"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["Twilight Zone: The Movie", "Bean", "Ocean's Thirteen", "Without Limits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Al Pacino?", "answers": ["The Secret Life of Bees", "Happy Feet", "Terminator 3: Rise of the Machines", "Cruising"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicholas Sparks?", "answers": ["Flags of Our Fathers", "Nighthawks", "The Last Song", "Shadows and Fog"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicholas Sparks?", "answers": ["Message in a Bottle", "Transformers: Age of Extinction", "Dick", "8mm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicholas Sparks?", "answers": ["The War", "Zandalee", "The Lucky One", "No Entry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicholas Sparks?", "answers": ["The Unbelievables", "The Country Bears", "Airheads", "The Notebook"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicholas Sparks?", "answers": ["Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham", "Gerry", "Four Rooms", "A Walk to Remember"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicholas Sparks?", "answers": ["Nights in Rodanthe", "Hope Springs", "S.W.A.T.", "The Incredibles"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicholas Sparks?", "answers": ["Safe Haven", "Gamer", "In Love and War", "Signs"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Nicholas Sparks?", "answers": ["Mission: Impossible II", "Dear John", "Pu-239", "Friends with Money"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Michael Clayton", "Hudson Hawk", "Michael", "Hansel & Gretel: Witch Hunters"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["After Earth", "While You Were Sleeping", "Return to Horror High", "Jackie Brown"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Around the World in 80 Days", "Sachein", "Hum Saath-Saath Hain: We Stand United", "Ocean's Twelve"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Fantastic Mr. Fox", "Aitraaz", "Crossing Over", "The Da Vinci Code"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["McQ", "Burn After Reading", "Fight Club", "Mary Reilly"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Curious George", "Once Upon a Time in China II", "Angel and the Badman", "Gravity"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Behaving Badly", "Jersey Girl", "Babylon A.D.", "Combat Academy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["The Thin Red Line", "Seval", "The Terminal", "Emmtan-Magan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["All About Steve", "Namak Halaal", "Raajneeti", "Welcome to Collinwood"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Contagion", "Drowning Mona", "The Shootist", "The Descendants"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["The Monuments Men", "Men of Honor", "Blade Runner", "Three Mississippi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Oblivion", "Duplicity", "From Dusk till Dawn", "Arizona Dream"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Cop Out", "Say Anything...", "Shooter", "Fail Safe"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Batman & Robin", "Austin Powers: International Man of Mystery", "Marvin's Room", "The Woodsman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["The Bonfire of the Vanities", "Safe", "Planet 51", "Spy Kids 3-D: Game Over"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Cahill U.S. Marshal", "Simon Birch", "Desi Boyz", "Ocean's Eleven"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["The World According to Garp", "Leatherheads", "Zanjeer", "Get Carter"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Air Force One", "Phantoms", "Kilroy", "WWE Tagged Classics 2003: No Way Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Argo", "The Passion of the Christ", "Romeo Must Die", "Innerspace"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["The Last Boy Scout", "Return of the Killer Tomatoes", "Cocktail", "Amblin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Planet 51", "Rumble in the Bronx", "Jungle Fever", "August: Osage County"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Sand and Sorrow", "Salt 2", "Tropic Thunder", "The Story of Yanagawa's Canals"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Madea's Big Happy Family", "Suburbicon", "Mr. & Mrs. Smith", "The Deer Hunter"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Pu-239", "Melody Time", "The Ant Bully", "Ferdinand the Bull"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Chains of Gold", "The Ides of March", "Deewana", "Stir of Echoes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Bird on a Wire", "Deewana Mujh Sa Nahin", "Kill Bill Volume 1", "Confessions of a Dangerous Mind"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Whisper of the Heart", "The Men Who Stare at Goats", "Valley Girl", "Mr. Bean's Holiday"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Southland Tales", "Out of Sight", "Desi Boyz", "Enter the Dragon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["XXX: State of the Union", "RV", "Syriana", "Arabian Nights"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Miracle Run", "Punch-Drunk Love", "Dragon Fight", "The Good German"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Rebecca", "Red River", "The I Love Lucy 50th Anniversary Special", "Ocean's Thirteen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["She's Having a Baby", "Infancy", "The Perfect Storm", "The Face: Jesus in Art"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Three Kings", "Kevin Hart: I'm a Grown Little Man", "Sleeping with the Enemy", "The Firm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Kyon Ki", "A Few Good Men", "Criminal", "The Town"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Solaris", "Tees Maar Khan", "Pearl Harbor", "Murder by Numbers"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Swades", "Babylon A.D.", "Spy Kids", "The Mangler"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Legends of the Fall", "Good Deeds", "Red Surf", "Kaal"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["One Fine Day", "Magnum Force", "Badlanders", "Yaadon Ki Baaraat"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Unbecoming Age", "The Last Boy Scout", "The 39 Steps", "The Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Kachche Dhaage", "The Rundown", "The Jacket", "Three O'Clock High"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Maximum Overdrive", "Family Bond", "Morgan and Destiny's Eleventeenth Date: The Zeppelin Zoo", "Tim Janis: Beautiful America"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Hammy's Boomerang Adventure", "Chocolat", "Ted", "Up in the Air"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["An Orphan's Tragedy", "F.I.S.T", "The American", "'Til There Was You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Let the Devil Wear Black", "The Harvest", "Cocaine Cowboys", "Training Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Kung Fu Panda 2", "Intolerable Cruelty", "The Villain", "The Newton Boys"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["No Place to Hide", "Fire with Fire", "The Peacemaker", "The Ninth Gate"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Super Rhino", "Rope", "Tomorrowland", "My Big Fat Greek Wedding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see George Clooney?", "answers": ["Anger Management", "Raja Hindustani", "8", "Hero"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Deewane", "The Pacifier", "Mr. Tadano's Secret Mission: From Japan with Love", "Derailed"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Look Who's Talking Now", "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial", "Hitting It Hard", "Hum Dil De Chuke Sanam"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Raju Chacha", "Desperado", "Homefront", "Deep Impact"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Sudden Impact", "Mystic Pizza", "The Heart Is But A Child", "The 40-Year-Old Virgin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["The Bonfire of the Vanities", "Carbon Copy", "Dragon Fight", "Singham"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Stop-Loss", "Ready", "The Rookie", "The Landlord"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["London Dreams", "Hangmen", "Men in Black: Alien Attack", "Dumb & Dumber"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Kyon Ki", "In the Bag", "Gangaajal", "Fast Times at Ridgemont High"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["From Dusk Till Dawn 2: Texas Blood Money", "Lone Survivor", "Jumper", "Pyar To Hona Hi Tha"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Mazes and Monsters", "Flubber", "Chori Chori", "Mad Max: Fury Road"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Random Hearts", "Ishq", "The Fearless Hyena", "Blossoms & Blood"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Mississippi Masala", "Golmaal: Fun Unlimited", "Saturday Night Fever", "High School Musical 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Flying Swords of Dragon Gate", "Gair", "The Great Debaters", "Once Upon a Time in China"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["All the Best: Fun Begins", "Geronimo: An American Legend", "Olympus Has Fallen", "Mazes and Monsters"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Anand", "Sangram", "The Alamo", "Kadhal FM"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Ocean's Twelve", "Love and Death", "The Other Guys", "Himmatwala"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Star Wars Episode IV: A New Hope", "Ferdinand the Bull", "Toy Story", "Tezz"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Jung", "Boobie", "Gran Torino", "Howl's Moving Castle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Scavenger Hunt", "What's New Pussycat?", "Street Smart", "Dil Kya Kare"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["The Notebook", "The Robber Bride", "Suhaag", "Larry Crowne"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Raajneeti", "The Chain Reaction", "Traveller", "Lucky Numbers"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Gigli", "Funny People", "Mehbooba", "Salt"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Dil Hai Ke Manta Nahin", "The Thin Red Line", "Major Saab", "Jawani Zindabad"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Taarzan: The Wonder Car", "Signs", "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind", "License to Kill"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["City Hunter", "Mystic River", "Unthinkable", "Golmaal 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["The Dark Knight Rises", "Once Bitten", "Once Upon a Time in Mumbaai", "Creepshow"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Chandni Chowk to China", "The Loved One", "Kabhi Kabhie", "Satyagraha"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Cahill U.S. Marshal", "Arthur and the Vengeance of Maltazard", "Naajayaz", "The Blind Side"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Daylight", "Jaan", "Igor", "Hercules in New York"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Death to Smoochy", "Abbot Hai Teng of Shaolin", "Omkara", "Max Payne"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Salt", "Marnie", "Qayamat Se Qayamat Tak", "Bol Bachchan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Ghajini", "Juvies", "Kachche Dhaage", "The Mummy - Tomb of the Dragon Emperor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["The Parent Trap", "The Legend of Drunken Master", "Qayamat: City Under Threat", "Friday the 13th"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["The Skin Game", "Dilwale", "Cocktail", "Virtuosity"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Big Jake", "Diljale", "Flesh and Blood", "The Bumblebee Flies Anyway"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Pulp Fiction", "Star Wars Holiday Special", "An American Tail: Fievel Goes West", "Son of Sardaar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Thambikku Indha Ooru", "Kekk\u00f4 Kamen: Royale", "Desi Boyz", "Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Kaalia", "Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace", "Rascals", "Cry-Baby"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["The Iron Giant", "Premonition", "Zakhm", "Stage Fright"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["How to Swim", "Har Dil Jo Pyar Karega", "Batman Begins", "Phool Aur Kaante"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Badlanders", "Zanjeer", "Once Upon a Time Again", "Aakrosh"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["For Queen and Country", "Golmaal Returns", "Annie", "Force 10 from Navarone"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Love Love Love", "Ash Wednesday", "American Teacher", "Hulchul"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Menace II Society", "Stop-Loss", "Ek Hi Raasta", "The Bonfire of the Vanities"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Vijaypath", "What's Eating Gilbert Grape", "Mission: Impossible II", "Donald in Mathmagic Land"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Mary Poppins", "Men in Black", "Deewangee", "Dead Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["The Birdcage", "Itihaas", "Young and Innocent", "Spellbound"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Erin Brockovich", "Dulhan Hum Le Jayenge", "Gundaraj", "The Brazilian Job"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["The Cherry Orchard", "U Me Aur Hum", "License to Kill", "Ek Tha Tiger"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["The Comancheros", "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial", "High Crimes", "Naam"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Ajay Devgan?", "answers": ["Knight and Day", "Solitary Man", "Masti: Sanam Teri Kasam", "Stage Fright"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sunny Leone?", "answers": ["Sunny Leone Loves HD Porn", "The New Legend Of Shaolin", "Alice in Wonderland", "Raising Arizona"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sunny Leone?", "answers": ["The Thetan", "Delhi Belly", "Zila Ghaziabad", "Close Encounters of the Third Kind"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sunny Leone?", "answers": ["Knight and Day", "The Virginity Hit", "Black Snake Moan", "Welcome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sunny Leone?", "answers": ["Los Bandoleros", "The Brave", "Two for the Money", "Jism 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Sunny Leone?", "answers": ["Melody Time", "Goodfellas", "Shootout at Wadala", "Scent of a Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Thamizhan", "The Founding of a Republic", "Austin Powers: International Man of Mystery", "Silver Linings Playbook"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["The Kid", "Lord of War", "Bouncers", "Men of Honor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Melinda and Melinda", "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham", "Atlanta Symphony Golden Anniversary", "The Adventures of Tom Thumb and Thumbelina"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["The Conversation", "Hum Dil De Chuke Sanam", "Blades of Glory", "Thinner"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Million Dollar Baby", "Red Sonja", "Men Seeking Women", "Cocaine Cowboys"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Man on Fire", "I'm Still Here: Real Diaries of Young People Who Lived During the Holocaust", "Sweet and Lowdown", "Anchorman: The Legend of Ron Burgundy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Minions", "Beyond All Boundaries", "Megamind: The Button of Doom", "Dear Frankie"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Jay and Silent Bob Strike Back", "City Hall", "Star Wars Episode III: Revenge of the Sith", "Ghost Rider: Spirit of Vengeance"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Frost on Satire", "Emmtan-Magan", "Crimson Tide", "Ace Ventura: When Nature Calls"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Winter's Tale", "Hook", "Bullet to the Head", "The Other Guys NYPD Recruitment Video"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Paint Your Wagon", "Kids From Shaolin", "Hard Rain", "Curious George"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["How to Train Your Dragon 2", "Superstar", "Let the Devil Wear Black", "Dil Chahta Hai"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Radio Flyer", "Bachelorette", "Abhimaan", "Master Spy: The Robert Hanssen Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Tropic Thunder", "1408", "The Color Purple", "Step Brothers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Anchorman 2: The Legend Continues", "Inglourious Basterds", "Riddick", "Cocktail"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["The Tourist", "The Producers", "Aankhen", "The Whole Nine Yards"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Hansel & Gretel: Witch Hunters", "Captain Corelli's Mandolin", "Bon Voyage", "Clerks II"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Like Stars on Earth", "Boris and Natasha: The Movie", "Transporter 3", "Fight for Your Right Revisited"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["The Harvest", "J. Edgar", "Devdas", "Dick"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["The Game Plan", "Stranger than Fiction", "The Five-Year Engagement", "Wilde Salome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["A Night at the Roxbury", "Bullets Over Broadway", "Rush Hour 2", "Darr"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["You Don't Know Jack", "Larry Crowne", "The Wendell Baker Story", "No Entry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["The Man Who Shot Liberty Valance", "The Ladies Man", "Blackmail", "The Great Buck Howard"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["The Campaign", "You've Got Mail", "Scenes from Django Unchained - UK Winner", "Spy Kids"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Police Story 2", "Golmaal Returns", "Kicking & Screaming", "Stalk of the Celery Monster"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Zila Ghaziabad", "Armour of God II: Operation Condor", "Lagaan: Once Upon a Time in India", "A Bucket of Blood"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["The Mountain Eagle", "Multi-Facial", "The Landlord", "The Gnome-Mobile"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Old School", "The Favor", "Turbo", "Turn It Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Dolores Claiborne", "Children of the Corn IV: The Gathering", "Baaghi: A Rebel for Love", "Tim and Eric's Billion Dollar Movie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Elf", "Andaaz", "Kiki's Delivery Service", "Captain Phillips"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Raising Arizona", "Killing Them Softly", "Semi-Pro", "Interview with the Vampire: The Vampire Chronicles"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Bangkok Dangerous", "Hitting It Hard", "The 40-Year-Old Virgin", "The Other Guys"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Haywire", "Land of the Lost", "Hum Tumhare Hain Sanam", "Castle in the Sky: Bonus Material"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Arthur and the Vengeance of Maltazard", "Everybody's Fine", "Presidential Reunion", "Two If by Sea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Andaaz", "Shootout at Wadala", "Talladega Nights: The Ballad of Ricky Bobby", "Secret Agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Mystic Pizza", "The Polar Express", "Winter Passing", "Sivakasi"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Pattiyal", "Star Wars Episode II: Attack of the Clones", "Everything Must Go", "Aatank Hi Aatank"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Ghilli", "Sleeping Beauty", "Beretta's Island", "The Suburbans"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Maya Memsaab", "Quicksilver Highway", "A Christmas Carol", "Lego: The Piece of Resistance"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Thunder Run", "Saawan... The Love Season", "Deuce Bigalow: European Gigolo", "Zoolander"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Bewitched", "The Sword in the Stone", "Going All the Way", "Sora Iro no Tane"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Something Evil", "Joe Kidd", "All the Right Moves", "MegaMind"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["The Simple Life of Noah Dearborn", "Two of a Kind", "The Virginity Hit", "The Game of Their Lives"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Student of the Year", "Moneyball", "Drowning Mona", "The Tall Guy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Chain Reaction", "Frenzy", "The Thin Pink Line", "Broken City"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Yes Man", "Casa de Mi Padre", "The Substitute", "Priya: The Charming Girl of India"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Will Ferrell?", "answers": ["Psycho", "Curly Sue", "McLintock!", "Dear Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["All the Right Moves", "Mujhse Shaadi Karogi", "Bananas", "Secret Agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Antz", "Pulp Fiction", "Geronimo: An American Legend", "Evan Almighty"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Charlotte's Web", "Junior", "To Rome with Love", "Azhagai Irukkirai Bayamai Irukkirathu"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Alice", "Lawaaris", "Perfect", "Lucky: No Time for Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Way of the Dragon", "Big Daddy", "Celebrity", "The Legend 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Love and Death", "Gravity", "Omkara", "The Journey of Natty Gann"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Zelig", "Moonstruck", "Lock Up", "The Monuments Men"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Red River", "Madhosh", "Shadows and Fog", "The Guiding Light"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Himmatwala", "Thulladha Manamum Thullum", "Anand", "Scoop"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Take the Money and Run", "Fail Safe", "National Lampoon's Animal House", "Blind Date"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Mo' Better Blues", "Thuppakki", "Match Point", "The Jubilee Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Another Woman", "Death Race", "The Defender", "He's Just Not That Into You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Annie Hall", "Holi", "Perfect Stranger", "Donald in Mathmagic Land"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Grease", "Fading Gigolo", "Oblivion", "Date Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace", "Hollywood Ending", "Hum", "Happy Gilmore"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Kaal", "Alpha Dog", "The Chronicles of Riddick", "Don't Drink the Water"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Sangram", "Fight Club", "What's New Pussycat?", "Rocky II"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Anything Else", "Hairspray", "Despicable Me", "Number Seventeen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Marigold", "Young and Innocent", "Blue Jasmine", "Ocean's Thirteen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Cinema16: American Short Films", "Interiors", "The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers", "Golmaal 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Crank", "Princess Mononoke", "Sooryavansham", "Sweet and Lowdown"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Manhattan", "Good Deeds", "Swordfish", "The Contortionist's Handbook"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Ladder 49", "J. Edgar", "Chain Reaction", "You Will Meet a Tall Dark Stranger"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events", "One Eight Seven", "Life Is Beautiful", "The Family That Preys"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Taking Lives", "Scooby-Doo", "The Purple Rose of Cairo", "Rasigan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["World's Greatest Dad", "Blow Out", "Baadshah", "Mighty Aphrodite"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["The 39 Steps", "Gridiron Gang", "Hannah and Her Sisters", "Pardes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Crimes and Misdemeanors", "Minority Report", "Heyy Babyy", "To Catch a Thief"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Getting Straight", "Jersey Girl", "Fu gui fu yun", "September"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Sukiyaki Western Django", "A Midsummer Night's Sex Comedy", "Gangster Squad", "Don"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Reckless", "Gamer", "Casino Royale", "Nishabd"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Good Will Hunting", "Stardust Memories", "Tokyo Species", "XXX: State of the Union"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["The Mountain Eagle", "To Catch a Thief", "Zila Ghaziabad", "Melinda and Melinda"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Pirates of the Caribbean: On Stranger Tides", "Swiss Family Robinson", "Sleeper", "The Comancheros"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Midnight in Paris", "The Fugitive", "Romance & Cigarettes", "Wild Things"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["The Dead Pool", "Small Time Crooks", "Three Kings", "Kevin Hart: Laugh at My Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Vicky Cristina Barcelona", "Easy Virtue", "JFK", "The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Try Seventeen", "Paint Your Wagon", "Firefox", "Broadway Danny Rose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Mr. Tadano's Secret Mission: From Japan with Love", "The Front", "Billu Barber", "Coriolanus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["The 39 Steps", "Bulletproof", "Psycho", "New York Stories"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Gone Girl", "Paul", "The Curse of the Jade Scorpion", "Grand Canyon"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Time Share", "Husbands and Wives", "The Outsiders", "Babes in Toyland"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Adaptation", "Everyone Says I Love You", "Any Given Sunday", "Tooth Fairy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["The Ladykillers", "Where the Truth Lies", "Turn It Up", "Bullets Over Broadway"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Cassandra's Dream", "The Manxman", "Saugandh", "Hansel & Gretel: Witch Hunters"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Rocky IV", "Deconstructing Harry", "The Cable Guy", "Training Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Tears of the Sun", "The Outsiders", "Manhattan Murder Mystery", "ATL"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Cupid & Cate", "Mallrats", "Radio Days", "Tashan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Woody Allen?", "answers": ["Duplicate", "Whatever Works", "The Will Smith Music Video Collection", "Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Cyborg 2", "The River Wild", "Bhool Bhulaiyaa", "I Am Legend"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Margaret", "Showtime", "Salt", "Mighty Aphrodite"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Beowulf", "One More Kiss", "She's the One", "The 40-Year-Old Virgin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Gia", "Rebecca", "The Iceman Tapes: Conversations with a Killer", "Speed 2: Cruise Control"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["The Topkapi Affair", "The Mexican", "Fist of Fury", "Reign Over Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["The Woodsman", "Life Is Beautiful", "Lovesick", "Amistad"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Lonely Hearts", "Valentine's Day", "Island in the Sky", "Lara Croft Tomb Raider: The Cradle of Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Don", "Alexander", "Gundaraj", "Philadelphia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["A Mighty Heart", "The Big Picture", "Holi", "Nepali"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Foxfire", "The Legend of Bagger Vance", "Just for Laughs: Stand-Up: Vol. 3: Launching Pad", "Airheads"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Atlanta Symphony Golden Anniversary", "The Rock", "Under Capricorn", "Maleficent"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["McQ", "Looking for a Home", "Golmaal: Fun Unlimited", "Kung Fu Panda"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["The Defender", "The Corruptor", "Angela & Viril", "Cobra"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Kevin Hart: Let Me Explain", "Hell's Kitchen", "Hoshi o Katta Hi", "Madea's Big Happy Family: The Play"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Playing God", "Rumble Fish", "Batman Begins", "Daulat Ki Jung"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Daddy and Them", "February 14", "Always", "George Wallace"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Mr. & Mrs. Smith", "Khiladi 786", "Khamoshi: The Musical", "Brazil"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["The Skeleton Dance", "Wanted", "The Whole Nine Yards", "Foxcatcher"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Mojave Moon", "Tyler Perry's Madea's Family Reunion", "Dolphin Tale", "Stepmom"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Way of the Dragon", "Graveyard Shift", "Stephen King's Desperation", "In the Land of Blood and Honey"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["The Incredibles", "WWE Tagged Classics 2003: Royal Rumble", "Kung Fu Panda 3", "Evolution"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Beyond Borders", "Apocalypto", "Coogan's Bluff", "T2 3-D:Battle Across Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Band of Brothers", "Fast & Furious 6", "Ek Hi Raasta", "Pushing Tin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Volunteers", "Changeling", "8mm", "Anjaam"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["O.S.O.", "Salt 2", "Fast Five", "Six Degrees of Separation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Fast & Furious 7", "Life or Something Like It", "Morgan and Destiny's Eleventeenth Date: The Zeppelin Zoo", "Jay and Silent Bob Strike Back"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Cool World", "Without Evidence", "Riddick: Blindsided", "Two Bits"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Love Today", "Hollow Man", "The Appointments of Dennis Jennings", "Kung Fu Panda 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Captain Corelli's Mandolin", "Thelma & Louise", "Alice & Viril", "The Fifth Element"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["The Front", "Big", "The Bone Collector", "Big Fish"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Anand", "Pokiri", "A Place in Time", "Blow Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Bangkok Dangerous", "Bon Voyage", "Taking Lives", "Doctor Who and the Curse of Fatal Death"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Cleopatra", "Stalk of the Celery Monster", "Room 10", "Stalk of the Celery Monster"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Dus", "Footloose", "The Good Shepherd", "We're Back! A Dinosaur's Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Sachein", "Conan the Barbarian", "Rowan Atkinson Live!", "True Women"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["The Founding of a Republic", "The Undefeated", "Lookin' to Get Out", "Riddle"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Original Sin", "Ishq", "Northern Lights", "Curious George"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["The Legend 2", "Kung Fu Panda Holiday", "Blue", "Scooby-Doo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Har Dil Jo Pyar Karega", "Playing by Heart", "Once Upon a Time Again", "Unbreakable"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["One Hundred and One Dalmatians", "Muniyandi Vilangial Moonramandu", "The Number 23", "Gone in Sixty Seconds"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Broken Arrow", "From Dusk Till Dawn 2: Texas Blood Money", "Singham", "Love Is All There Is"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Mean Streets", "Striking Distance", "Lara Croft: Tomb Raider", "Conan the Barbarian"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas", "The Fever", "Collateral", "Antz"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["The Tourist", "Traveller", "Kiki's Delivery Service", "Too Young to Die?"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Hackers", "The Maker", "Dream for an Insomniac", "Amazing Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Hamlet", "Fast & Furious", "Shark Tale", "The Passion of the Christ"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["The Thin Pink Line", "This Boy's Life", "Sky Captain and the World of Tomorrow", "Hanover Street"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["200 Cigarettes", "Coimbatore Mappillai", "Kung Fu Panda: Secrets of the Masters", "Born to Defence"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Angelina Jolie?", "answers": ["Popeye", "Shadow of a Doubt", "Unbroken", "Rambo: First Blood Part II"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Taking Lives", "The Adventures of Tintin: The Secret of the Unicorn", "Dolores Claiborne", "Tremors"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["King Lear", "Horrible Bosses 2", "Losing Chase", "Heartbreak Ridge"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Angels in America", "National Lampoon's Animal House", "Firewall", "Midnight Run"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Wild Things", "Nishabd", "Kadhalukku Mariyadhai", "Presidential Reunion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["O.S.O.", "The Air I Breathe", "The Wise Little Hen", "The Contortionist's Handbook"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Last Hero in China", "The Air Up There", "Hackers", "Castle in the Sky: Bonus Material"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Nothing Too Good for a Cowboy", "Quicksilver", "The Witches", "Million Dollar Baby"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Family Plot", "Children of the Corn", "Taps", "Friday the 13th"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["100 Years of Comedy", "Pet Sematary", "Trapped", "Khatta Meetha"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Kyon Ki", "Saajan", "The Devil's Advocate", "Apollo 13"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["R.I.P.D.", "Escape to Victory", "Catch .44", "Premonition"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Apocalypse Now Redux", "Thulladha Manamum Thullum", "Riddick: Blindsided", "The Woodsman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Merry Mirthquakes", "Eliza Graves", "Raising Arizona", "Death Sentence"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Step Up", "My One and Only", "D-Tox", "Cop Land"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Hamlet", "Forty Deuce", "Vettaikkaaran", "Pilot Season"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Hang 'Em High", "Traveller", "Picture Perfect", "Don Juan DeMarco"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Batman vs. Superman", "X-Men", "An American Tail: Fievel Goes West", "The Devil's Advocate"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Sin City", "Class", "Menace II Society", "Frost/Nixon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["The Big Picture", "So Undercover", "The Searchers", "Peter Pan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Entourage", "Charlotte's Web", "Where the Truth Lies", "Phool Aur Kaante"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Troy", "Cinderella", "Coming to America", "Pyrates"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["The Myth", "Cliffhanger", "Stir of Echoes", "Patch Adams"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["JFK", "Heyy Babyy", "Rain Man", "Rocky IV"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Longshot", "Reservoir Dogs", "The Medallion", "Criminal Law"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Tees Maar Khan", "Frankie and Johnny", "Soul Men", "Telling Lies in America"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Lock Up", "Marlowe", "Man on Fire", "Loverboy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Lone Survivor", "Everybody's Fine", "Knight and Day", "Mystic River"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Glengarry Glen Ross", "Ek Tha Tiger", "Making Sandwiches", "The River Wild"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Schindler's List", "Best of Raw: Vol. 1", "X-Men: First Class", "Wheels on Meals"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Elephant White", "The Secrets of Jonathan Sperry", "The Undefeated", "Dumb and Dumber To"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Jayne Mansfield's Car", "Sleepwalkers", "Salt", "The Master"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Murder in the First", "How to Train Your Dragon 3", "We Are One: The Obama Inaugural Celebration at the Lincoln Memorial", "Turbo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Half Past Autumn", "Flatliners", "Speed", "Hitting It Hard"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["She's Having a Baby", "Children of the Corn", "Since You've Been Gone", "Brubaker"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Gia", "Boobie", "Beauty Shop", "Black"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Hellfighters", "Veer-Zaara", "Kill Bill Volume 2", "Hollow Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["End of the Line", "Andaz Naya Naya", "Edge of Darkness", "The Paradine Case"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Courage Under Fire", "The Expendables 3", "End of Days", "Taking Chance"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["A Few Good Men", "G.I. Joe: Retaliation", "Miss Congeniality", "Firelight"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Rails & Ties", "Shahenshah", "Brazil", "The Pelican Brief"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Romeo Must Die", "Footloose", "Jumper", "The Color of Money"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Solaris", "Jism 2", "Cop Land", "Digging to China"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Super", "Maximum Overdrive", "The Precious One", "Johnny Suede"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Rango", "Tashan", "Empire of the Sun", "My Dog Skip"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["The Front", "Sudden Impact", "Sleepers", "Frost on Satire"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["The King of Comedy", "The Virginity Hit", "Balto", "Six Days Seven Nights"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Thamizhan", "Ash Wednesday", "White Water Summer", "Toy Story 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Kevin Bacon?", "answers": ["Diner", "Bronco Billy", "Punch-Drunk Love", "Jo Jeeta Wohi Sikandar"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see J. D. Salinger?", "answers": ["Pari", "The Foot Shooting Party", "Lock Up", "Scary Movie 4"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["North by Northwest", "The Great Gatsby", "Looper", "Chisum"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Suhaag", "Frankenweenie (1984)", "Random Hearts", "Ram Jaane"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Shahenshah", "Killing Season", "Carlito's Way", "Loomis Fargo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Ed Wood", "What's Eating Gilbert Grape", "Deva", "Zanjeer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Ab Tumhare Hawale Watan Saathiyo", "How to Swim", "Cassandra's Dream", "WWE: King of the Ring 2000"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Find Me Guilty", "Namak Halaal", "The Horse Soldiers", "Man on Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["2 Guns", "Grease", "Yaarana", "Deuce Bigalow: European Gigolo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Jersey Girl", "Kaalia", "White House Down", "The Cowboys"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Inception", "Romeo + Juliet", "Arthur and the Vengeance of Maltazard", "Baghban"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Scarecrow", "Loverboy", "Mohabbatein", "Gossip with the Girls"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Veer-Zaara", "Absolute Power", "Rambo: First Blood Part II", "Daddy and Them"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Treasure Island", "Jhoom Barabar Jhoom", "Jewel of the Sahara", "Chennai Kadhal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["The Chronicles of Riddick", "Saudagar", "For Queen and Country", "12 Monkeys"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Crank: High Voltage", "The Accidental Spy", "Satyagraha", "Silver Linings Playbook"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Sangram", "Time Changer", "Baabul", "Pipe Dream"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["The Sorcerer's Apprentice", "Turbo", "Don", "Minsara Kanna"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Entourage", "Drive Angry", "Adalat", "Rio Bravo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Besharam", "Mazes and Monsters", "Big Fish", "The Brave Heart Will Take the Bride"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Mary Reilly", "Yes Boss", "Naseeb", "The Break-Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["I am Here", "The Pelican Brief", "The Iron Giant", "Agneepath"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Toofan", "Romeo + Juliet", "Ender's Game", "The Love Guru"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Suspect Zero", "Monte Carlo", "Death to Smoochy", "Muqaddar Ka Sikandar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Nishabd", "Madea's Witness Protection", "The Bone Collector", "The Monuments Men"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Black", "Find Me Guilty", "Rajavin Parvaiyile", "Tees Maar Khan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Johnny Suede", "Dostana", "I'm Still Here: Real Diaries of Young People Who Lived During the Holocaust", "Flawless"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["The Company Men", "Deewaar", "Parker", "Spy Kids"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Babylon A.D.", "Vertigo", "Oscar", "English Vinglish"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Benny & Joon", "Bhoothnath", "Patch Adams", "Fifty Shades of Blue"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Children of the Corn: The Final Sacrifice", "Jersey Girl", "Fu gui fu yun", "Mard"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Fast Food", "Scavenger Hunt", "Amar Akbar Anthony", "Needful Things"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Coolie", "Carbon Copy", "Priyamudan", "The Newton Boys"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["The Brazilian Job", "Cutting Class", "Bbuddah... Hoga Terra Baap", "Battlefield Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Once Upon a Time in China", "Rasigan", "Vettaikkaaran", "Sooryavansham"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Grudge Match", "Super 8", "Khushi", "The Adjustment Bureau"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["The Devil's Advocate", "The Gauntlet", "Sharaabi", "The Lodger: A Story of the London Fog"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["The Chain Reaction", "Sholay", "That Thing You Do!", "Biwi No.1"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Renaissance Man", "Live by Night", "Machine Gun Preacher", "Anand"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Babylon A.D.", "Aarakshan", "Enemy of the State", "Mrs. Brown"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["The Yards", "Sarkar", "Around the World in 80 Days", "Ladder 49"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Say Anything...", "Paa", "Stardust Memories", "Star Wars Episode II: Attack of the Clones"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["The Match Girl", "Aankhen", "The United States of Leland", "Commando"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Never Say Goodbye", "All About Steve", "Charlotte's Web", "Saved!"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Lawaaris", "Mei and the Kittenbus", "The Switch", "Chasing Mavericks"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["The River", "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham", "Going All the Way", "The Untouchables"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Michael Collins", "Hum", "State of Play", "Doogal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Silsila", "The Accidental Spy", "Saving Mr. Banks", "CZ12"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["The Jayne Mansfield Story", "Kanden Kadhalai", "Terminator 3: Rise of the Machines", "Aladin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["What Lies Beneath", "Namastey London", "He's Just Not That Into You", "Kabhi Kabhie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Jodhaa Akbar", "Beyond All Boundaries", "El Dorado", "Celebrity"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Abhimaan", "August Rush", "Irokoishi", "8"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Amitabh Bachchan?", "answers": ["Khuda Gawah", "The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring", "Stardust Memories", "Changing Lanes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Tum Mere Ho", "The War", "The Other Guys NYPD Recruitment Video", "Gair"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["12 Years a Slave", "Omkara", "Isi Ka Naam Zindagi", "Joe Kidd"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["The Adventures of Tom Thumb and Thumbelina", "Mangal Pandey: The Rising", "The Island of Doctor Agor", "The Bourne Identity"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["A Mother's Tears", "Mumbai Diaries", "Kung Fu Panda 3", "Deep Blue Sea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Darr", "U Me Aur Hum", "Don Juan DeMarco", "Dil"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Eyes Wide Shut", "Zandalee", "A Bronx Tale", "Lagaan: Once Upon a Time in India"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Sachein", "Suspicion", "Awwal Number", "Blood Work"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["The Corruptor", "The Story of Us", "Madhosh", "D-Tox"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["McLintock!", "Ghulam", "My Big Fat Greek Wedding", "Humko Deewana Kar Gaye"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Stir of Echoes", "Nishabd", "All the Best: Fun Begins", "Ghajini"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["When Corruption Was King", "Ion", "Wanderlust", "Dil Hai Ke Manta Nahin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Aatank Hi Aatank", "Kevin Hart: I'm a Grown Little Man", "The Fighter", "Thick as Thieves"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["The River Wild", "Fanaa", "Babes in Toyland", "Let Go"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring", "Spirit: Stallion of the Cimarron", "The House Bunny", "Jawani Zindabad"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["The Thin Pink Line", "Sand and Sorrow", "The Aviator", "Talaash"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Rio Lobo", "Revenge for Jolly!", "Saludos Amigos", "Peekay"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Talladega Nights: The Ballad of Ricky Bobby", "Sarfarosh", "The Machine", "Tremors"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Earth", "Talladega Nights: The Ballad of Ricky Bobby", "The Believer", "Beetlejuice"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Raja Hindustani", "Machete", "The Kid", "De Dana Dan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Jaane Tu Ya Jaane Na", "Poor Things", "Desi Boyz", "Namastey London"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Out of Sight", "Graveyard Shift", "Rang De Basanti", "The Man Who Shot Liberty Valance"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Sesame Street: Singing with the Stars", "Gangaajal", "Dhoom 3: Back in Action", "Pain & Gain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Being Human", "Priya: The Charming Girl of India", "Something to Talk About", "Nausica\u00e4 of the Valley of the Wind"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Seval", "Live Free or Die Hard", "Dil Chahta Hai", "Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Meng li xi shi", "Young and Innocent", "Black and White", "Madness In The Desert"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", "Over the Hedge", "The Magic of Belle Isle", "Yaadon Ki Baaraat"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Side Effects", "Horton Hears a Who!", "Secret Agent", "Munna Bhai Chale Amerika"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Going All the Way", "Boys", "Daulat Ki Jung", "Arthur and the Vengeance of Maltazard"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Valentine's Day", "Frankenweenie (1984)", "Bollywood Dreams", "The Bourne Identity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Temptation: Confessions of a Marriage Counselor", "Don: The Chase Begins Again", "Shakti: The Power", "Naye Nagme: Vol. 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Holi", "Twins", "Edward Scissorhands", "Thunderbolt and Lightfoot"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Thuppakki", "Raakh", "Super Rhino", "Nothing in Common"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Pecan Pie", "Akele Hum Akele Tum", "White House Down", "Naked in New York"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Reindeer Games", "Delhi Belly", "Dear John", "Movie 43"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Premonition", "Crimes and Misdemeanors", "Baazi", "Larry Crowne"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Babylon A.D.", "Sleeping Beauty", "She's the Man", "Ishq"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["City Hall", "Crank: High Voltage", "Be Cool", "Andaz Apna Apna"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Mr. Popper's Penguins", "Valley Girl", "Ali", "Hum Hain Rahi Pyar Ke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Gardener of Eden", "Jo Jeeta Wohi Sikandar", "Blossoms & Blood", "Bagavathi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Bhoothnath", "Sky", "Stage Fright", "Like Stars on Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Mann", "The Enforcer", "The Negotiator", "Ransom"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Three Mississippi", "Daredevil", "Mela", "SugarTime"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Eddie Presley", "The Money Pit", "3 Idiots", "Mission: Impossible"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["New Police Story", "Rio Lobo", "Love Love Love", "First Blood"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Dhadkan", "Bad Boys", "Deewana Mujh Sa Nahin", "Robin Williams: Weapons of Self-Destruction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Without Limits", "xXx", "Peepli Live", "The Manchurian Candidate"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Star Kid", "Rajavin Parvaiyile", "Andaz Naya Naya", "Yeh Hai Jalwa"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Men in Black", "Foxcatcher", "35 and Ticking", "Qayamat Se Qayamat Tak"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["Riddle", "The American", "Green Zone", "Parampara"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Aamir Khan?", "answers": ["The Longest Day", "Boobie", "Dinner for Schmucks", "Afsana Pyaar Ka"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Abraham Zapruder?", "answers": ["Gun Shy", "Zapruder film", "Suspect Zero", "The Beach"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Gnomeo & Juliet", "Arabian Nights", "The Avengers", "The Simple Life of Noah Dearborn"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Swiss Family Robinson", "G.I. Joe: Retaliation", "The Precious One", "The Office Party"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Hum Aapke Hain Kaun...!", "Pain & Gain", "The Incredibles", "Hearts in Atlantis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Untitled The Departed 2 Sequel", "Trucks", "Bullet to the Head", "Best of Raw: Vol. 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Bandhan", "Drive Angry", "The Good Shepherd", "Race to Witch Mountain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["The Wicker Man", "G-Force", "WWE Tagged Classics 2003: No Way Out", "Nanban"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Journey 3: From the Earth to the Moon", "Too Late for Divorce", "Argo", "Saving Private Ryan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Second Glance", "The Dark Side of the Sun", "Salem's Lot", "Untitled Miami Athletes Project"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Return to Horror High", "Southland Tales", "The Bank Job", "Sarfarosh"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Naajayaz", "Lincoln", "The Bowling Ball", "The Scorpion King"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Himmatwala", "Crossing Over", "Gridiron Gang", "Schindler's List"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["The Island of Doctor Agor", "Empire State", "Happy Feet", "The Truman Show"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Snitch", "All About Steve", "Diljale", "Seeking a Friend for the End of the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Tales from Earthsea", "Grudge Match", "Gravity", "WWE: WrestleMania 27: Vol. 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Ciudad", "Get Shorty", "Lucky: No Time for Love", "Mandela: Long Walk to Freedom"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Hollywood Homicide", "The Mummy Returns", "Hope Springs", "Anger Management"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["WWE Tagged Classics 2003: Royal Rumble", "The Defender", "Mean Streets", "Schindler's List"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Royal Rumble", "The Good German", "Goodbye Lover", "Sleepless in Seattle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["What's Eating Gilbert Grape", "Inception", "Lore", "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Oliver Twist", "Faster", "Judwaa", "Bhool Bhulaiyaa"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Namak Halaal", "The Final Cut", "WWE: The Videos: Vol. 1: Ramped Up", "Hum Saath-Saath Hain: We Stand United"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Getaway", "Fast & Furious 6", "Bringing Out the Dead", "Mazes and Monsters"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Con Air", "Longshot", "La escribana de uraba", "The Happiest Millionaire"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Born to Defence", "Journey 2: The Mysterious Island", "Lifeboat", "The Million Dollar Hotel"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["WWE: King of the Ring 2002", "Bobby", "Kaalia", "Soul Men"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["From up on Poppy Hill", "Walking Tall", "New Year's Eve", "Find Me Guilty"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Try Seventeen", "Fighting", "WWE: King of the Ring 2000", "Apocalypto"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["The Lone Ranger", "Fast Five", "Mandela: Long Walk to Freedom", "Intolerable Cruelty"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Two Mules for Sister Sara", "Planet 51", "Nick of Time", "The Lodger: A Story of the London Fog"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Pawnshop Chronicles", "Nim's Island", "The Dark Half", "The Other Guys"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Hercules in New York", "Ek Tha Tiger", "Stone Cold Steve Austin: The Bottom Line on the Most Popular Superstar of All Time", "Bollywood Dreams"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Signs of Life", "Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man's Chest", "Stardust", "Tooth Fairy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Fast & Furious 7", "Nilaave Vaa", "Black", "Night at the Museum: Battle of the Smithsonian"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["February 14", "Reno 911!: Miami", "Death Becomes Her", "Green Street"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Dhoom 3: Back in Action", "Old School", "Rudderless", "WrestleMania XXX"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Star Wars Holiday Special", "Captain America: The First Avenger", "Imagine", "The Game Plan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Cry Freedom", "Dil", "Linda Lovelace for President", "Be Cool"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Number Seventeen", "Hercules: The Thracian Wars", "The Lego Movie", "Into the Woods"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Spy Hunter", "Chaos", "Wrestling with Angels: Playwright Tony Kushner", "Stuck on You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Lions for Lambs", "Looper", "The Rundown", "Catch Me If You Can"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Inglourious Basterds", "A Nightmare on Elm Street", "Scarecrow", "WWE: WrestleMania 27: Vol. 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Hulchul", "Three O'Clock High", "The Guiding Light", "Brock Lesnar: Here Comes the Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Doom", "The Dead Zone", "Creepshow 2", "Forrest Gump"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Dwayne Johnson?", "answers": ["Thunderbolt and Lightfoot", "Vampire's Kiss", "Road to Perdition", "Get Smart"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Soul Men", "Firefox", "Mela", "Ghajini"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Arwin!", "Shaft", "Chalte Chalte", "Two of a Kind"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Pirates of the Caribbean: At World's End", "Unbreakable", "Ocean's Thirteen", "Who Do I Gotta Kill?"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Untitled Terrence Malick project", "Hostage", "The Pacifier", "XXX: State of the Union"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Unity", "Pulp Fiction", "The Man Who Shot Liberty Valance", "A River Runs Through It"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Sarkar", "Saving Face", "Basic", "Lean on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Mohabbatein", "Jumper", "Toy Story 3", "She's So Lovely"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Nick of Time", "Star Wars Episode III: Revenge of the Sith", "Boss", "Taking Chance"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Blossoms & Blood", "Cleaner", "The Animal", "Pocahontas"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Josh", "The Secrets of Jonathan Sperry", "Arena", "The Protector"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["The Negotiator", "Atlanta Symphony Golden Anniversary", "Remember the Titans", "Manhattan Murder Mystery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Jeet", "The Color Purple", "Tyler Perry's Madea's Family Reunion", "Star Wars Episode II: Attack of the Clones"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Kicking & Screaming", "Jack & Jill", "The Long Kiss Goodnight", "The Book of Eli"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Heroes", "Meeting Evil", "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial", "The Other Guys NYPD Recruitment Video"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey", "Fresh", "Convention", "Ek Tha Tiger"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Zelig", "Deep Blue Sea", "Empire of the Sun", "Jo Jeeta Wohi Sikandar"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Mazes and Monsters", "Jaan", "The Samaritan", "Mandela: Long Walk to Freedom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Alice", "Wild at Heart", "Azhagiya Tamil Magan", "Snakes on a Plane"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["The 11th Hour", "Captain Corelli's Mandolin", "True Romance", "Unidentified"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Independence Day", "Firefox", "Iron Man 2", "Garv"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Ocean Heaven", "xXx", "Comic Relief IV", "Office Killer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Dulhan Hum Le Jayenge", "True Crime", "Dan in Real Life", "Rules of Engagement"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Serpico", "Stone", "The Avengers: Age of Ultron", "Kanden Kadhalai"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Runaway Bride", "Life or Something Like It", "O.S.O.", "Lakeview Terrace"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Merry Mirthquakes", "Beretta's Island", "Karan Arjun", "1408"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Amar Akbar Anthony", "Planet Terror", "Goodfellas", "Paycheck"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["The Journey of Natty Gann", "Be Cool", "Coming to America", "The Panic in Needle Park"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["The Man", "Amistad", "Swordsman II", "Celebrating AFI"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["The Whole Nine Yards", "Jackie Brown", "Commando", "Mandingo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["That Thing You Do!", "The Spirit", "Frenzy", "In Harm's Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Dumb & Dumber", "The Angriest Man in Brooklyn", "The Avengers", "Drillbit Taylor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["The Incredibles", "Nighthawks", "Maximum Overdrive", "Footloose"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Captain America: The Winter Soldier", "One Hundred and One Nights", "Rat Race", "Don's Plum"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["The Medallion", "Rob-B-Hood", "The Jungle Book", "Menace II Society"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Do the Right Thing", "Sangharsh", "Dinner for Schmucks", "Curious George"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["A Time to Kill", "Yuvvraaj", "Big Fish", "Dream for an Insomniac"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Where the Wild Things Are", "Dinner for Schmucks", "All the Best: Fun Begins", "Captain America: The First Avenger"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Jungle Fever", "Ghulam", "I am Here", "Half Nelson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Love Part 2", "One Eight Seven", "Around the World in 80 Days", "Grindhouse"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Grown Ups 2", "Kill Bill Volume 2", "Shinjuku Incident", "Man About Town"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Cop Out", "Slow Burn", "Oldboy", "Rat Race"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Copper Mountain", "The Other Guys", "The Chronicles of Riddick: Dark Fury", "The Expendables 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Rudderless", "Deewangee", "Django Unchained", "Gardener of Eden"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Unthinkable", "Shakespeare in Love", "Destiny Turns on the Radio", "Ocean Heaven"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace", "Curly Sue", "The Mission", "Amistad"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Coach Carter", "Ted", "Frenzy", "The Orphan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Akele Hum Akele Tum", "Die Hard with a Vengeance", "Pirates of the Caribbean 5", "Devdas"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Turbo", "Legalese", "Rat Race", "Mystic River"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["Dragon Lord", "The Robber Bride", "The Story of Us", "Jurassic Park"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["S.W.A.T.", "Another Woman", "Three Kings", "Shahjahan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see Samuel L. Jackson?", "answers": ["The Brave", "Black Snake Moan", "Zandalee", "Kaze Tachinu"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["The Third Wheel", "Two of a Kind", "The Brave Heart Will Take the Bride", "The Goonies"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Pudhiya Geethai", "Out of Time", "Braveheart", "Look Who's Talking Too"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Tim", "Life or Something Like It", "Look Who's Talking", "Vertigo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Dial M for Murder", "Predator", "Hairspray", "Two Mules for Sister Sara"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["The Conqueror", "Face/Off", "In the Line of Fire", "Geronimo: An American Legend"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Pilot Season", "The Animal", "Savages", "Endrendrum Kadhal"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Awwal Number", "Killing Season", "Daredevil", "Rajavin Parvaiyile"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Tai Chi Master", "Ride Along", "Domestic Disturbance", "Predator"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["People I Know", "Wrestling with Angels: Playwright Tony Kushner", "Saturday Night Fever", "Red Heat"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Tooth Fairy", "Child in the Night", "She's So Lovely", "The Bank Job"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Megamind: The Button of Doom", "The Sugarland Express", "Shout", "Firewall"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["The Great Buck Howard", "Tere Naam", "Ladder 49", "Super"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["How to Swim", "Hollywood on Fire", "Staying Alive", "Tai Chi Master"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["The Wrong Man", "Pulp Fiction", "Kujiratori", "Kiki's Delivery Service"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Mr. & Mrs. Smith", "An Unfinished Life", "Swordfish", "Jawani Zindabad"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Rocky III", "SugarTime", "GOTTI: In The Shadow Of My Father", "Salaam-e-Ishq: A Tribute to Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Blades of Glory", "Eyes of an Angel", "Frost/Nixon", "Batman Returns"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Ask the Dust", "Grease", "U Me Aur Hum", "The Tall Guy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["The Good Son", "Pocahontas", "Blow Out", "Quicksilver"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["The Fast and the Furious", "The Air Up There", "A.I. Artificial Intelligence", "A Civil Action"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Tyler Perry's Laugh to Keep from Crying", "Geronimo: An American Legend", "Look Who's Talking Now", "The Client"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Murder in Mind", "Transcendence", "The Cable Guy", "Primary Colors"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Casino Royale", "Broken Arrow", "How to Fish", "The Chain Reaction"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["The Rookie", "The Patriot", "Michael", "Twilight Zone: The Movie"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Glory", "Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade", "Moment by Moment", "Ender's Game"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Desperado", "Be Cool", "Apocalypse Now", "Assassins"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["El Dorado", "The Gnome-Mobile", "Fearless", "Urban Cowboy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["The Boy in the Plastic Bubble", "Witness", "McQ", "Silver Linings Playbook"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Divine Secrets of the Ya-Ya Sisterhood", "Lucky Numbers", "The Skeleton Dance", "Risky Business"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Talaash: The Hunt Begins...", "School Ties", "The Thin Red Line", "Machete"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Himmatwala", "Battlefield Earth", "Meng li xi shi", "The Sugarland Express"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["The Sea Chase", "Jayne Mansfield's Car", "Cutting Class", "The General's Daughter"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Jawani Zindabad", "Untitled Miami Athletes Project", "Get Shorty", "The Robber Bride"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Daddy", "Changeling", "The Prince of Egypt", "Chains of Gold"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Old Dogs", "Major Saab", "Day-O", "The Hardy Men"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["The Devil's Rain", "Riddick: Blindsided", "Wild Wild West", "An Unfinished Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Get Carter", "The Experts", "Dolphin Tale", "Vampire's Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Phenomenon", "The Bowling Ball", "Gia", "The Numbers Station"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["FernGully: The Last Rainforest", "Just Go With It", "Boris and Natasha: The Movie", "Kill Bill Volume 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["The Blind Side", "Basic", "Nausica\u00e4 of the Valley of the Wind", "Rango"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Saving Mr. Banks", "The Proposal", "Carrie", "White Water Summer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Star Wars Episode IV: A New Hope", "White Man's Burden", "An Unfinished Life", "Kaal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["London", "The Taking of Pelham 123", "Bewafaa", "A Bucket of Blood"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["The Frisco Kid", "Fracture", "The Garden of Last Days", "Perfect"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Sachein", "Escape Plan", "Lonely Hearts", "Jumper"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street", "The Punisher", "Shinjuku Incident", "Take the Money and Run"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["We're Back! A Dinosaur's Story", "Chandni Chowk to China", "Wild Hogs", "Dog Day Afternoon"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Spring Breakers", "Deva", "Bolt", "Plane Crazy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["The Pursuit of Happyness", "The Perfect Storm", "Mad City", "G.I. Joe: The Rise of Cobra"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Judge Dredd", "A Love Song for Bobby Long", "From Dusk till Dawn", "The Thin Pink Line"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "In which movie you can see John Travolta?", "answers": ["Revolver", "From Paris with Love", "Suits", "Bambi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}